<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Money Talks</title>
		<link>https://web.24syv.dk/channels/91</link>
		<description>Our editors and correspondents give their authoritative take on the markets, the economy and the world of business. Published every Wednesday by Economist Podcasts. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
		<language>da-DK</language>
		<itunes:image href="https://assets.listentonews.com/uploads/provider/logo/342/-k4bg127u-mt_itunes_new.jpg"/>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Is the car industry running out of gas?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/645d1fa6eff373001106232d/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Buying a car used to be about two things: style and performance. But as motorists trade in their petrol or diesel cars for electric vehicles, manufacturers are increasingly focusing on experience by adding features like karaoke machines and mood lighting. Those drivers also have a lot more choices. The ditching of internal combustion engines in favour of battery-power has allowed new car makers to enter the market. But rather than thinking like BMW or Ford, they are looking to firms like Apple for their inspiration.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Tom Lee-Devlin examine the remaking of the auto industry. The Economist’s Simon Wright explains that software, rather than hardware, will define car brands in the future. Henrik Fisker, the founder of one of those new brands, tells them that a history of making petrol-powered cars doesn’t necessarily qualify established car makers to make electric vehicles. And advisor Tu Le explains why Western car makers are worried about competition from China.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/645d1fa6eff373001106232d/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/645d1fa6eff373001106232d/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: A business podcast on the business of podcasts</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6453d4f99a120f0011f1c35e/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Around a third of Americans now listen to at least one podcast a week. That fact has not escaped the attention of advertisers, who spent nearly $2bn on podcast ads last year. But with more than 4m podcasts for listeners to choose from, the industry is facing a reckoning. On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird ask what the future holds for the business of podcasts. Michael Mignano, who used to manage Spotify’s podcasting arm, tells them that companies have realised they can be much leaner. And Nick Hilton, a podcast production company founder, explains why he thinks 2022 is the year when podcasting died.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6453d4f99a120f0011f1c35e/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 15:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6453d4f99a120f0011f1c35e/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Last dance for TikTok?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/644aadc3628a2400115da502/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Time may be running short for TikTok. In the US, both Democrats and Republicans view the Chinese-owned app as a national security threat and would like to ban it. It’s practically the only policy issue that the two parties agree on. And yet the politicians in Washington DC have left it very late to act. TikTok has already reached 150 million users in the US, half the country’s population, and every day it adds more.  On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird look at whether the fears about TikTok are well grounded, and what the options are for addressing them. The Economist’s Alexandra Suich Bass explains why alternatives short of an outright ban have gone nowhere. China security analyst Matthew Johnson says his biggest concern is that Beijing could use the app to spread pro-Chinese propaganda. Meanwhile, Nazak Nikakhtar, a former secretary of the US Commerce Department, suggests a way of neutralising the app without upsetting users.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/644aadc3628a2400115da502/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/644aadc3628a2400115da502/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Why oh why EY?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6441561b7301040011928715/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The professional services firm EY reportedly spent hundreds of millions of dollars preparing to split itself into separate audit and advisory companies. Then earlier this month it abruptly called the divorce off. EY is not unique. All of the &quot;big four&quot; accounting firms - including PwC, KPMG and Deloitte - combine the stodgy traditional business of audit with a fast-growing free-wheeling consultancy wing. On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird ask whether all four firms find themselves stuck in unhappy marriages. Professor Laura Empson of Bayes Business School retells how these one-time frumpy low-margin audit firms were beguiled by the glamour and big fees of corporate advisory work. Meanwhile Tom Rodenhauser, managing partner at Kennedy Research Reports, explains why the consulting units have now outgrown their auditing counterparts, and would do well to ditch them and go it alone.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6441561b7301040011928715/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6441561b7301040011928715/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Succession Asia</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/643834f5990bb700117e3772/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Fans of the popular television show “Succession” have been gripped by the family battle to take control of the fictional patriarch Logan Roy’s sprawling media empire. But across Asia family businesses are worried about their own, very real, succession battles as a new generation of plutocrats look to take over from their fathers.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Tom Lee-Devlin delve into the challenges facing some of Asia’s wealthiest families. Author, Joe Studwell, talks about some of the characters worrying about their legacy and Kevin Au from the Chinese University of Hong Kong explains how succession challenges can be overcome.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/643834f5990bb700117e3772/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 17:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/643834f5990bb700117e3772/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Will video games eat Hollywood?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/642ef82c63f9a20011635055/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Video game makers used to look to Hollywood for their inspiration. But in recent years, the market for games has grown to nearly $200bn, five times more than people spend at the box office and more, even, than they spend on streaming services like Netflix or Disney+. And that has caught the attention of the movie industry, which is now looking to game makers for its ideas.On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird examine how gaming took over media. Bad Robot is one of the film and television production companies that has expanded into gaming. Tanya Watson, president of Bad Robot Games, explains what game makers can learn from cinematographers but also what she has to teach them. And former Spotify executive Nick Lightle discusses why it could take some time before the streamers take over gaming.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/642ef82c63f9a20011635055/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 16:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/642ef82c63f9a20011635055/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The A to Z of economics</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6425c11a6f707e001185fbbe/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Hosts Alice Fulwood, Mike Bird and Tom Lee Devlin take to the road this week with a single aim: bring economics to life. The mission takes them to some unexpected corners of the world and forces them to don some interesting attire. Inspired by The Economist’s A-Z guide, Tom travels to one of the UK’s largest sandwich factories for a lesson in efficiency. Alice visit’s George Washington’s estate to understand how mercantilism made America the country it is today. And Mike learns how Singapore has overcome the limits of its sea border.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6425c11a6f707e001185fbbe/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:09</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6425c11a6f707e001185fbbe/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Discredit Suisse</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/641cb7c02424c300112415a2/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Few would have predicted that the demise of Silicon Valley Bank, a niche Californian lender, would be followed by the failure of Credit Suisse. But on March 19 the banking crisis reached Zurich, where regulators brokered a fire sale that saw the ailing 167-year-old bank sold to rival UBS.On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird chart the spread of the crisis and examine its fallout. Richard Berner, a former advisor to the Treasury Secretary, explains: “Silicon Valley Bank was not systemic in life, but proved to be systemic in death.” And Huw van Steenis, who used to advise the chief executive of UBS, explains how the crisis has roiled bond markets.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/641cb7c02424c300112415a2/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 20:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/641cb7c02424c300112415a2/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: What went wrong at SVB?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/641379c7bdb5eb00117d8964/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Until last week, most people beyond California and the tech world probably hadn’t heard of Silicon Valley Bank, but its swift collapse made headlines across the globe. On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird examine what brought the bank down and to what extent the panic has been contained–or might still be spreading. Peter Conti-Brown from University of Pennsylvania’s Wharton School says incompetence was behind the bank’s collapse. And former Treasury Secretary Larry Summers tells them the US government’s decision to guarantee deposits should be enough to restore confidence in the banks and prevent fear spreading.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/641379c7bdb5eb00117d8964/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 20:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/641379c7bdb5eb00117d8964/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The rise of the robots</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/640a385189451a0011d20674/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Robots are getting better and cheaper—and that means they will play a much larger role in our lives. They are already reaching beyond the car plants and warehouses, where they have become commonplace, to turn their mechanised hands to making cocktails and cooking chicken. But what will that mean for the economy?On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird examine whether the rise of the machines is good for workers and hear from Korea, where there are more robots per factory worker than any other country on earth. Kim Povlsen, the boss of robot-maker Universal Robots, says greater automation is needed as populations age and labour shortages become increasingly severe. And Susanne Bieller from the International Federation of Robotics, a global industry group, gives a glimpse of what the future might have in store.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/640a385189451a0011d20674/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/640a385189451a0011d20674/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Not made in China</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6400fc034ebfa8001081044b/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China was the source of $1trn-worth of electronic goods and components in 2021, roughly a third of the global total. And it’s not just consumer electronics that begin their life in China. The country is the source of everything from childrens’ toys to medical equipment—it dominates the global supply chain. But manufacturers are increasingly looking elsewhere to make their products as China’s rising wages and growing tensions with the US make its factories less attractive than its neighbours.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Tom Lee-Devlin look at Asia’s alternative manufacturing hubs. Manmohan Sodhi, professor of operations and supply chain management at Bayes business school in London, tells them that manufacturing requires more than just factories—it also needs universities, labs and designers. Former diplomat and trade negotiator Wendy Cutler, who is now vice president of the Asia Society Policy Institute, says today’s China-centric supply chain structure is no longer sustainable.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6400fc034ebfa8001081044b/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 19:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6400fc034ebfa8001081044b/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Could K-pop become a monopoly?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63f799930a0d230011758127/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The rise of Korea’s musicians from local celebrities to international superstars is credited to Lee Soo-man, the godfather of K-pop. The industry he developed gave rise to groups like BTS, which has been the biggest-selling band in the world for two years running. Now, Lee has sold most of his stake in SM Entertainment, the company he founded, to one of its biggest rivals.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Tom Lee-Devlin delve into the world of K-pop and examine how the businesses making one of Korea's newest export industries operate. Author, Mark Russell, tells them how K-pop went global. Analyst, Bokyung Suh, breaks down the secret to its commercial success, and explains whether fans should fear a potential K-pop commercial monopoly.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63f799930a0d230011758127/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 16:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63f799930a0d230011758127/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The king of quants</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63ee7d3f2b83290011ae3136/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Quantitative investors are known for their cool, mathematical approach to investing. They build models which search for patterns across huge data sets to discern where they should invest. The frenzied “bubble in everything” wrongfooted many quants in 2020–but the stock markets return to Earth, which crippled many traditional funds, generated huge returns for the quants in 2022. Nowhere was this clearer than in the performance of AQR Capital Management, a quant fund run by Cliff Asness. Its long-running strategy returned 43.5% last year, net of fees. On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird speak to Cliff Asness, the co-founder and chief investment officer of AQR, one of the world’s biggest quant fund managers. He tells them why he’s more open than his competitors and what still keeps him up at night. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks  For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63ee7d3f2b83290011ae3136/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63ee7d3f2b83290011ae3136/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Adani’s short story</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63e55e2176a4a40010955185/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Just weeks ago, Gautam Adani was the third richest person in the world. But he was caught short when Hindenburg Research, a small American short-seller, issued a report that spooked investors, wiping $100bn from the value of Adani firms.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Tom Lee-Devlin examine the allegations levelled at Adani’s firms, which the company has forcefully denied. The Economist’s Mumbai bureau chief, Tom Easton, talks them through Hindenburg’s report and Adani’s response. Analyst Mahesh Vyas considers the impact on Adani’s ability to borrow to fund infrastructure projects. And short-seller Andrew Left describes what it’s like to hit send on a report that’s intended to crash a firm’s stock price.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63e55e2176a4a40010955185/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 20:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63e55e2176a4a40010955185/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Goldman Sags</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63dc13593c0b1d00118f618a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Goldman once dominated Wall Street. In 2009, after the financial crisis, when most financial institutions were left reeling, Goldman had its best year ever. It appeared an apex-predator, one that could outsmart its rivals in even the toughest environments. But the last decade has been humbling for Goldman.On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird ask what is going wrong with Goldman Sachs. We hear how the bank grew from a basement office selling promissory notes in downtown Manhattan to become the most revered name on Wall Street. Analyst Steven Chubak tells us when things changed for Goldman, and how it is trying to adapt. And The Economist's Patrick Foulis says the bank’s mystique is at odds with its “mediocre, pedestrian and humdrum” valuation.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63dc13593c0b1d00118f618a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63dc13593c0b1d00118f618a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Can Disney rekindle the magic?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63d2e2be4e926200111c0c5a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The Walt Disney Company turns 100 years old this week. But the silver screen success that helped it become the world’s biggest entertainment company will not be enough to keep it on top for another century. As households swap cable packages for streaming, and kids turn to gaming, rather than movies, Disney needs reanimating.On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird ask whether Disney has lost its touch. The Economist’s Tom Wainwright takes us on a tour of the Magic Kingdom, to assess its sprawling empire. Analyst Rich Greenfield explains why the company is losing billions on streaming. And Matthew Ball, former head of strategy for Amazon Studios, tells us about the big bet Disney needs to make if it wants to retain its crown.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63d2e2be4e926200111c0c5a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 20:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63d2e2be4e926200111c0c5a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: How globalisation gave way</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63c9806487d5680011f551f3/media.mp3</link>
			<description>America has changed the way it views the rest of the world. Rather than pushing for a more globalised economy with fewer trade barriers, the US is now seeking a more protected system of international trade. President Biden’s Inflation Reduction Act promises nearly $400bn to boost clean energy and reduce dependence on China for things like batteries for electric cars. The Chips Act, meanwhile, provides incentives worth $52bn to boost America’s semiconductor industry.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood examine what this new zero-sum era means for the global economy. Chad Bown from the Peterson Institute for International Economics tells them the age of globalisation isn’t returning any time soon. Henry Gao from Singapore Management University blames America’s attempt to “out-China China by becoming more like China”.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63c9806487d5680011f551f3/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 18:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63c9806487d5680011f551f3/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The new power in the North Sea</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63c04831ed26ab0011c88317/media.mp3</link>
			<description>For decades, the North Sea’s fierce gales have created a challenge for those extracting the oil and gas buried beneath its swells. But the region’s poor weather is also the key to its future: offshore wind. And the plans are surprisingly ambitious.On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird ask whether the North Sea can turn green. The Economist’s Matthieu Favas says wind farms in the North Sea could power Europe’s 200m homes. Jesper Frost Rasmussen, mayor of Esbjerg, explains how the offshore wind industry has changed life in the Danish port town. Ulrik Stridbæk of Orsted, the world’s largest offshore wind developer, says that some sites are already generating the same amount of power as a large nuclear power station. Plus, we speak to Thomas Dalsgaard about why his firm, Copenhagen Infrastructure Partners, wants to build a physical island 100 kilometres off the coast of Denmark. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63c04831ed26ab0011c88317/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63c04831ed26ab0011c88317/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The economics of thinness</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63b72a7a938ea90011f2062f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Across the rich world there is a negative relationship between incomes and weight, as measured by body mass index. The richer people are, the thinner they tend to be. But separate the data by gender and a startling gap appears. Rich women are much thinner than poorer ones; but rich men and poor men are just as likely to be overweight or obese.On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood and Thomas Lee-Devlin examine why it may be rational, in economic terms, for ambitious women to pursue thinness. John Cawley of Cornell University explains his research that suggests overweight women have lower salaries than their thinner peers. We examine the legacy of Helen Gurley Brown, the outspoken former editor-in-chief of Cosmopolitan magazine, who championed dieting to get ahead. And Jennifer Shinall, a law professor at Vanderbilt University, considers potential solutions to weight-based discrimination.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63b72a7a938ea90011f2062f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 19:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63b72a7a938ea90011f2062f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: TikTok’s ticking time bomb—an episode from our archive</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63a45d124e50e40011cc7d2a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>It’s the fastest growing app in the world, filled with dance trends, cats misbehaving, and questionable financial advice. Teenagers love it; Western politicians are less convinced. Could TikTok’s popularity be its downfall?In one of our favourite episodes of 2022, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Soumaya Keynes investigate just who is afraid of TikTok’s growing influence. First, our media editor Tom Wainwright unpacks the relationship between TikTok, its parent company ByteDance, and its Chinese twin, Douyin. Then, AB Bernstein’s Robin Zhu outlines just how big a threat the app poses to the likes of Facebook, Snapchat, and YouTube. Plus, Federal Communications Commissioner Brendan Carr outlines his concerns about TikTok’s ability to harvest user data. And we ask: how long before this ticking geopolitical time-bomb blows up? Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63a45d124e50e40011cc7d2a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 16:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63a45d124e50e40011cc7d2a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Is Christmas becoming more efficient?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63a348961a67f20011fdebed/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Economists are a gloomy lot, and no less so at Christmas. Whereas most people see gift-giving as a source of joy, economists fret about the potential for misallocated resources. One Scrooge-ish study found that, on average, $100 spent on gifts was worth the same as around $85 of cash spent directly by the recipient. But are there reasons to believe that over time, Christmas is becoming more efficient?On this week’s podcast, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood hear from the father of Scroogenomics, Joel Waldfogel, about why Christmas may be improving for economists—even if it means fewer presents. And they speak to The Economist’s Ore Ogunbiyi about the nightmare after Christmas for retailers.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63a348961a67f20011fdebed/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 17:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63a348961a67f20011fdebed/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The changing ideology of Silicon Valley</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/639a17a11edbe60011f39be9/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Startup founders in Silicon Valley are often motivated by an almost religious idealism: young tech workers, looking to move fast and break things, want to use technology to make the world a better place. But 2022 has brought about a reckoning: the business models of once-star firms, such as Uber and Meta, are under threat; the allure of the dishevelled whizz-kid has been undermined by the downfall of Sam Bankman-Fried; and the expense of Palo Alto has pushed plucky startups out. The Bay Area has often been populated by liberals, but many of tech’s heroes, like Elon Musk and Marc Andreessen, have shifted to the right. On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Soumaya Keynes and Alice Fulwood ask whether Silicon Valley has lost its religion. Margaret O’Mara, professor of history at the University of Washington, reveals the Valley’s past. And Adrian Daub, the author of “What Tech Calls Thinking”, tells us that the secret of the successful founder is to bamboozle regulators while they make a bit more money.To help us improve our podcasts, please fill out a short questionnaire at economist.com/moneytalkssurveySign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/639a17a11edbe60011f39be9/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 18:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/639a17a11edbe60011f39be9/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: China reopens</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6390da7b6ad47e0010e6206f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China’s draconian zero-covid policies have required repeated and lengthy lockdowns, enormous make-shift quarantine facilities, and endless testing for the population. They have also done real damage to its economy. After rare outbreaks of protest against the policy in several cities, the strict rules that have smothered normal life around the country are being relaxed, after almost three years in place.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Soumaya Keynes and Alice Fulwood ask what this means for the Chinese economy—and the world. One of China’s best-known investors, Fred Hu, tells us the policy has been driving China’s economy “to the ground” and Goldman Sachs’ Andrew Tilton says that restrictions have shaved up to 5% off GDP growth. But what will happen as China opens up?Take our listener survey at economist.com/moneytalkssurveySign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6390da7b6ad47e0010e6206f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 18:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6390da7b6ad47e0010e6206f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The new rules of investment</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6387a46643ba18001168f473/media.mp3</link>
			<description>High inflation, amid warnings of a global recession, is forcing investors to tear up the rule book. Since the financial crisis, bonds have been seen as a safe bet—even if they did not promise much of a return. Equity markets, led by soaring tech stocks, were where fortunes were made. Both have plunged this year. In a world where rising interest rates have left governments worrying about how to afford their debts, and companies will struggle to raise cash, investors need new strategies.On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Soumaya Keynes and Mike Bird ask what those new rules of investing look like. Wei Li, global chief investment strategist for the world’s biggest investor, BlackRock, argues this new macroeconomic era is here to stay. And Mohamed El-Erian, chief economic adviser to Allianz, says investors need to focus on picking winners within stocks and bonds.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6387a46643ba18001168f473/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 18:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6387a46643ba18001168f473/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Why it’s time to talk about Indonesia</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/637e64554c25cc00106da84a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Indonesia is the world’s third-largest producer of coal. Not only does it power the country, it powers the economy. But the country’s president, Joko Widodo, wants to change that. Indonesia is garnering global attention due to its stock of nickel and cobalt, core elements in the batteries needed for the booming electric vehicle industry. Can the government swap the fossil-fuel-powered economy to one that runs on batteries instead?On this week’s podcast, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood ask whether Indonesia can really go green. Zanny Minton Beddoes, The Economist’s editor-in-chief, sits down with Joko Widodo to find out if he is the man to wean the country off coal. Finance minister Sri Mulyani Indrawati and education minister Nadiem Makarim tell us how to train a generation of battery-makers. And Patrick Foulis, our business-affairs editor, warns of a red flag.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/637e64554c25cc00106da84a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 19:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/637e64554c25cc00106da84a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The cryptocalypse </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63755d72a45feb0011b93f56/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Until last week, Sam Bankman-Fried - or SBF as he’s become known - was crypto’s poster-child. He was a regular in Washington, DC where he schmoozed journalists, regulators and lawmakers alike. He funded political campaigns and sponsored sports teams ranging from basketball to Formula One. For many, the floppy-haired, 30-year-old once-billionaire wasn’t just the face of his crypto trading firm FTX, he was the face of crypto. But last week, SBJ’s business, which was valued at $32bn at the start of the year, collapsed into bankruptcy and now he is being investigated by regulators and law-enforcement agencies.On this week’s “Money Talks’, hosts Alice Fulwood and Soumaya Keynes ask whether the crypto phenomenon can survive the loss of a figurehead. They speak with Alesia Haas, the CFO of the second-largest exchange Coinbase. And hear from some of the recipients of SBF’s contributions to the effective altruism movement about what’s next. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63755d72a45feb0011b93f56/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63755d72a45feb0011b93f56/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Is pay transparency good?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/636beba1feabb20012629a72/media.mp3</link>
			<description>On November 1st, New York City’s workers woke up to a new reality: every job listing for work that could be done in one of the five boroughs now had a stated salary band. Gossips rejoiced. But who does the law really benefit?On this week’s podcast, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood look at the pros and cons of pay transparency. First, they hear from Harvard Business School’s Zoe Cullen who says wages fell by 2% on average when firms opened up about pay. Then, they speak to Joel Gascoigne, the founder of online marketing firm Buffer, who went further than companies in New York and published each of his employees’ salaries, by name, on the company’s website (it lists his salary as $298,958). And then they go to Norway, where incomes have always been publicly available - and hear about the unexpected consequences on happiness when you can easily see what your friends, neighbours and enemies earn. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalksFor full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/636beba1feabb20012629a72/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 18:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/636beba1feabb20012629a72/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks:  The tech reckoning</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6362b3fe20b76a0011c56d1b/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Most of America’s biggest technology firms are having a bad time - and not just the ones who have been recently acquired by a mercurial billionaire. More than $1tn has been wiped from their market value in recent weeks. Is the sell-off just investor jitters? Or is it a symptom of something more fundamental about the future of the sector? On this week’s podcast, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood are joined by our technology editor Tom Wainwright and global business correspondent Thomas Lee-Devlin to diagnose the common problem facing the movers (like Uber), the streamers (like Netflix) and the creepers (like Facebook owner, Meta). And we ask what they can learn from China, where tech behemoth Alibaba has seen its share price plunge by 77% from a 2020 peak. Plus, we ask if this is a turning point - what does that mean for the future of the formerly most profitable sector in America?Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6362b3fe20b76a0011c56d1b/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 18:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6362b3fe20b76a0011c56d1b/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Wall Street's top cop</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/635983a21b1c6a0012a53824/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gary Gensler has spent just a little over a year and a half as the head of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), America’s top markets regulator. In that time, he’s proposed 40 separate filings for rules, given 60 speeches, and intervened, in sometimes controversial ways, in everything from crypto to SPACs to environmental regulations. In other words: he is getting a lot done and making a lot of people angry. On this week’s episode, hosts Alice Fulwood, Mike Bird and Soumaya Keynes sit down with Mr Gensler to try and figure out what he wants to accomplish and how he plans on getting it all done. They discuss everything from the functioning of the Treasury market, to efforts to prioritise retail investors in the wake of the meme-stock craze, to why he thought it was important that the SEC fine the reality television star Kim Kardashian.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/635983a21b1c6a0012a53824/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 18:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/635983a21b1c6a0012a53824/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: How to rebuild Ukraine</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/635047e26e8bc20012fbf1ce/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Ukraine’s economy is both hurting and defying expectations. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) estimates that GDP will shrink by 35% this year and inflation is running at 24%. Yet slowly and grimly the country’s economy has adapted to war—and seems to be growing again. What can and should the long march back to normalcy look like?On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Soumaya Keynes and Alice Fulwood are joined by our European economics editor Christian Odendahl and our Europe correspondent Matt Steinglass, who is in Ukraine, to discuss the country’s economic future. They hear from Yuriy Ryzhenkov, the boss of Metinvest, Ukraine’s largest steel company and the owner of the factory that became the site of a deadly siege in Mariupol, about how the firm is adapting. And Vladyslav Rashkovan, the alternate executive director at the IMF responsible for Ukraine, outlines the key areas Western powers should be thinking about in terms of their plans to offer reconstruction aid to the country.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/635047e26e8bc20012fbf1ce/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 19:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/635047e26e8bc20012fbf1ce/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Panic economics</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6347011ba23fcd0012cf2495/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This year’s Nobel prize in economics was awarded to Ben Bernanke, Philip Dybvig, and Douglas Diamond for their pioneering research into the role that banks play in financial crises. On this week’s episode, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood speak with Professors Dybvig and Diamond about their eponymous model of financial panics - one economics’ most cited papers - and ask whether policymakers have truly absorbed their insights.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6347011ba23fcd0012cf2495/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 19:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6347011ba23fcd0012cf2495/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Managing the consultants</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/633dd220b8bb2e00111ce943/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The image of management consultants has taken a pounding in recent years, giving the industry a reputation for unscrupulousness on par with investment bankers. And a recent difficulties and controversies at the three most prestigious firms - McKinsey, Bain and Boston Consulting Group (BCG), known collectively as MBB - hasn’t exactly helped the perception that they serve mostly to bamboozle CEOs while collecting fat fees. Can the industry be reformed?On this week’s episode, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Soumaya Keynes are joined by our global business correspondent Thomas Lee Devlin to find out more about the booming business for advice, and the problems that bedevilling the industrry. They also speak with New York Times journalists Michael Forsythe and Walt Bogdanich about their newly-published book, “When McKinsey Comes to Town”, looking at failures at the most prestigious consultancy, McKinsey - failures that McKinsey says misrepresent its business. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/633dd220b8bb2e00111ce943/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 19:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/633dd220b8bb2e00111ce943/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The rate shock</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63349b8a45963e00125a65ca/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The world’s financial markets are going through their most painful adjustment since the global financial crisis. Global stock markets have sold off sharply and bond markets are on course for their worst year since 1949. The British pound briefly fell to its lowest level ever against the dollar. And the Japanese government has intervened to prop up the value of the yen for the first time since 1998. What’s underlying this shift?On this week’s episode, hosts Alice Fulwood, Mike Bird and Soumaya Keynes are joined by our business affairs editor Patrick Foulis to parse the fallout from this month’s synchronous decision by the majority of the world’s central banks to raise interest rates. They’ll look at the idiosyncrasies of two outliers: Britain, where the government’s tax cuts are at odds with the Bank of England’s desire to reign in prices, and Japan, where the central bank recently decided to keep rates negative. Plus, Blue Bay Asset Management’s chief investment officer Mark Dowding explains why he’s decided to bet against sterling. And former Bank of Japan policy committee member Goushi Kataoka outlines why he thinks a weak yen could spell opportunity for Japan’s ailing economy.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63349b8a45963e00125a65ca/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 19:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63349b8a45963e00125a65ca/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Beyond seasonable doubt</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/632b42a913fe70001252183d/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Lawsuits aimed at green-house gas emissions are a growing trend, and better science is making them more precise. As ESG comes under attack, could these suits represent a different front in pressuring companies to act on climate change?On this week’s episode, hosts Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird speak with our environment editor Catherine Brahic about the rise in climate litigation aimed at holding companies responsible for climate change. Then, we head to Peru, to meet the farmer at the centre of a potentially seismic court case against Germany’s largest electricity firm. Finally, Sophie Marjanac of the environmental organisation ClientEarth explains why the law can be a useful way to outline the responsibilities of corporations when it comes to greenhouse gas emissions and who pays the costs of a warming planet.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/632b42a913fe70001252183d/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 16:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/632b42a913fe70001252183d/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money talks: India's moment</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6321fdcb1c230f0011e5a148/media.mp3</link>
			<description>India’s economy recently overtook Britain’s to be the world’s fifth largest, and it’s on track to be the fastest growing big economy this year. Part of what’s powering that growth is renewed domestic investment by the country’s big conglomerates. Could this be the year that India’s promise is realised?On this week’s episode, hosts Mike Bird, Soumaya Keynes and Alice Fulwood examine what’s powering India’s growth. First, Natarajan Chandrasekaran, the chairman of India’s biggest conglomerate, Tata Sons, explains why the company is investing $90bn domestically. Then, our global energy and climate innovation editor Vijay Vaitheeswaran heads to Pune, where he finds that India’s green energy transition is well underway. Finally, our Mumbai bureau chief Tom Easton takes a tour of Tamil Nadu, where he sees factories rapidly being built to help power India’s domestic manufacturing transition. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalksFor full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6321fdcb1c230f0011e5a148/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 16:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:50</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6321fdcb1c230f0011e5a148/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Running on empty</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6318c9c56179b90013499f65/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Europe is facing a catastrophic energy crisis. Prices for the natural gas needed to power many of its electricity plants have increased ten-fold since last summer. Most recently, Russia has choked off gas supplies to the Nord Stream 1 pipeline in retaliation against the G-7’s decision to put a cap on Russian oil prices. What needs to be done to keep homes warm this winter?On this week’s episode, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird investigate the options facing European governments as they scramble to tackle soaring consumer energy bills. First, our Europe economics editor Christian Odendahl explains the extent of the problem and the structural factors that underpin it. Then, the IMF’s Assistant Director for Europe Oya Celasun describes how direct cash support can protect the poor from surging energy prices. Finally, Scottish Power chief executive Keith Anderson outlines his plan for a state-supported price freeze and structural reform of the UK’s energy market.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6318c9c56179b90013499f65/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6318c9c56179b90013499f65/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Will the electric vehicle boom go bust?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/630f81d5c9d2ec00145491aa/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This month, California banned the sale of petrol cars by 2035. It could prompt a third of American states to embrace electric vehicles more quickly. But America is a laggard when it comes to the EV revolution. The European Parliament voted in June for a ban on sales of petrol and diesel cars by 2035. Japan and others are also aiming for a ban by 2035. But government efforts to encourage consumers to switch to buying electric cars could run into the reality that there isn’t yet enough capacity to manufacture the batteries necessary to power all those cars. On this week’s episode, hosts Alice Fulwood, Soumaya Keynes and Mike Bird look at whether the EV boom could go bust before it gets going. They’re joined by our industry editor Simon Wright who lays out the challenges battery manufacturers face in getting raw materials. Then, Peter Carlsson, the chief executive of European battery manufacturer Northvolt, outlines the challenges his firm faced in building a gigafactory in Sweden. Finally, Ford’s vice-president of sustainability Bob Holycross explains why the carmaker sees the switch to EVs as a refounding of the company.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/630f81d5c9d2ec00145491aa/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/630f81d5c9d2ec00145491aa/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Who is winning the sanctions war?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63064ff6ad5a26001418ed5c/media.mp3</link>
			<description>At the outset of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, the West united to impose unprecedented sanctions on Vladimir Putin’s regime. Six months on, a furious debate has erupted about the true state of Russia’s economy, which has so far defied the gloomiest predictions.. So is the West losing the sanctions war?On this week’s episode, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood are joined by senior economics writer Callum Williams to investigate why Russia’s economy is doing better than expected. Then Nicholas Mulder, assistant professor of history at Cornell University, explains how long it has taken for sanctions to have an impact in the past. Finally, deputy chief economist at the Institute for International Finance Elina Ribakova outlines what further measures the West could take.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63064ff6ad5a26001418ed5c/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/63064ff6ad5a26001418ed5c/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Land, locked</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62fd0a12bb11e5001354c973/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Mortgage boycotts that began in Jiangxi, China have spread to nearly 100 cities across the country, threatening over 320 real estate projects. They add more trouble to a property market that was already in turmoil and portend future pain in the world’s second largest economy.On this week’s episode, hosts Mike Bird, Soumaya Keynes and Alice Fulwood are joined by our China economics editor, Simon Cox, and our China business and finance editor, Don Weinland, to find what’s causing the crisis. First, University of California San Diego associate professor Victor Shih explains why the roots of this crisis go as far back as the early 1990s. Then, investor Andrew Left re-evaluates his report from 2012 in which he said the now-bankrupt Evergrande - once China’s second-largest property developer - was a fraud. The call got him banned from trading on Hong Kong’s stock exchange. And finally, they ask what this could mean politically for the Chinese government. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalksFor full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62fd0a12bb11e5001354c973/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 15:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62fd0a12bb11e5001354c973/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Fragile economies</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62f3c3c23e75ca0012fa2924/media.mp3</link>
			<description>From Sri Lanka to Pakistan, El Salvador to Ghana, Egypt to Tunisia, some emerging economies are feeling the pain of rising commodity prices, higher interest rates and a strong dollar. Is a wave of historic debt defaults coming for emerging markets?On this week’s episode, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird, and Alice Fulwood continue their exploration of the impact of the strong dollar. First, Kroll chief economist Megan Greene explains which countries she thinks are most vulnerable. Then, a look at what was behind the Latin American debt crisis of the 1980s, which led to an economic downturn more severe than the Great Depression. Finally, our trade and economics editor Ryan Avent says that many nations have learned lessons from past crises that could help them weather this difficult period.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62f3c3c23e75ca0012fa2924/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62f3c3c23e75ca0012fa2924/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Top dollar</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62eae2533e0cb50012711519/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This year, the dollar is up by 15% against the yen, 10% against the pound and 5% against the yuan. In July, it briefly hit parity against the Euro, something that last happened two decades ago. What’s behind the greenback’s rise?In this week’s show, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Soumaya Keynes examine what the dollar’s strength says about its role as the world’s dominant reserve currency. First, our US economics editor Simon Rabinovitch goes in search of lunch to determine if the dollar is overvalued. Then, Eurizon chief executive Stephen Jen tells us why the dollar is smiling. Finally Megan Greene, a senior fellow at Brown University and global chief economist for CRO, explains why efforts to replace the dollar as the world’s reserve currency have mostly failed.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62eae2533e0cb50012711519/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 21:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/62eae2533e0cb50012711519/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: How should crypto be regulated?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-howshouldcryptoberegulated-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The crypto winter has left many investors out in the cold. People have lost money as lending platforms have gone bust and complex stablecoin systems have unravelled. The push for better guardrails to be put in place has accelerated. But how do you protect consumers without stifling innovation?This week hosts Alice Fulwood, Mike Bird and Soumaya Keynes hear from Senator Cynthia Lummis, co-author of a bill that would split oversight of crypto in the US between existing agencies. They then speak to the head of one of those agencies, Rostin Behnam from the CFTC, about the role it can play. And our editor Kim Gittleson heads to an industry gathering in Paris, to find out how European crypto insiders are reacting to attempts to regulate them.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalksFor full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-howshouldcryptoberegulated-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 17:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-howshouldcryptoberegulated-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The backlash against ESG</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebacklashagainstesg/media.mp3</link>
			<description>One of the hottest areas of investing in recent years has been ESG: using environmental, social, and governance metrics as ways to assess potential investments. But the idea that you can make profits with purpose has recently come under pressure. Elon Musk has called ESG a scam; German police have just launched “greenwashing” raids; and insiders are spilling the beans. For something with hints of a moral crusade, ESG is in danger of turning into an unholy mess. On this week’s episode, hosts Alice Fulwood, Soumaya Keynes and Mike Bird investigate the problems plaguing ESG, and ask if the industry can survive. Blackrock’s former co-Chief Sustainability Officer Tariq Fancy explains why he decided the industry wasn’t fit for purpose. Lisa Woll, CEO of US SIF: The Forum for Sustainable and Responsible Investment, argues that the private sector has an important role to play alongside government policy. And Henry Tricks, the author of our special report on ESG, explains why he thinks the industry should focus solely on reducing emissions - and jettison the S and G. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebacklashagainstesg/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 15:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebacklashagainstesg/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Britain's growth crisis</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-britainsgrowthcrisis/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Britain’s Conservative party may be changing leadership, but it will take a lot more than that to change the country's gloomy economic situation. Prices are rising at their fastest pace in 40 years–at one of the highest rates in the West. The cost of servicing the country’s ballooning debt has increased. And a recession is looming. On this week’s episode, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird investigate just what’s behind Britain’s growth crisis. First, they ask our Britain editor Andrew Palmer how much of the current situation is down to Boris Johnson’s government’s economic policies and the OBR’s David Miles explains how much space the incoming government has to cut taxes. Then, Anna Valero of London School of Economics explains what’s behind Britain’s tepid growth: a productivity crisis. The Economist’s Joshua Roberts shows venture capital’s role. Finally, they ask just what can be done to get Britain’s economy back on track. Subscribe to our weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks and sign up to our new, six-week online course &quot;Fintech and the Future of Finance&quot; at economist.com/futureoffinance. Use discount code ‘moneytalks’ for a special offer. For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-britainsgrowthcrisis/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 17:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:42</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-britainsgrowthcrisis/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: TikTok’s ticking time bomb</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tiktok-stickingtimebomb/media.mp3</link>
			<description>It’s the fastest growing app in the world, filled with dance trends, cats misbehaving, and questionable financial advice. Teenagers love it; Western politicians are less convinced. Could TikTok’s popularity be its downfall? This week, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Soumaya Keynes investigate just who is afraid of TikTok’s growing influence. First, our media editor Tom Wainwright unpacks the relationship between TikTok, its parent company ByteDance, and its Chinese twin, Douyin. Then, AB Bernstein’s Robin Zhu outlines just how big a threat the app poses to the likes of Facebook, Snapchat, and YouTube. Plus, Federal Communications Commissioner Brendan Carr outlines his concerns about TikTok’s ability to harvest user data. And we ask: how long before this ticking geopolitical time-bomb blows up? Correction: An earlier version of this podcast said that the Chinese Communist Party recently took a 1% ownership stake in ByteDance. It was Chinese state-owned enterprises who recently took a 1% stake in a Chinese subsidiary of ByteDance. Apologies. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tiktok-stickingtimebomb/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 17:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tiktok-stickingtimebomb/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Crypto winter is here</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-cryptowinterishere/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In much of the northern hemisphere, it is summer. But in the world of crypto, winter has arrived. The price of bitcoin, which has been hovering around $20,000, is 70% below its peak of last year. In fact, the entire market capitalisation of the cryptoverse has shrunk by more than two-thirds since November 2021. Is this, as the crypto bulls say, a much needed correction? Or is this the beginning of a domino effect that could see the entire decentralised finance system unravel?This week, hosts Alice Fulwood, Mike Bird and Soumaya Keynes first look at why this crash is different from the many that have come before in the short life-span of cryptocurrencies. Then, they ask what weaknesses have been exposed in this downturn. Will this downturn finally see the end of the crypto hype and bust cycle?Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-cryptowinterishere/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 18:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-cryptowinterishere/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: House arrest</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-housearrest/media.mp3</link>
			<description>House prices across the rich world have dramatically increased since 2020. But that rapid rise could soon be coming to a sputtering halt, as central banks raise interest rates in an effort to rein in prices. Is another housing crash on the way?This week, hosts Alice Fulwood, Mike Bird and Soumaya Keynes investigate the potential fallout of rapidly rising mortgage rates. First, they speak with Dallas Federal Reserve senior research economist Enrique Martinez-Garcia, who argues that America is currently in a housing bubble. Then, our senior producer JohnJo Devlin takes a tour of one of the most exposed property markets in the world: Norway’s. Finally, our global property correspondent Vinjeru Mkandawire explains which other countries’ housing markets are most vulnerable to rising rates – and offers her opinion of the best place in the world to buy a house.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-housearrest/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-housearrest/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Supply chain reactions</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-supplychainreactions/media.mp3</link>
			<description>More than two years after the pandemic, supply chains are still snarled. Shipping times remain at record highs. Baby food, tampons, and semiconductors are all scarce. Companies are still struggling to answer a basic question: just when will all of this end? But one thing seems clear: after years of anxious speculation, the structure of the world’s supply chains have fundamentally changed.On this week’s Money Talks, hosts Soumaya Keynes, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood go on a journey to find out what’s still leading to delays and investigate the big shifts that will continue long after shelves are finally full. They’re joined by Audrey Ross, import and export compliance manager at Orchard Custom Beauty and Chris Rogers, principal supply chain economist at Flexport, who talk about the factors that are still gumming up delivery of goods. Then, Michael Wax, co-founder of Forto, explains why digitising the industry could help speed up shipping times. Finally, our US business editor Charlotte Howard unpacks what all of this will mean for supply chains in the future and why the old system might be finished.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-supplychainreactions/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 15:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-supplychainreactions/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The fight for financial supremacy in Asia</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefightforfinancialsupremacyinasia/media.mp3</link>
			<description>For decades, Hong Kong, Shanghai and Singapore have been the three heavyweight cities in Asian business and finance, with Hong Kong the undisputed champion. But as the city-state’s draconian security law and zero covid policy begin to bite, its rivals are going for the title.In this week’s Money Talks, hosts Mike Bird and Soumaya Keynes investigate whether Singapore or Shanghai could take the lead as Asia’s main financial centre. First, they ask Michael Mainelli of think-tank Z/Yen what makes a financial centre. Then, our China business and finance editor Don Weinland makes the case for Shanghai, James Crabtree of the International Institute for Strategic Studies gives the view from Singapore and our China correspondent Sue-Lin Wong argues we shouldn’t count out Hong Kong just yet.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefightforfinancialsupremacyinasia/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 16:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefightforfinancialsupremacyinasia/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The Alexander technique (update)</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique-update-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A hundred years ago, Sadie Alexander became the first African American to receive a PhD in economics and then spent a career fighting racial discrimination. This spring, the American Economic Association made her a distinguished fellow, their first ever posthumous award. We’ve decided to update this episode we first ran in December 2020 looking at her forgotten contributions to the field. Soumaya Keynes hosts.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalksPlease subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique-update-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique-update-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The next recession</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextrecession/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Since 1900, the global economy has fallen into a recession about once a decade on average. In 2020, the world experienced the deepest downturn since the second world war. Just two years on, is another recession on the way? This week, hosts Soumaya Keynes and Mike Bird focus on the economic slowdown in the world’s two biggest economies - in America and in China – and ask what could be done to prevent a full blown recession. They’re joined by our US economics editor Simon Rabinovitch in Washington, D.C., who asks former Treasury Secretary Larry Summers and Saint Louis Federal Reserve president James Bullard to weigh up the likelihood of a recession in America this year. Plus, London School of Economics associate professor Keyu Jin gives us the view from Beijing.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextrecession/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextrecession/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Worse than the average bear (market)</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-worsethantheaveragebear-market-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The beginning of 2022 has been particularly brutal for stock markets. The S&amp;P 500 had its worst April since 1970, the past seven weeks have marked the Dow Jones Industrial Average’s longest losing streak since 1980, and the tech-heavy Nasdaq has fallen 20% from its peak, putting it officially in bear market territory. This week, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Soumaya Keyes start small then zoom out. First, they look at what’s behind the crypto crash and hear from one unlucky investor who lost it all. Then, they speak with Rebecca Patterson, hedge fund Bridgewater’s chief investment strategist, who connects the dots between the crypto carnage and the rising power of retail investors. And finally, legendary bear market investor Jeremy Grantham explains why he thinks the stock market bubble hasn’t fully burst yet.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-worsethantheaveragebear-market-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 19:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-worsethantheaveragebear-market-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Out of gas</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-outofgas/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Russia’s trade surplus has continued to grow, even in the wake of Western sanctions. It’s now forecast to be double what it was last year. That’s prompted an acknowledgement among Western countries that more needs to be done to squeeze the country economically. Recently, the G7 announced plans to completely wean itself off of Russian oil; the European Union is trying to follow suit. But that still leaves a gigantic loophole: natural gas.In this week’s episode, host Mike Bird goes back to a key point in the 1970s to find out how Germany, Europe’s largest economy, became so reliant on Russian gas. Our European economics editor Christian Odendahl and our Berlin bureau chief Vendeline Von Bredow examine the geopolitical fallout from Germany’s misguided energy policy. And Georg Zachmann of the Bruegel Institute explains why liquified natural gas could potentially be part of the short-term solution.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-outofgas/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 19:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-outofgas/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Proxy wars</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-proxywars/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A record number of company shareholders have put forward resolutions at annual meetings this year, pressuring companies on everything from their environmental practices to political donations. Host Alice Fulwood asks our US business editor Charlotte Howard why the new frontline in corporate purpose has shifted to proxy battles. Plus, our US audio correspondent Stevie Hertz heads to Nebraska to find out more about a contentious resolution to unseat Warren Buffett from Berkshire Hathaway. And Thomas DiNapoli, the head of one of America’s largest pension funds, explains why the fund is supporting resolutions on everything from worker’s rights at Starbucks to racial equity at Amazon this year and weighs in on the spat between Disney and Florida Governor Ron DeSantis.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-proxywars/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:09</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-proxywars/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Breaking the bank? Part two</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-breakingthebank-parttwo/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Thirty years ago, rich-world central banks started winning the fight against inflation. More recently, they have begun to fight new battles, including against climate change or inequality. As the old enemy of inflation returns, in this two-part series, host Soumaya Keynes asks if central banks are fighting on too many fronts. In part two, Simon Rabinovitch, our US economics editor, asks former president of the New York Federal Reserve William Dudley and former economic advisor to President Barack Obama Jason Furman why the Fed failed to act on rising prices. Plus, our finance editor Rachana Shanbhogue and economics editor Henry Curr debate what can be done now and what lessons the Fed’s failure can hold for other central banks around the world.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-breakingthebank-parttwo/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 15:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-breakingthebank-parttwo/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Breaking the bank? Part one</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-breakingthebank-partone/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Thirty years ago, rich-world central banks started winning the fight against inflation. More recently, they have begun to fight new battles, including against climate change or inequality. As the old enemy of inflation returns, in this two-part series, host Soumaya Keynes asks if central banks are fighting on too many fronts. In part one, Rachana Shanbhogue, our finance editor and author of a new Special Report on central banks, explains why the remit of central banks has expanded. Plus, former Federal Reserve Governor Sarah Bloom Raskin gives us the inside story on her decision to withdraw her contentious nomination to run the central bank’s regulatory efforts, after pushback from Republican Senators over her views on climate change and monetary policy. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-breakingthebank-partone/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-breakingthebank-partone/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Clearing the rouble</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-clearingtherouble/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In the wake of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, western nations imposed historic sanctions meant to cripple Russia's economy. In the immediate aftermath, Russia’s currency, the rouble, plummeted. Yet over the past six weeks, something strange happened. Instead of continuing its downward trajectory, by some measures, the rouble instead became the world’s best performing currency in March. Our host Mike Bird investigates what the rouble’s supposed strength can tell us about the impact of economic sanctions on Russia.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks  For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-clearingtherouble/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 18:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-clearingtherouble/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: State of the unions</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-stateoftheunions/media.mp3</link>
			<description>We go inside two historic Amazon union votes in America. One, in Staten Island, New York, where our US audio correspondent Stevie Hertz follows the twists and turns of the first-ever successful vote to unionise a warehouse. The other was in Bessemer, Alabama. Our Mountain West correspondent Aryn Braun explains why a second run of last year’s failed vote looks set to end in defeat once again, but why the threat to Amazon’s business model persists. Then, our US business editor Charlotte Howard and senior economics writer Callum Williams ask if this is a watershed moment or a high water mark for workers’ power, given America’s tight labour market.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-stateoftheunions/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 17:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-stateoftheunions/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The new superpowers</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenewsuperpowers/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The transition to greener energy will shift the balance of power from oil and gas-producing countries to those with abundant deposits of materials needed for electricity grids, batteries and solar panels. Our Schumpeter columnist, Henry Tricks, and finance correspondent, Matthieu Favas, analyse who will be the winners and losers, the scale of investment needed to extract these minerals, and how history shows that sudden wealth from natural resources can be more of a curse than a blessing for the stability of nations.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenewsuperpowers/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 17:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenewsuperpowers/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: War of Interdependence</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-warofinterdependence/media.mp3</link>
			<description>What impact will the war in Ukraine have on the world economy and globalisation? Will it reshape the existing economic order built over decades? Host Rachana Shanbhogue asks Gita Gopinath, the First Deputy Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund. And how will geopolitics, further disruptions to supply chains and an upswing in covid cases affect China's economy? The Economist's China economics editor, Simon Cox, and China business and finance editor, Don Weinland, assess whether China's determination to follow a zero-covid policy will hamper its prospects.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-warofinterdependence/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 19:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-warofinterdependence/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Grain damage</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-graindamage/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Russia's invasion of Ukraine is creating one of the worst disruptions to the supply of wheat since the first world war. As prices spike, the damage from this shock will ripple right across the world⁠—affecting corn, vegetable oil, fertilisers and many other agricultural products. Can other countries fill the shortfall and who will be worst affected? Henry Tricks, our Schumpeter columnist, asks The Economist's Matthieu Favas and Charlotte Howard how serious a food crisis the world is facing.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-graindamage/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 18:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-graindamage/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Houston, we have a problem</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-houston-wehaveaproblem/media.mp3</link>
			<description>As America and Britain announced embargoes on Russian energy, our global energy and climate innovation editor Vijay Vaitheeswaran talked to oil and gas industry leaders in Houston where jaws dropped and prices soared. He asks Jose Fernandez, US undersecretary of state for economic growth, and Fatih Birol, head of the International Energy Agency, whether the West can afford to ban Russian oil. As governments scramble to plug the shortfall, we talk to Scott Sheffield, head of Pioneer Natural Resources, and Vicki Hollub, chief executive of Occidental Petroleum, about whether this could be American shale’s big moment. And Bob Dudley, former boss of BP who now heads the Oil and Gas Climate Initiative, argues the rush for energy security doesn't necessarily put the energy transition on hold. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-houston-wehaveaproblem/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-houston-wehaveaproblem/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Sanctioning behaviour</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-sanctioningbehaviour/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In response to Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, the West imposed unprecedented financial sanctions, effectively freezing the reserve assets of Russia. This triggered chaos in Russia's economy and prompted president Vladimir Putin to make nuclear threats, sending shock waves around the world. Will Russia weaponise energy and cut off its oil and gas supplies to the West? And, having crossed the Rubicon, the West has a new potent weapon—its use is being watched very carefully by China.The Economist’s global energy and climate innovation editor, Vijay Vaitheeswaran, hosts with senior editor Matthew Valencia, business affairs editor Patrick Foulis and Juan Zarate, American former deputy national security adviser and author of “Treasury’s War”.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-sanctioningbehaviour/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 18:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-sanctioningbehaviour/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Barbarians at the crossroads</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-barbariansatthecrossroads/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Low interest rates and barely-there regulation have made the past decade a golden age for private financial markets. Once a niche pursuit, the industry is supersizing and adopting myriad new strategies to profit from different types of assets—and attract new investors. As alternative assets enter the mainstream, The Economist’s Matthew Valencia and host Alice Fulwood ask how long the private-markets party can continue.With John Connaughton, head of private equity at Bain Capital; Anne Glover, chief executive of Amadeus Capital Partners and a member of Yale University’s investment committee; and Alisa Wood, head of private markets and real-asset strategies at KKR.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-barbariansatthecrossroads/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-barbariansatthecrossroads/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: How high?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-howhigh-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Persistently high inflation has brought back fears of a wage-price spiral. Our economics team Soumaya Keynes, Simon Rabinovitch and Callum Williams explore how expectations of high inflation become reality. We look at the data on whether workers or firms are winning the battle over wages. And, as they reach for all the tools at their disposal, are central banks still in control?With Julia Coronado, founder of MacroPolicy Perspectives; Ethan Harris, head of global economics at Bank of America; Dario Perkins, head of global macro at TS Lombard; and Ricardo Reis of the London School of Economics.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-howhigh-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 21:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-howhigh-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The next financial crisis</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextfinancialcrisis/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Over the past 15 years power and risk in financial markets have shifted radically. New investors have flooded in and, buoyed by pandemic stimulus, most have had an incredible ride. But as policymakers put the brakes on, global financial markets are starting to wobble. How might this new high-tech, bank-light system fare under a serious stress test?Mike Bird hosts with Alice Fulwood, The Economist’s US finance correspondent; Greg Jensen, co-chief investment officer of Bridgewater Associates; Robert Shiller, professor of economics at Yale University and author of “Narrative Economics”; and The Economist’s Buttonwood columnist, John O’Sullivan.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextfinancialcrisis/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextfinancialcrisis/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Caged tiger</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-cagedtiger/media.mp3</link>
			<description>As China celebrates the lunar new year and the winter Olympics open in Beijing, host Mike Bird and Simon Cox, our China economics editor, size up the looming threats to economic growth. Against the mounting costs of a zero-tolerance approach to the pandemic and a sharp slowdown in the property sector, can Xi Jinping deliver on his promise of “common prosperity” for all?With Don Weinland, The Economist’s China business and finance editor; Angela Zhang, director of the Centre for Chinese Law at Hong Kong University and author of “Chinese Antitrust Exceptionalism”; and Zhu Ning, a professor at the Shanghai Advanced Institute of Finance and author of “China’s Guaranteed Bubble”.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-cagedtiger/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 20:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-cagedtiger/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The energy weapon</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theenergyweapon/media.mp3</link>
			<description>What happens if Vladimir Putin invades Ukraine again, the West hits Russia with sanctions, and Mr Putin retaliates by shutting down supply of Russian gas? The Economist’s global energy &amp; climate innovation editor Vijay Vaitheeswaran explores how this would rock energy markets from American shale oil to Chinese imports of LNG. What are the lessons from the last time Russia turned off the taps and how could Europe, already facing record prices, wean itself off its dependency?With Thane Gustafson, professor of energy policy at Georgetown University and author of “Klimat: Russia in the Age of Climate Change”; Amy Myers Jaffe, director of the climate policy lab at Tufts University and author of “Energy’s Digital Future”; and Daniel Yergin, vice president of IHS Markit and author of “The New Map: Energy, Climate, and the Clash of Nations”.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theenergyweapon/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 20:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theenergyweapon/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Moonshooters</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-moonshooters/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This week Microsoft announced its biggest ever deal, spending $69bn on games publisher Activision Blizzard to advance its ambitions in gaming and the metaverse. The world’s most powerful tech companies are racing to splash their cash on frontier technologies. We crunch the numbers on where they are investing their billions and ask whether these new corporate moonshots will supercharge productivity or further entrench the giants’ dominance in the future.Rachana Shanbhogue hosts, with Kevin Scott, chief technology officer of Microsoft, and Margrethe Vestager, competition commissioner for the European Union. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-moonshooters/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 19:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:58</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-moonshooters/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The bossy state</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebossystate/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Governments around the world are deciding it is time to bring big business to heel. Host Rachana Shanbhogue and The Economist’s business editor Jan Piotrowski explore the new age of state interventionism. A suite of old tools is being dusted off and reimagined—from a return to picking winners to turning the century-old global tax system on its head. The big state is back in business.With Oren Cass, director of American Compass; Sarah Miller, founder of the American Economic Liberties Project; Christiane Arndt-Bascle, head of regulatory performance at the OECD; and Professor Michael Devereux, director of the Centre for Business Taxes at Oxford University.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebossystate/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 19:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebossystate/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Rags to riches</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-ragstoriches/media.mp3</link>
			<description>How did second-hand clothes become fashion’s hottest buy? Online resale and rental firms are changing the calculus on what it means to buy fashion “as an investment”. Host Alice Fulwood speaks to entrepreneurs and economists to find out how technology is creating new markets and why consumers are saying out with the new and in with the old.With Eshita Kabra-Davies, founder of By Rotation; Francesca Muston, vice president of fashion at forecaster WGSN; James Reinhart, founder of thredUP; Professor Alvin Roth, economist at Stanford University and Julie Wainwright, founder of The RealReal.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-ragstoriches/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-ragstoriches/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: 2021 unwrapped</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-2021unwrapped/media.mp3</link>
			<description>From Ever Given to Evergrande, via empty crisp packets and the metaverse, host Henry Tricks leads a brave band of The Economist’s finest through the tribulations and triumphs of the past year in business, finance and economics. The team unpack the data that made their jaws drop, face baffling clues to mystery items and offer their predictions—and hopes—for 2022. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-2021unwrapped/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 16:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-2021unwrapped/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Meet the cryptokings</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-meetthecryptokings/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Four men hold the keys to a $2trn market. Our finance correspondent Matthieu Favas speaks to some of the most powerful people in the world of cryptocurrencies—the founders of the most important crypto exchanges—to find out what it takes to stay on top in the most volatile market of all. We examine their strategies against a looming reckoning with regulators and ask whether their visions for how crypto will change the world could become reality. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts. With Brian Armstrong of Coinbase, Sam Bankman-Fried of FTX and Changpeng Zhao of Binance.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-meetthecryptokings/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 19:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-meetthecryptokings/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The not-so-great resignation</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenot-so-greatresignation/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The idea that the pandemic has prompted people to quit their jobs en masse fills corporate earnings calls, headlines and social media. But do the data hold up? Host Patrick Lane investigates what is really going on in the labour market. Will the Biden administration usher in a new age for America’s formidable unions? And we visit a would-be paradise for digital nomads. We would love to hear from you—please take a moment to complete our listener survey at economist.com/moneytalkssurvey Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenot-so-greatresignation/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenot-so-greatresignation/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Omicronomics</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-omicronomics/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China’s economy is slowing while America’s overheats, prompting Jerome Powell to suggest this week that the Fed could act faster than planned. As the Omicron variant triggers a fresh wave of travel restrictions, is the world economy caught between a rock and a hard place? Host Patrick Lane and Henry Curr, our economics editor, assess the threats to global growth.With Carmen Reinhart, senior vice-president and chief economist of the World Bank group, and Wang Tao, chief China economist and head of Asia research for UBS, an investment bank.We would love to hear from you—please take a moment to complete our listener survey at economist.com/moneytalkssurvey Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-omicronomics/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 18:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-omicronomics/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Veni, vidi, VC</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-veni-vidi-vc/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Venture capital is no longer embodied by Silicon Valley investing in its own backyard. A new wave of both capital and competition is powering new ideas across sectors and around the world. Our correspondent Arjun Ramani and host Rachana Shanbhogue speak to veteran VCs, newcomers and founders to find out whether the innovation being funded will be worth the risks.With Roelof Botha, partner at Sequoia Capital; Rana Yared, general partner at Balderton; Ali Partovi, chief executive of Neo; Dr Maria Chatzou Dunford, founder of Lifebit.ai and Rachel Delacour, co-founder of Sweep.We would love to hear from you—please take a moment to complete our listener survey at economist.com/moneytalkssurvey Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-veni-vidi-vc/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 19:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-veni-vidi-vc/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Inflated expectations</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-inflatedexpectations/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Until recently worrying about rising prices seemed like a relic of the 1970s. Now it borders on a global obsession. As new data on inflation from around the world exceed expectations, host Rachana Shanbhogue asks whether central bankers will be able to curb the trend. Plus, we crunch the numbers in our alternative inflation “Uluru” index.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-inflatedexpectations/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 19:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-inflatedexpectations/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: It’s not just Evergrande</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-it-snotjustevergrande/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The debt-ridden Chinese property giant continues to teeter on the verge of collapse. But the rot in China’s financial system goes much deeper—and could pose a global risk. As COP26 in Glasgow nears a close, we explore the drawbacks of the debate over “degrowth” for tackling climate change. And the property website Zillow’s house-flipping flop reveals the limits of big data in real estate. Henry Tricks hostsSign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-it-snotjustevergrande/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-it-snotjustevergrande/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Yield curveball</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-yieldcurveball/media.mp3</link>
			<description>With the prospects for inflation clouded in uncertainty, central banks are in a new staring contest with the bond market. Who will blink first? Also, host Henry Tricks explores how the private sector is influencing what might be the most corporate COP ever. And economist Claudia Goldin tracks five generations of American women to work out why the gender pay gap persists—and how to conquer it.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-yieldcurveball/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 18:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:42</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-yieldcurveball/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Is the future non-fungible?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-isthefuturenon-fungible-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This week The Economist auctioned off an Alice in Wonderland-inspired NFT for charity. Host Rachana Shanbhogue finds out how the sale went and explores the promise and pitfalls of this dizzying new market. Plus, the financial landscape in Africa is changing fast: we ask why the unicorn population has more than doubled this year and speak to Sim Tshabalala, head of the continent’s largest lender, Standard Group Bank. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-isthefuturenon-fungible-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-isthefuturenon-fungible-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: In a tightening spot</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-inatighteningspot/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Higher inflation looks likely to last into 2022. The Bank of England could be the first big central bank to raise interest rates—why might it make the first move? Also, our team explores how real-time data are upending economics. And Michael Dell, boss of the eponymous tech firm, on why founders are leaving Silicon Valley for Texas and why PCs are still sexy. Rachana Shanbhogue hostsSign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-inatighteningspot/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 19:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-inatighteningspot/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: A real-world revolution</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-areal-worldrevolution/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This year's Nobel prize celebrates the &quot;credibility revolution&quot; that has transformed economics since the 1990s. Today most notable new work is not theoretical but based on analysis of real-world data. Host Rachana Shanbhogue speaks to two of the winners, David Card and Joshua Angrist, and our Free Exchange columnist Ryan Avent explains how their work has brought economics closer to real life.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-areal-worldrevolution/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 18:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-areal-worldrevolution/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The new logic of trade</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenewlogicoftrade/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Trade used to be about efficiency and growth. But those goals are being overtaken by others, from security to environmentalism. Our Britain economics editor Soumaya Keynes and host Rachana Shanbhogue investigate how the blurring of economic and political concerns is driving—and destabilising—trade relationships, with global consequences.We hear from Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala, director-general of the World Trade Organisation, about the WTO’s complicated history and contested future. US Trade Representative Katherine Tai explains where she thinks the current rules-based system falls short, particularly when it comes to China. And Pamela Coke-Hamilton, head of the International Trade Centre, identifies the winners and losers of this new era.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenewlogicoftrade/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 17:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenewlogicoftrade/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Bricks and mortar</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-bricksandmortar/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China’s largest developer Evergrande is threatening to default—what does this reveal about the broader troubles in the country’s property market? And if you live in a big American or European city, there’s a good chance that a mighty financial institution could be your next landlord. Plus, historian Adam Tooze looks back at the economic impact of the pandemic. Patrick Lane hosts.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-bricksandmortar/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 17:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:25</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-bricksandmortar/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Volatile gas</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-volatilegas/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The price of natural gas is rocketing, with global consequences. Is volatility in this crucial fuel here to stay? We also ask why an investigation at the World Bank has put Kristalina Georgieva, the head of the International Monetary Fund, in the spotlight. And, after our adventures in DeFi-land last week, economist Eswar Prasad assesses who should control the future of money and payments. Patrick Lane hostsSign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-volatilegas/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 18:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-volatilegas/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Alice in DeFi-land</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aliceindefi-land/media.mp3</link>
			<description>After a painstakingly slow start, the financial system is now digitising fast. Alice Fulwood, The Economist’s US finance correspondent, and host Rachana Shanbhogue explore the different emerging models shaping the future of money and payments. With David Marcus, head of Facebook Financial and Novi, its new digital wallet system; Benoît Cœuré, head of innovation at the Bank for International Settlements, a club of central banks (recorded at the 2021 Eurofi forum) and Lex Sokolin, head of decentralised finance at ConsenSys, a blockchain software firm.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aliceindefi-land/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 19:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aliceindefi-land/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Opening gambit at Intel</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-openinggambitatintel/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The notoriously insular American chipmaker wants to throw open the doors. Succeed or fail, this reversal will shake up a $600bn industry at the heart of the global economy. Plus, Harvard economist Edward Glaeser explains how the pandemic is transforming the world’s cities. And, as high streets and malls open, can the direct-to-consumer boom last? Patrick Lane hosts.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-openinggambitatintel/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-openinggambitatintel/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Delta means change</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-deltameanschange/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The Delta variant has altered the direction of the pandemic and the threats the world economy faces—economic policy must adapt. Also, what can America's ‘gilded age’ reveal about China's future? And, the world’s strictest limits on video games could be a ‘critical hit’ to the industry. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-deltameanschange/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 16:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-deltameanschange/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The fight over the Fed</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefightoverthefed/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The Federal Reserve under Jerome Powell has taken an extraordinarily bold gamble. But will the central bank chairman still be in office to see if it pays off? Plus why construction firms cannot build fast enough to keep up with the rich world’s housing boom. And the race for territory as, one by one, American states legalise betting on sports.Rachana Shanbhogue hosts. Featuring Peter Jackson, CEO of Flutter Entertainment.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefightoverthefed/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 16:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefightoverthefed/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The brass is greener</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebrassisgreener/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Hundreds of billions of dollars are pouring into the business of decarbonisation. Can this green boom flourish where the last one wilted? Plus, why the branchless neobanks finally conquering America face new challenges beyond the pandemic. And the cybersecurity industry is thriving—but do those shelling out for protection get what they pay for? The Economist’s finance editor Rachana Shanbhogue hosts, with Ciaran Martin, former head of the National Cyber Security Centre.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebrassisgreener/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 17:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thebrassisgreener/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: What tech does China want?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-whattechdoeschinawant-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The contours of Xi Jinping’s grand plan for the Chinese technology industry are emerging. But with so much damage done to the country’s star firms, host Henry Tricks asks what is driving the crackdown. Can the Communist Party pull off an ambitious overhaul of the data economy without crippling it? And what could the West learn from watching the fallout?With Don Weinland, The Economist’s China business and finance correspondent; Simon Cox, our China economics editor; Kendra Schaefer, head of tech at Trivium China; and Dr Keyu Jin of the London School of Economics.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-whattechdoeschinawant-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-whattechdoeschinawant-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Playing catch-up</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-playingcatch-up/media.mp3</link>
			<description>At the start of the 21st century, developing economies were a source of unbounded optimism and fierce ambition. But the pandemic has revealed a very different picture: many poor and middle-income countries seem to be losing the knack of catching up with rich ones. Is the golden age of emerging markets over? And how can countries now battered by the pandemic get back on that path to rapid growth?Rachana Shanbhogue hosts with Jim O’Neill, former chief economist at Goldman Sachs who 20 years ago coined the term “BRICs”; Makhtar Diop, head of the International Finance Corporation; our trade and international economics editor, Ryan Avent; China economics editor, Simon Cox, and Africa correspondent, Kinley Salmon.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-playingcatch-up/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 17:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-playingcatch-up/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Robinhood and the merry mob</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-robinhoodandthemerrymob/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The trading app brought retail investing to the public—now it is going public via its retail investors. Our Wall Street correspondent reports from inside its unusual IPO. Plus, as food prices soar, big agriculture is having a bumper year. How long can it last? And lessons from the history books for a new age of central banking. Patrick Lane hosts Subscribers to The Economist can join John O’Sullivan, Buttonwood columnist, and Alice Fulwood, Wall Street correspondent, on July 29th for a live event unpicking the inner workings of financial markets and how to make sense of them. Register and submit your questions at economist.com/marketseventFor full access to print, digital and audio editions as well as exclusive live events, subscribe to The Economist at economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-robinhoodandthemerrymob/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-robinhoodandthemerrymob/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Uncertainty principles</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-uncertaintyprinciples/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Financial markets are rattled by fears about the rapidly spreading Delta variant of covid-19. But another threat also looms: can the economic recovery survive the end of emergency stimulus? Plus, why America’s shale-oil tycoons are now fracking as little as possible. And, our correspondent meets bitcoin miners in rural China to find out why they are packing up and shipping out. Simon Long hosts Subscribers to The Economist can join our finance reporters John O’Sullivan, Buttonwood columnist, and Alice Fulwood, Wall Street correspondent, on July 29th for a live event unpicking the inner workings of financial markets and how to make sense of them. Register and submit your questions at economist.com/marketseventFor full access to print, digital and audio editions as well as exclusive live events, subscribe to The Economist at economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-uncertaintyprinciples/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 17:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-uncertaintyprinciples/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: China Inc stays global</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-chinaincstaysglobal/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Can a new generation of Chinese multinational companies learn to adapt and even thrive in a hostile environment at home and abroad? Also, how Europe’s latest green plan aims to plug the leaks in the world’s biggest carbon market. And, why online shopping is about to become a whole lot more chatty. Simon Long hostsSign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-chinaincstaysglobal/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 18:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-chinaincstaysglobal/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Tapering without the tantrum</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-taperingwithoutthetantrum/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The economic recovery is outpacing expectations—but so is inflation. Can central banks wind back their support without sending markets into freefall? And, the Olympics used to be a bonanza for corporate sponsors, but this years’ games are turning into a reputational minefield. Rachana Shanbhogue hostsSign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-taperingwithoutthetantrum/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-taperingwithoutthetantrum/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Lives v livelihoods</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-livesvlivelihoods/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Lockdowns have become a default tool for governments trying to control covid-19. But are the benefits worth the costs? The return to the office is proving much more difficult than last year’s abrupt exodus. And as he prepares to move to a new beat, our China economics editor reflects on a decade of spectacular growth—and what lies ahead. Rachana Shanbhogue hostsSign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-livesvlivelihoods/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-livesvlivelihoods/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The Empire of Son</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theempireofson/media.mp3</link>
			<description>How has the world's biggest technology investor Softbank ridden the wave of the pandemic?And, the surging threat of cyber-heists—the methods and menace of the new bank robbers. Also, survival of the fittest in economic theory.Simon Long hosts For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theempireofson/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 17:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theempireofson/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Ride shares</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-rideshares/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The company that owns China’s leading ride-sharing app is expected to float on the stockmarket in New York next month, in what could be the biggest IPO in the world this year. We examine its ambitions and its plans to beat the competition. And, what about the inflation in the room? Host Patrick Lane asks how American businesses are coping with a spring surge of prices. Also, we talk to the CEO of Twitch, a streaming service that made watching people play video games big business. For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-rideshares/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 10:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-rideshares/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Green bottlenecks</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-greenbottlenecks/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The clean-energy business is thriving. Theories of decarbonisation are finally being put into practice. But how can the green boom avoid getting bogged down? Plus, the new geopolitics of business: American and Chinese big companies dominate. How did Europe become an also-ran and can it recover its footing? And, why the ghost storefronts of Fifth Avenue could stay empty. Rachana Shanbhogue hostsFor full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-greenbottlenecks/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 17:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-greenbottlenecks/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Reweaving America’s safety-net</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-reweavingamerica-ssafety-net/media.mp3</link>
			<description>President Joe Biden wants to Europeanise the American welfare state. How will the biggest social-policy experiment since the 1960s work—and who will pay for it? Also, the work from home revolution promises a financial reckoning for commercial property. And, as LGBT+ Pride month begins, how can companies avoid “rainbow-washing”? Host Simon Long explores the pitfalls of woke advertising.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-reweavingamerica-ssafety-net/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 16:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-reweavingamerica-ssafety-net/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: A tale of two Europes</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-ataleoftwoeuropes/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The French are back in cafes and Italians can stay out past 10pm—relief at reopening is widespread but European economic recovery risks being starkly unequal. Plus, Arnold Donald, CEO of Carnival, the world’s biggest cruise company, shares lessons from a year in the doldrums as ships prepare to set sail again. And, are cryptocurrencies a financial world unto themselves? Patrick Lane hosts.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-ataleoftwoeuropes/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 17:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-ataleoftwoeuropes/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Where have all the workers gone?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-wherehavealltheworkersgone-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Businesses are struggling to fill vacancies at the same time as millions of people are out of work. Host Patrick Lane investigates this conundrum. Also, each year almost 10% of global tax revenue is lost through companies shifting their income to tax havens. How can governments get the world’s most profitable companies to cough up? And, Patrick Collison, co-founder and CEO of Stripe, on the rise of America’s biggest ever unlisted firm.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-wherehavealltheworkersgone-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 17:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-wherehavealltheworkersgone-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Does the world still need banks?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-doestheworldstillneedbanks-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Technological change is upending finance as the clout of payment platforms and tech firms grows and central banks begin to issue their own digital currencies. But can you imagine a world without banks? Rachana Shanbhogue explores the future of banking with Alice Fulwood, The Economist’s Wall Street correspondent, Jamie Dimon, CEO of JPMorgan Chase, Patrick Collison, cofounder and CEO of Stripe, Kahina van Dyke, head of digital and data at Standard Chartered, and Jean-Pierre Landau, former deputy-governor of the Banque de France.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-doestheworldstillneedbanks-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 18:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-doestheworldstillneedbanks-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Berkshire after Buffett</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-berkshireafterbuffett/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Now that the world’s most celebrated investor has named a successor, the conglomerate he created must face some hard truths. Also, as companies wrestle with thorny issues from climate change to voting rights, economist Dambisa Moyo argues corporate boards need a makeover. And, the pandemic has coaxed millions of older people online—now companies are racing to keep up with the silver surfers. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-berkshireafterbuffett/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 16:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:25</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-berkshireafterbuffett/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The QE quandary</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theqequandary/media.mp3</link>
			<description>As economies recover, central bankers will need to decide what to do with their asset-purchase schemes and their enormous balance-sheets. We look at how quantitative easing was pioneered in Japan 20 years ago and why it is still a black box. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theqequandary/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 17:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theqequandary/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Less stick more carrot</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lessstickmorecarrot/media.mp3</link>
			<description>As America and its allies threaten more penalties against Russia over the treatment of opposition leader Alexei Navalny, does the West’s overdependence on economic sanctions risk making them ineffective? Also, why India is proving an attractive—and clever—investor in poor countries concerned about Chinese influence. And, do plans for a football Super League risk an own goal? Patrick Lane hosts A note for our listeners: from May 5th 2021 Money Talks will be published every Wednesday.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lessstickmorecarrot/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 18:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lessstickmorecarrot/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Politics in the boardroom</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-politicsintheboardroom/media.mp3</link>
			<description>From voting rights to climate change, companies are under pressure to speak out—is it wise to mix business and politics? Also, China’s state control over tech giants like Ant Group is growing. Trillions of dollars in market value are at stake. And, as crypto-marketplace Coinbase prepares to list and bitcoin’s value surges, we take a look at the currency’s hidden costs. Rachana Shanbhogue hostsFor full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-politicsintheboardroom/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 18:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-politicsintheboardroom/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The future of work</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefutureofwork/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The pandemic has fuelled an explosion of unemployment and a transformation in how many people work, especially in richer countries. We consider the many reasons for optimism about the labour market and the prospects for working from home. And, we talk to David Autor, a labour economist at MIT, about the effect of covid-19 on automation. Simon Long hosts For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefutureofwork/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 17:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thefutureofwork/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The next generation</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextgeneration/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The EU’s €750bn recovery fund aims to rejuvenate the old continent, but ten months in it faces legal challenges and is yet to pay out a cent. Sustainable investing has been accused of “greenwashing”: we crunch the numbers to find out the real impact. And, ahead of Deliveroo’s IPO, our correspondents take to two wheels to investigate the economics of food delivery. Patrick Lane hosts.With Paolo Gentiloni, European commissioner for economy and former prime minister of Italy, and Tariq Fancy, former chief investment officer for sustainable investing at BlackRock.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextgeneration/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 18:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thenextgeneration/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Over the great wall</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-overthegreatwall/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Against the backdrop of sanctions and retaliations, China's capital markets are increasingly interwoven with global finance—what will this mean for foreign investors? Plus, will President Joe Biden’s fiscal stimulus trigger a dreaded return to high inflation—with global consequences? And, a new generation of workers' unions takes on the tech giants. Simon Long hosts.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-overthegreatwall/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 19:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-overthegreatwall/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The retail revolution</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theretailrevolution/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The shopping industry is in a state of flux. Smartphones and social media are enabling a data-driven transformation that is only just getting started. Host Henry Tricks investigates whether the future of shopping will be ruled by giants and how personal data will increasingly shape not just what gets bought, and where, but even what gets made. Could a new generation of consumers change capitalism for the better?With David Liu, vice president of strategy at Pinduoduo, Harley Finkelstein, president of Shopify, Nilam Ganenthiran, president of Instacart, and Katie Hunt, cofounder of Showfields.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theretailrevolution/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 18:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theretailrevolution/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: SPAC to the future</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/spactothefuture/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Special-purpose acquisition companies are Wall Street’s latest craze, attracting everyone from celebrities to retail investors. An alternative to the traditional IPO, SPACs could transform tech investing and supercharge innovation. They are even shaping the post-Brexit battle to be Europe’s financial capital. But are these “blank-cheque firms” a mania, a useful innovation, or both? Simon Long hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/spactothefuture/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 20:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:50</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/spactothefuture/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Bonds, shaken and stirred</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-bonds-shakenandstirred/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Last week’s turmoil in the bond market has calmed for now, but fears of inflation mean more turbulence ahead. Plus, how poor countries trying to secure debt relief are caught in a minefield of lenders’ competing priorities and egos. And, host Simon Long takes a lesson from a former hostage negotiator in the secrets of successful listening.For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-bonds-shakenandstirred/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 17:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-bonds-shakenandstirred/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Pricing pollution</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-pricingpollution/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Could the success of the world’s biggest carbon market provide a model for the world? Plus, Cristina Junqueira, cofounder of Nubank, a Brazilian digital bank, on how the pandemic is supercharging the fintech revolution. And, why sports cards’ leap from the schoolyard to the stock exchange reveals the growing financial power of social networks. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-pricingpollution/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 19:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-pricingpollution/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Return of the wheelie-bag</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-returnofthewheelie-bag/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Globetrotting had never been easier—then the pandemic brought it to a standstill. The Economist’s industry editor Simon Wright investigates how mass travel has changed the world and what it will take to get people moving again. Could this shock to the system be an opportunity to make the future of tourism greener, safer and more enjoyable?With Michael O’Leary, CEO of Ryanair, James Liang, chairman of CTrip and Trip.com, Gloria Guevara, president of the World Travel and Tourism Council, and Brian Pearce, chief economist of the International Air Transport Association.Subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-returnofthewheelie-bag/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:11:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-returnofthewheelie-bag/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Return of the wheelie-bag</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-returnofthewheelie-bag/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Globetrotting had never been easier—then the pandemic brought it to a standstill. The Economist’s industry editor Simon Wright investigates how mass travel has changed the world and what it will take to get people moving again. Could this shock to the system be an opportunity to make the future of tourism greener, safer and more enjoyable?With Michael O’Leary, CEO of Ryanair, James Liang, chairman of CTrip and Trip.com, Gloria Guevara, president of the World Travel and Tourism Council, and Brian Pearce, chief economist of the International Air Transport Association.Subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-returnofthewheelie-bag/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 19:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-returnofthewheelie-bag/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Twin peaks</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-twinpeaks/media.mp3</link>
			<description>As the price of oil rises, so too does the value of the battery metals that could replace it. Host Patrick Lane asks what’s driving these competing bets on the fuels of the future. Plus, the rise of the hairy zombies: why some of the most pandemic-battered shares in USA Inc are confident of an afterlife. And, how remote work is playing havoc with American taxes. Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-twinpeaks/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-twinpeaks/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: UnStoppable</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-unstoppable/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The GameStop saga continues—does it reveal a cheat code to how to beat the stockmarket, or is it a sign of a deeper transformation at work in the financial system? Plus, property is the biggest asset market in the world and nowhere bigger than in China. Host Simon Long asks how long China’s property boom can hold. And, our Buttonwood columnist shares some hard truths about investing in bricks and mortar. Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-unstoppable/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 19:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-unstoppable/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The chips are down</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thechipsaredown/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The vast semiconductor industry is booming but faces new stresses that recently stalled production lines worldwide and could threaten the stability of the global economy. President Biden’s “Buy American” executive order aims to create jobs and boost resilience—but will Americans actually benefit? And, economist Mariana Mazzucato makes the case for a modern “moonshot”. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thechipsaredown/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 19:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thechipsaredown/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden, it’s time</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-biden-it-stime/media.mp3</link>
			<description>What will the new president’s plans mean for the American economy—and for its partners and rivals around the world? Sabine Weyand, of the European Commission’s department for international trade, explains how the EU hopes to rebalance the global trading order in the post-Trump era. And host Simon Long asks why, despite a return to growth, the Communist Party is busy reining in China Inc.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-biden-it-stime/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:08:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-biden-it-stime/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Biden, it’s time</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-biden-it-stime/media.mp3</link>
			<description>What will the new president’s plans mean for the American economy—and for its partners and rivals around the world? Sabine Weyand, of the European Commission’s department for international trade, explains how the EU hopes to rebalance the global trading order in the post-Trump era. And host Simon Long asks why, despite a return to growth, the Communist Party is busy reining in China Inc.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-biden-it-stime/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 17:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-biden-it-stime/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Testing their metals</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-testingtheirmetals/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Despite the economic catastrophe of the pandemic, prices of goods such as copper, iron ore and soya beans are surging; just how far can commodities climb? Also, how the Brexit trade agreement will reshape business on both sides of the Channel. And, the economic cost of covid-19 is impossible to calculate—but host Patrick Lane has a go anyway.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-testingtheirmetals/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 18:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-testingtheirmetals/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Companies' responsibility in closing the skills gap</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Having tripled in value in the past quarter, the cryptocurrency continues its rollercoaster ride, as the financial establishment begins to jump aboard. Also, why a new EU-China investment deal fails to balance competition, cooperation and confrontation. And, what can companies do to bridge the gap between the workforce of today and the jobs of tomorrow? Rachana Shanbhogue hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:07:15</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New EU-China investment deal fails to balance competition</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Having tripled in value in the past quarter, the cryptocurrency continues its rollercoaster ride, as the financial establishment begins to jump aboard. Also, why a new EU-China investment deal fails to balance competition, cooperation and confrontation. And, what can companies do to bridge the gap between the workforce of today and the jobs of tomorrow? Rachana Shanbhogue hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:08:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Once bitcoin, thrice as high</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Having tripled in value in the past quarter, the cryptocurrency continues its rollercoaster ride, as the financial establishment begins to jump aboard. Also, why a new EU-China investment deal fails to balance competition, cooperation and confrontation. And, what can companies do to bridge the gap between the workforce of today and the jobs of tomorrow? Rachana Shanbhogue hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:06:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Once bitcoin, thrice as high</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Having tripled in value in the past quarter, the cryptocurrency continues its rollercoaster ride, as the financial establishment begins to jump aboard. Also, why a new EU-China investment deal fails to balance competition, cooperation and confrontation. And, what can companies do to bridge the gap between the workforce of today and the jobs of tomorrow? Rachana Shanbhogue hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 18:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-oncebitcoin-thriceashigh/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Forgotten Heroine of Economics: The Alexander technique</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A hundred years ago, Sadie Alexander became the first African American to receive a PhD in economics and then spent a career fighting racial discrimination. In this episode, The Economist’s trade and globalisation editor Soumaya Keynes speaks to Nina Banks of Bucknell University about rediscovering Alexander's economics and why her insights are still relevant today.  Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 19:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The Alexander technique</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A hundred years ago, Sadie Alexander became the first African American to receive a PhD in economics and then spent a career fighting racial discrimination. In this episode, The Economist’s trade and globalisation editor Soumaya Keynes speaks to Nina Banks of Bucknell University about rediscovering Alexander's economics and why her insights are still relevant today.  Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 16:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thealexandertechnique/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The year that was</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/merrytalks-theyearthatwas/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Tins of tuna and bedroom slippers, triple-digit growth and IPO implosion—what could it all mean? Host Henry Tricks leads an international band of “Money Talks” regulars on a whistlestop tour through a year like no other. The team choose their stories of the year, face baffling clues to mystery items, and share their predictions—and their hopes—for 2021.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/merrytalks-theyearthatwas/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 18:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:16:11</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/merrytalks-theyearthatwas/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Merry Talks: The year that was</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/merrytalks-theyearthatwas/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Tins of tuna and bedroom slippers, triple-digit growth and IPO implosion—what could it all mean? Host Henry Tricks leads an international band of “Money Talks” regulars on a whistlestop tour through a year like no other. The team choose their stories of the year, face baffling clues to mystery items, and share their predictions—and their hopes—for 2021.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/merrytalks-theyearthatwas/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 16:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/merrytalks-theyearthatwas/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The madness of crowds</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-themadnessofcrowds/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A volatile world begets volatile financial markets. Does this explain investor enthusiasm for tech stocks and IPOs—or is something else afoot? Also, Michael O’Leary, the boss of Europe’s largest airline Ryanair, reads the skies ahead. And, the little-known history of working from home: even in the 18th and 19th centuries it had its advantages. Patrick Lane hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-themadnessofcrowds/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 19:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:58</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-themadnessofcrowds/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Will inflation bounce back?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-willinflationbounceback-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Worrying about inflation has gone out of style. But a small band of economists and investors argue the pandemic could usher in a new era of rising prices. Also, how one of the world’s biggest pension funds is navigating this and other pandemic-related risks. And, the remarkable resilience of America’s chain restaurants. Simon Long hostsPlease subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-willinflationbounceback-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 18:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-willinflationbounceback-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Joe’s dream team</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-joe-sdreamteam/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Mr Biden’s latest nominations for his economic team send a clear message about his gameplan. Plus, deal season returns. Salesforce is eyeing up Slack—united, could the pair take on Microsoft? And, the publishing giant building a behemoth of books. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-joe-sdreamteam/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-joe-sdreamteam/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Joe’s dream team</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-joe-sdreamteam/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Mr Biden’s latest nominations for his economic team send a clear message about his gameplan. Plus, deal season returns. Salesforce will buy Slack—united, could the pair take on Microsoft? And, the publishing giant building a behemoth of books. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-joe-sdreamteam/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 19:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-joe-sdreamteam/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The money doctors</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-themoneydoctors/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A quiet revolution is happening in asset management. Host Patrick Lane and John O’Sullivan, The Economist’s markets columnist, speak to industry insiders about a centuries-old model under strain. They ask about the cost of the race to zero fees, if value investing has had its day and whether the quest for higher returns will lead to China.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-themoneydoctors/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 18:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-themoneydoctors/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>China is in, America and India are out</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lukewarmrception/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China is in, America and India are out; is the world’s biggest trade agreement a triumph for rules-based trade or a step towards a new world order? Donald Trump’s last nominations to the Federal Reserve could help secure his legacy—and limit Mr Biden’s ability to fix the country’s economic problems. And, the candy-pink Swedish unicorn hoping to work its magic in America. Patrick Lane hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lukewarmrception/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 19:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:06:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lukewarmrception/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Lukewarm RCEPtion</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lukewarmrception/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China is in, America and India are out; is the world’s biggest trade agreement a triumph for rules-based trade or a step towards a new world order? Donald Trump’s last nominations to the Federal Reserve could help secure his legacy—and limit Mr Biden’s ability to fix the country’s economic problems. And, the candy-pink Swedish unicorn hoping to work its magic in America. Patrick Lane hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lukewarmrception/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-lukewarmrception/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The inheritance of Joe</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theinheritanceofjoe/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Coaxing the American economy back to health will be an unenviable challenge for the 46th president. From taxes to tariffs, we assess the task. And, as Ant agonises, what does the fate of the world’s biggest suspended IPO reveal about the future of private enterprise in China? Simon Long hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theinheritanceofjoe/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 17:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theinheritanceofjoe/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Buried in treasuries</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-buriedintreasuries/media.mp3</link>
			<description>On election day in the United States, host Patrick Lane looks at perhaps the world’s most important asset market: American government bonds. As it grows, this supposed safe haven is malfunctioning. If Joe Biden wins the presidency, his choice of treasury secretary will reveal much about his priorities—we size up the frontrunners. And, how to count the cost of partisanship to America Inc.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-buriedintreasuries/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 18:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-buriedintreasuries/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The great divergence</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thegreatdivergence/media.mp3</link>
			<description>As the covid-19 pandemic continues, disparities in the prospects of economies, industries and businesses are increasing. Host Rachana Shanbhogue and Henry Curr, our economics editor, investigate how the pandemic will recast the global economic order. They talk to Gita Gopinath, chief economist at the IMF, to identify who risks being left behind. And as the pandemic upends labour markets, will governments resist change or embrace the new reality?Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thegreatdivergence/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-thegreatdivergence/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Xinomics</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-xinomics/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A new economic era is dawning in China—a potent mix of autocracy, technology and dynamism. Our Asia economics editor Simon Rabinovitch and host Simon Long speak to local business owners and economists about this evolution of state capitalism. Could a new sort of central planning help Chinese technology dominate the world stage? And how should the West respond?Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-xinomics/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 18:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-xinomics/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The prize is right</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theprizeisright/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This year’s Nobel prize rewards two economists who reimagined an ancient form of transaction—the auction. Host Rachana Shanbhogue asks one of the winners, Paul Milgrom, how he put his cutting-edge theory into practice. Plus, the $100bn bet that has not paid off: why SoftBank’s Vision Fund failed to supercharge tech start-ups. And, how are investors hedging against the risk of post-election volatility in America?Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theprizeisright/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 17:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:09:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theprizeisright/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The prize is right</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theprizeisright/media.mp3</link>
			<description>This year’s Nobel prize rewards two economists who reimagined an ancient form of transaction—the auction. Host Rachana Shanbhogue asks one of the winners, Paul Milgrom, how he put his cutting-edge theory into practice. Plus, the $100bn bet that has not paid off: why SoftBank’s Vision Fund failed to supercharge tech start-ups. And, how are investors hedging against the risk of post-election volatility in America?Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theprizeisright/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 18:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theprizeisright/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>GiAnt of finance</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-giantoffinance-acastab748e13/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Ant Group, the world’s biggest fintech platform, is preparing for a record-busting IPO. Is it a glimpse of the future of finance? Suzanne Clark, president of the US Chamber of Commerce, tells us how she thinks the elections will reshape America Inc. And, another Bond-film cliffhanger: can cinemas survive until the latest one shows up? Simon Long hostsPlease subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-giantoffinance-acastab748e13/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 16:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:09:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-giantoffinance-acastab748e13/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: GiAnt of finance</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-giantoffinance-acastab748e13/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Ant Group, the world’s biggest fintech platform, is preparing for a record-busting IPO. Is it a glimpse of the future of finance? Suzanne Clark, president of the US Chamber of Commerce, tells us how she thinks the elections will reshape America Inc. And, another Bond-film cliffhanger: can cinemas survive until the latest one shows up? Simon Long hostsPlease subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-giantoffinance-acastab748e13/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 17:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-giantoffinance-acastab748e13/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A plague but not on houses</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aplaguebutnotonhouses/media.mp3</link>
			<description>What is driving the global boom in house prices during the pandemic? Also, American fintech firms have long distanced themselves from traditional banking—so why are some now angling to become banks themselves? And, reflections on the life of Donald Kendall, the legendary PepsiCo boss who sparked the most epic battle in American marketing. Simon Long hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aplaguebutnotonhouses/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 16:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:07:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aplaguebutnotonhouses/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: A plague, but not on houses</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aplaguebutnotonhouses/media.mp3</link>
			<description>What is driving the global boom in house prices during the pandemic? Also, American fintech firms have long distanced themselves from traditional banking—so why are some now angling to become banks themselves? And, reflections on the life of Donald Kendall, the legendary PepsiCo boss who sparked the most epic battle in American marketing. Simon Long hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aplaguebutnotonhouses/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 19:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aplaguebutnotonhouses/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Power in the 21st century</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-powerinthe21stcentury/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Oil fuelled the 20th century, but now a huge energy shock is catalysing a shift to a new world order. Charlotte Howard, The Economist's energy and commodities editor, and host Rachana Shanbhogue investigate why this oil slump is different. They ask Spencer Dale, BP's chief economist, whether the world has passed peak oil. Daniel Yergin, author of “The New Map” and “The Prize”, explains how cleaner energy will reshape geopolitics. And Kevin Tu, of Beijing Normal University, on China's new role as a global powerhouse of electrification.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-powerinthe21stcentury/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-powerinthe21stcentury/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Power in the 21st century</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-powerinthe21stcentury/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Oil fuelled the 20th century, but now a huge energy shock is catalysing a shift to a new world order. Charlotte Howard, The Economist's energy and commodities editor, and host Rachana Shanbhogue investigate why this oil slump is different. They ask Spencer Dale, BP's chief economist, whether the world has passed peak oil. Daniel Yergin, author of “The New Map” and “The Prize”, explains how cleaner energy will reshape geopolitics. And Kevin Tu, of Beijing Normal University, on China's new role as a global powerhouse of electrification.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-powerinthe21stcentury/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-powerinthe21stcentury/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: No Huawei</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-nohuawei/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Britain has announced plans to ban Huawei from its 5G networks over security concerns, following pressure from America. How will this change the way Chinese tech firms operate in the West? The row is one sign relations between America and China are going from bad to worse; what does that mean for their trade agreement? And, is a slow bull emerging in China's stockmarkets? Simon Long hostsPlease subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-nohuawei/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-nohuawei/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: TikTok goes the clock</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tiktokgoestheclock-acastdbf757a2/media.mp3</link>
			<description>TikTok, a video-sharing app, is caught up in the US-China clash. Can the firm restructure itself to address concerns over privacy and security? Also, why the pandemic has meant some households are awash with cash. And, a question of judgment. Patrick Lane hosts  Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tiktokgoestheclock-acastdbf757a2/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:58</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tiktokgoestheclock-acastdbf757a2/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The age of free money</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theageoffreemoney/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In response to the covid-19 pandemic governments have pumped huge amounts of cash into economies and the role of central banks is changing dramatically. Host Rachana Shanbhogue asks Henry Curr, The Economist's economics editor, whether this heralds a new era of macroeconomics. Economists Ken Rogoff and Claudia Sahm look at what else policymakers can do—should interest rates go negative? And, banking in the shadows.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions: www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theageoffreemoney/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theageoffreemoney/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Yearnings season</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-yearningsseason/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The global pandemic has hit American companies hard, reflected in the latest earnings season, and it could be many quarters before a return to profitability. In Europe, Germany is used to being an economic powerhouse, but the virus has left it in a slump. And, could central banks ditch cash in favour of virtual money? Simon Long hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-yearningsseason/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-yearningsseason/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Tik for Tok</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tikfortok/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Relations between America and China are at a fresh low. What do Donald Trump’s latest threats mean for Chinese businesses? Also, the coronavirus has had a disastrous effect on Saudi Aramco’s earnings. How can the state-controlled oil company weather the extreme conditions? And, the bumps ahead for America’s $800bn trucking industry. Rachana Shanbhogue hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tikfortok/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tikfortok/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Party like it’s 1999</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-partylikeit-s1999/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Tech companies are lining up to go public, while America’s stockmarkets fly high. What explains the exuberance on Wall Street and in Silicon Valley in the middle of a deep recession? How long will the fun last? And, Jim McKelvey, the founder of payments company Square on how innovation can thrive in economic chaos. Rachana Shanbhogue hostsPlease subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-partylikeit-s1999/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-partylikeit-s1999/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Blockbust-up</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-blockbust-up/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China is poised to become the world’s biggest box office. Is this an opportunity for Hollywood or could it be a show-stopper? As the dollar hovers around its weakest level in two years, we ask how it became so central to the world economy and whether this spells the beginning of the end for dollar dominance. And economist Sir Paul Collier argues that individualism is holding back society. Patrick Lane hosts Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-blockbust-up/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-blockbust-up/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The shape of recovery</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theshapeofrecovery/media.mp3</link>
			<description>While big tech and Wall Street are breaking records, main-street businesses are struggling to survive; governments and central banks must decide whether they can afford to dig deeper to help. Six months into the pandemic, host Rachana Shanbhogue asks Patrick Foulis, The Economist's business affairs editor, Wall Street correspondent Alice Fulwood and Vijay Vaitheeswaran, US business editor, is it time for repeat prescriptions or a new economic diagnosis?Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theshapeofrecovery/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-theshapeofrecovery/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Double bubble, is tech in trouble?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-doublebubble-istechintrouble-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The rise and rise of American stockmarkets has faltered; what is behind the selloff in tech shares? Netflix has had a blockbuster year but faces rising costs and stiff competition. Its co-founder Reed Hastings argues the American streaming giant still has plenty of room to grow. And, what is wrong with the concept of “net zero” carbon emissions? Patrick Lane hosts.Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-doublebubble-istechintrouble-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:11</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-doublebubble-istechintrouble-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Can Oracle see TikTok’s future?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-canoracleseetiktok-sfuture-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>After Microsoft's takeover bid was rejected, a new deal with Oracle, a big software company, could allow the Chinese-owned social-video app to continue operating in America without a sale. The wolf, the diamonds and the foreign minister: why the biggest luxury-goods deal in history, LVMH’s purchase of Tiffany, has been put on ice. And covid-19 is putting capitalism to the test—which market models come out on top? Rachana Shanbhogue hosts. Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-canoracleseetiktok-sfuture-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 11:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-canoracleseetiktok-sfuture-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Why house prices are so stubbornly high</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/646646aa5f8b2200116e73c1/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Housing in America has never been this unaffordable. The pandemic set off skyrocketing prices; then the Fed began to rapidly increase interest rates, pushing up borrowing costs. Many predicted this might result in a crash. But after dropping 10% from all-time highs, home prices in America are picking up again. What is going on?On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird ask if anything can take the heat out of the American housing market. Skylar Olsen, chief economist at property app Zillow, tells them that interest rate rises have added $800 a month to the typical American household’s mortgage bill. And Domonic Purviance from the Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta explains how central bankers are thinking about the impact on the affordability of those loans.We would love to hear from you. Please fill out our listener survey at economist.com/moneytalkssurveySign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/646646aa5f8b2200116e73c1/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/646646aa5f8b2200116e73c1/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Another way, another dollar?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/646fa5f3c2fe9e0011117334/media.mp3</link>
			<description>From Alipay’s QR codes to PayPal, it’s never been easier to move money around. Central banks are even considering their own digital currencies. And all that cross-border cashlessness has some wondering about the dollar’s international dominance.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird and Tom Lee-Devlin examine the risks to the world’s reserve currency. The Economist’s Arjun Ramani explains how far digital payments have come; Mairead McGuinness, European Commissioner for financial services, discusses ambitions for a digital euro; and Michael Pettis from Peking University explains the costs inherent in hosting a reserve currency.We would love to hear from you. Please fill out our listener survey at economist.com/moneytalkssurveySign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/646fa5f3c2fe9e0011117334/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/646fa5f3c2fe9e0011117334/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The great debt hangover</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6478bb866542600011932a3f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Decades of cheap money has left businesses in America and Europe addicted to debt. Some companies have been borrowing cash just to dole it out to shareholders. But with interest rates now reaching levels not seen in 15 years, those debt-drunk firms are waking up to the threat of a mighty hangover.On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin and Alice Fulwood ask if those firms can kick their debt habit. Goldman Sachs’ chief credit strategist, Lotfi Karoui, explains how companies became hooked in the first place—and what will happen when they start cutting back. And Torsten Slok from Apollo, one of the world’s largest private capital managers, tells them why the cost of borrowing isn’t likely to fall any time soon.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6478bb866542600011932a3f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6478bb866542600011932a3f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The trillion-dollar question</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6482198bd9a829001193e571/media.mp3</link>
			<description>For over three decades, the people most excited about Nvidia’s chips have been gamers. They used its graphics cards to render games in super-high definition. But over the last 15 years Nvidia has slowly established itself as the go-to provider of chips and software to the booming artificial intelligence space. Now it is investors that are paying attention—Nvidia’s market cap has almost tripled this year, briefly soaring above $1trn in late May. On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird explore the astonishing rise of Nvidia. The Economist’s Guy Scriven explains how the AI boom made the Californian chip maker into a $1trn company. Stacy Rasgon, an analyst at Bernstein Research, charts the company’s “30-year journey to overnight success” and Pierre Ferragu from New Street Research tells them that Google and Amazon have their sights on the chip market.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6482198bd9a829001193e571/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6482198bd9a829001193e571/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The baby bust blues</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/648b403f889ad000110ab94a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In more than half of the world's countries, the number of babies being born has fallen below the replacement rate. For the next generation, that means living in a less-populous country than their parents—and that gives birth to some big problems. Not only will the bill for their ageing parents’ care be shared between fewer people, but there will be a smaller pool of potential entrepreneurs and innovators to create jobs and come up with big ideas for society. On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Tom Lee-Devlin ask whether shifting demographics are pushing the world towards the mother of all economic slumps. Matthias Doepke, a professor at London School of Economics, warns there is no quick fix. Demographics expert James Liang, explains how a shrinking population stifles innovation.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/648b403f889ad000110ab94a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/648b403f889ad000110ab94a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: What happens if inflation sticks?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/649d96fb204c4c00108f99a9/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Over the past two years, inflation has been full of surprises. Central bankers are now facing up to the very real possibility that bringing sticky inflation down to their 2% targets could bring deep economic pain. Some analysts are starting to ask whether they might be tempted to tolerate higher inflation instead. On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird ask what would happen if ballooning price rises aren’t brought back down to target. The Economist’s Josh Roberts tells them why higher inflation may be here to stay. And Ed Cole, from asset manager Man Group, and Andrew Balls, from PIMCO, explain what would happen in equities and bond markets if it does. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/649d96fb204c4c00108f99a9/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/649d96fb204c4c00108f99a9/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Averting the city death spiral</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64946fb218e50d00111e4a8a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Cities across the world are in the midst of an identity crisis. With fewer workers commuting into offices and more shoppers heading online, what are they now for? It’s a question that commercial real estate investors are scrambling to find an answer to.On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood explore an office block that’s been repurposed to find out what the future holds for cities. Nick Bloom, a professor of economics at Stanford who’s been researching home working for more than two decades, tells them fully remote work can dent productivity by 10%. And Ed Glaeser, chair of the economics department at Harvard and one of the world’s leading experts on urban economics, says that troubled cities like San Francisco need to focus on making their downtown areas safe.We would love to hear from you. Please fill out our updated listener survey at economist.com/podcastsurveySign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64946fb218e50d00111e4a8a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 15:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64946fb218e50d00111e4a8a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Will green flying take off?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64a6f58241e02c0011f938a4/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=NN_QjkGbqLTYz_FzGsIB3PCJoXIjtNB9wrMFU_FE-nM</link>
			<description>The aviation industry is responsible for more than 2% of annual carbon emissions. That figure is set to rise as more passengers take to the skies. But the sector has set itself an ambitious target: to hit net-zero emissions by 2050. On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin and Alice Fulwood ask if airlines can really go green. Tom discovers the limits of battery-powered flight when a trip in one of the world’s first electric planes ends in an emergency landing. Andreea Moyes, from Air BP, explains why sustainable aviation fuel—and not batteries—will help solve the industry’s carbon problem. And Jim Harris, from consultancy Bain, argues that the days of cheap flying may be behind us.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64a6f58241e02c0011f938a4/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=NN_QjkGbqLTYz_FzGsIB3PCJoXIjtNB9wrMFU_FE-nM</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64a6f58241e02c0011f938a4/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=NN_QjkGbqLTYz_FzGsIB3PCJoXIjtNB9wrMFU_FE-nM" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The Jamie Dimon interview</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64b02f195df0030012b29259/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=pqr3UXDtEPZs2kFxUeR8VlmYucbg2cke6nIBp0w-Ogc</link>
			<description>Jamie Dimon runs America’s biggest and most successful bank: JP Morgan Chase. That makes him the boss of 300,000 people across more than 60 countries. He’s the only CEO of a major bank to have been in his role since before the financial crisis. But there is a question about what he does next—Mr Dimon’s enthusiasm to talk policy has led to speculation that his next act could be political.On this week’s podcast, Mr Dimon speaks to The Economist’s editor-in-chief Zanny Minton Beddoes about recession, China and what he does next.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64b02f195df0030012b29259/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=pqr3UXDtEPZs2kFxUeR8VlmYucbg2cke6nIBp0w-Ogc</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:37</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64b02f195df0030012b29259/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=pqr3UXDtEPZs2kFxUeR8VlmYucbg2cke6nIBp0w-Ogc" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: How to build a sports business</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64b9726a8fa9bb0010902d00/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=98ovYJJUH8CCAuFNA_6k0t7IIy5eczfRcK16bxTf6Qo</link>
			<description>Newspaper sports pages have - in recent years - often read more like business sections with reports of mergers, acquisitions and well-funded startups trying to steal market share. But those deals tend to be structured with the interests of team bosses and players in mind, rather than the fans. That got the “Money Talks” team wondering: where does the balance lie between commercial imperatives in sport and fan support? On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood draft in The Economist’s resident sports geek Arjun Ramani to examine what makes a good sports business. The deputy commissioner of the National Basketball Association, Mark Tatum, tells them how to structure a league to keep fans engaged. And Chatri Sityodtong, the founder of martial arts league ONE Championship, explains how to make money from those fans. But Bobby Sharma, the founder of Bluestone Equity Partners, says the rules of the game are changing as younger fans turn to streaming services rather than cable. Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64b9726a8fa9bb0010902d00/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=98ovYJJUH8CCAuFNA_6k0t7IIy5eczfRcK16bxTf6Qo</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64b9726a8fa9bb0010902d00/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=98ovYJJUH8CCAuFNA_6k0t7IIy5eczfRcK16bxTf6Qo" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Lights! Camera! Inaction…</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64c29b8a0e1a7c0011398a12/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=zzKoKI40pgjfeUxljlK20k1cXEI6ZjvMX_LqCBVg5GA</link>
			<description>The only action taking place in Hollywood is on the picket lines. Thousands of writers and actors have taken to the streets to protest the way that technology has affected their wages. At the top of their list of demands is a change to the way they are compensated when shows air on streaming services, like Netflix. But filmmakers' use of artificial intelligence is also in the spotlight as concerns mount about how companies might use actors’ likenesses. On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood and Mike Bird examine how tech is transforming Tinsel Town. The Economist’s Aryn Braun hears from actors on the picket line. Analyst Michael Pachter explains why Netflix may benefit from giving actors a big pay rise. And Tom Graham, the boss of effects firm Metaphysic, says AI could deliver Hollywood-quality fan fiction movies.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64c29b8a0e1a7c0011398a12/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=zzKoKI40pgjfeUxljlK20k1cXEI6ZjvMX_LqCBVg5GA</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64c29b8a0e1a7c0011398a12/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=zzKoKI40pgjfeUxljlK20k1cXEI6ZjvMX_LqCBVg5GA" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Lessons from the great macro experiment</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64cbe82d085d260011d8d601/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=APMGnyQso9Ysq1ukryObP7fWbDYhrgE2vDKEEAhNJOI</link>
			<description>American economists are scratching their heads in confusion. The Fed’s aggressive rate hikes hasn’t produced the outcome many expected. Instead of recession and massive layoffs, the US economy now looks tantalisingly close to a fabled “soft landing” with the jobs market remaining resilient, and inflation tumbling. The unique set of circumstances of the post-pandemic US economy have perplexed almost everyone. The Fed's latest rate rise could now be the last for a while. What can this rate hike cycle teach us about interest rates and the US economy?On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood, and Tom Lee-Devlin examine how interest rates and policy transmission have functioned in the post-covid US. The Economist’s US Economics Editor Simon Rabinovitch explains why economists across the board have had their expectations confounded. Founder of Macropolicy Perspectives Julia Coronado lays out the key lessons from this unusual rate hike cycle. And former Fed governor Frederic Mishkin tells us why he thinks recession is still a likelihood for the US economy.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64cbe82d085d260011d8d601/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=APMGnyQso9Ysq1ukryObP7fWbDYhrgE2vDKEEAhNJOI</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:42</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64cbe82d085d260011d8d601/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=APMGnyQso9Ysq1ukryObP7fWbDYhrgE2vDKEEAhNJOI" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Click and collect a grocery victory</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64d5215d3298c80011af7c14/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=o9VP6m2Xkf8z1e6d6Z0PoQehIZ91PQEAUymuwZQr_Ao</link>
			<description>Grocery shopping is a giant prize–accounting for around $800bn of spending a year in America. But it is also a notoriously tough business, with price-sensitive customers keeping a tight lid on margins. Add in online delivery and it often becomes unprofitable. Convincing customers to buy more of their groceries online is the holy grail for a digital-native company like Amazon, which is a newcomer to the business. But Amazon’s “technology first” approach hasn’t been enough to win over the market, or the customers who still see the value of shopping in-store. This leaves grocery stalwarts like Walmart with an opportunity–to expand online, while utilising their foothold in brick-and-mortar stores. With margins so tight, yet the lure of convenience strong, what is the future for online grocery shopping?On this week’s podcast, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Alice Fulwood, and Mike Bird examine how the grocery business is adapting to the digital age. Bill Aull, leader in the North America Retail and Consumer Practice at Mckinsey, explains how online grocery shopping has struggled to make a mark in the US. And author Jason Del Rey lays out what the battle between Amazon and Walmart tells us about the future direction of the industry.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64d5215d3298c80011af7c14/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=o9VP6m2Xkf8z1e6d6Z0PoQehIZ91PQEAUymuwZQr_Ao</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 17:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64d5215d3298c80011af7c14/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=o9VP6m2Xkf8z1e6d6Z0PoQehIZ91PQEAUymuwZQr_Ao" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Is America’s China policy working?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64de45264189310011603b18/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=AgmtetM5Jplf-DRP0U_6sqPXZ_o304-1kzSX7DMAFpY</link>
			<description>When is economic decoupling not economic decoupling? When it drives your allies to tighter commercial links with your adversary. That’s the situation the US finds itself in today, when it comes to its policies directed against China. Since the Trump administration put tariffs on Chinese imports in 2018, the US has been trying to extricate itself from commercial ties with the world's second-largest economy. President Biden has expanded the policy to keep China locked out of US supply chains in a few key high-tech industries. On the outside it looks like decoupling or de-risking is actually working. Business operations are relocating to other southeast Asian countries, India, and Mexico. But in crucial ways, the process is only skin deep. Take a closer look and the exodus from China is actually driving closer integration between the Chinese economy, and those of America’s friends. On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Tom Lee-Devlin and Alice Fulwood, examine whether US policy towards China is really working. Caroline Freund, Dean of the UC San Diego School of Global Policy and Strategy, explains how the countries that are expanding their exports to the US are at the same time becoming more integrated in supply chains with China. And Chris Miller, Associate Professor of international history at Tufts University and author of “Chip War: The Fight for the World’s Most Critical Technology” describes how reshoring, and lengthening supply chains is going to come at considerable cost.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64de45264189310011603b18/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=AgmtetM5Jplf-DRP0U_6sqPXZ_o304-1kzSX7DMAFpY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 16:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64de45264189310011603b18/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=AgmtetM5Jplf-DRP0U_6sqPXZ_o304-1kzSX7DMAFpY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Counting the cost of education</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64e7848f4a6f410011efcf74/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=1Y6mTLqfBYzGZtw40QwYPaVu4mpKFaUwmNfDiIvhlSw</link>
			<description>Is a college degree worth it? That question hangs over millions of would-be students, as they prepare to apply to university. It is one that many graduates might be mulling over as they have to start paying off their college debts once more. America’s pandemic-era moratorium on student debt payments comes to an end in September. On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird examine whether college is still worth the time and the money. Constantine Yannelis from the Chicago Booth School of Business explains how the US economy will be impacted when up to 45 million Americans are confronted with their student debt payments once more. And Michael Itzkowitz, who was appointed to the US Department of Education by former President Obama, reveals how often students fail to earn a return on their investment in education.   Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks. For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64e7848f4a6f410011efcf74/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=1Y6mTLqfBYzGZtw40QwYPaVu4mpKFaUwmNfDiIvhlSw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 16:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:15</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64e7848f4a6f410011efcf74/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=1Y6mTLqfBYzGZtw40QwYPaVu4mpKFaUwmNfDiIvhlSw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Information used to want to be free</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64f0bec9a3958200117fb4c0/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=SI21dVUP3JWBd_-UVl4E7nQE4I7aX1Con4Xvns_1KtM</link>
			<description>The mantra from the mid-2000s that “data is the new oil” is taking on a new sheen: tapping and refining it into personalised advertisements has become harder, thanks to increasing regulation and the self-serving policies of the tech behemoths. Meanwhile artificial intelligence is a data-guzzler, eschewing the pointedly personal in favour of the revealing aggregate. Both trends raise thorny questions about ownership of the precious underlying resource.On this week’s show, hosts Tom Lee-Devlin, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood examine how data are gathered and traded, and Kenn Cukier, a deputy executive editor at The Economist, describe the changes in online tracking that altered those paths. Sir Martin Sorrell, chairman of S4 Capital, a digital-advertising firm, describes how his industry is shifting. And Dennis Cinelli, chief financial officer of Scale AI, a data startup, surveys the land-grab of data among artificial-intelligence firms.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64f0bec9a3958200117fb4c0/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=SI21dVUP3JWBd_-UVl4E7nQE4I7aX1Con4Xvns_1KtM</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 16:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64f0bec9a3958200117fb4c0/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=SI21dVUP3JWBd_-UVl4E7nQE4I7aX1Con4Xvns_1KtM" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Why does everyone want to manage your wealth?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64f9fdaf464608001168f022/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ANv7jogI8hbDWDCNNe7HxV7mqfbyvEJfr4TK4YRESxA</link>
			<description>Wealth managers occupy a unique place in their clients’ lives. Not only do they advise on picking assets and tax-efficient investment strategies—they often find out about illicit affairs and which heirs might be a problem child. These services were once the preserve of those worth $10m or more but new technology means they are accessible to people with as little as $100,000 in the bank. And now banks are fighting to be the ones to advise the moderately wealthy. On this week’s podcast, hosts Alice Fulwood, Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird ask why wealth managers want to do business with the not-so-wealthy. Helen Watson, who’s head of UK wealth management at Rothschild &amp; Co, shares the secrets of managing other people’s fortunes. And Markus Habbel, a consultant at Bain, explains why 250m people might soon be in need of a wealth manager.Sign up for our new weekly newsletter dissecting the big themes in markets, business and the economy at www.economist.com/moneytalks For full access to print, digital and audio editions, subscribe to The Economist at www.economist.com/podcastoffer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64f9fdaf464608001168f022/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ANv7jogI8hbDWDCNNe7HxV7mqfbyvEJfr4TK4YRESxA</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/64f9fdaf464608001168f022/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ANv7jogI8hbDWDCNNe7HxV7mqfbyvEJfr4TK4YRESxA" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: China’s property crisis</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/65032f1005106400125e9058/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jbup6WNgD2VvGetbaLfXTrCp4mYQkT2E-6mSPtvUIiY</link>
			<description>Thousands of building projects across China have been halted or dramatically slowed as a rolling crisis engulfs the country’s property sector. The government’s “three red lines” policy sought to limit the leverage of property developers, but has now forced scores of them into default and restructuring. Confidence in the market has evaporated. And in a country where people buy their homes in advance, long before they are built, that wave of worry has sent sales tumbling.On this week’s podcast, hosts Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood, and Tom Lee-Devlin ask whether there is an end in sight to China’s growing property woes. The Economist’s Don Weinland takes a trip to Zhangzhou to examine what went wrong. Long-time China-watcher Anne Stevenson-Yang explains why real estate looms so large over China’s economy and Beijing-based property analyst Rosealea Yao explains what it would take to bring the crisis to an end.Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our limited time offer: www.economist.com/podcastsplus-moneytalksYou will not be charged until Economist Podcasts+ launches.If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you’ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.For more information about Economist Podcasts+, including how to get access, please visit our FAQs page. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/65032f1005106400125e9058/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jbup6WNgD2VvGetbaLfXTrCp4mYQkT2E-6mSPtvUIiY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 16:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/65032f1005106400125e9058/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jbup6WNgD2VvGetbaLfXTrCp4mYQkT2E-6mSPtvUIiY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The price of cheaper medicines</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/650c745e05dd320011cfe988/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MIel5NUIbzD8vDNwgNjkN5fIdxotO066ehzEgJZS7SE</link>
			<description>Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our limited time offer*One of the many aims of President Joe Biden’s signature legislation, the Inflation Reduction Act, is to cut the cost of drugs prescribed by Medicare, a government health insurance programme for Americans 65 and over. But the policy could have some side-effects for patients far beyond the US.Hosts: Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird. Contributors: Shailesh Chitnis, The Economist’s global business correspondent; Tricia Neuman, a senior advisor to Mr Biden; and David Fredrickson of AstraZeneca.*You will not be charged until Economist Podcasts+ launches. If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you’ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription. For more information about Economist Podcasts+, including how to get access, please visit our FAQs page. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/650c745e05dd320011cfe988/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MIel5NUIbzD8vDNwgNjkN5fIdxotO066ehzEgJZS7SE</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 16:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/650c745e05dd320011cfe988/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MIel5NUIbzD8vDNwgNjkN5fIdxotO066ehzEgJZS7SE" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Is America becoming uninsurable?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6515a2c52843410011550b40/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=EI855G7mCBNMCplVVc_rPfbM_J0VAYgjOohIu0oeJAw</link>
			<description>Insurers make their money betting against disasters. They wager that the premiums paid by policyholders will outstrip the losses caused by fires, floods and other catastrophes. But in parts of the US that winning formula is no longer working–and climate change is only worsening the odds for insurers. Hosts: Mike Bird and Tom Lee-Devlin. Contributors: Aryn Braun, The Economist’s US West Coast Correspondent; Karen Clark, founder of risk modelling firm KCC; and Jean-Paul Conoscente, CEO of Property and Casualty at Scor.Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our limited time offer. You will not be charged until Economist Podcasts+ launches.If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you’ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.For more information about Economist Podcasts+, including how to get access, please visit our FAQs page. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6515a2c52843410011550b40/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=EI855G7mCBNMCplVVc_rPfbM_J0VAYgjOohIu0oeJAw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:25</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6515a2c52843410011550b40/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=EI855G7mCBNMCplVVc_rPfbM_J0VAYgjOohIu0oeJAw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Why is customer service getting worse?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/651ed6f7e6253800116670e9/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ROwlAN4057K_ZDjniEPzewIgzxSxsWljzhghNSTNWeA</link>
			<description>Trouble is brewing in the world of customer service. After rising steadily for nearly two decades, customer contentment, as measured by the American Customer Satisfaction Index (ACSI), began plummeting around five years ago. But if it pays to keep customers happy, why are businesses getting worse at it?Hosts: Tom Lee-Devlin and Mike Bird. Guests: Darci Darnell, a senior partner at Bain; and Claes Fornell, architect of the ACSI.Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our limited time offer. You will not be charged until Economist Podcasts+ launches.If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you’ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.For more information about Economist Podcasts+, including how to get access, please visit our FAQs page. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/651ed6f7e6253800116670e9/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ROwlAN4057K_ZDjniEPzewIgzxSxsWljzhghNSTNWeA</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 15:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/651ed6f7e6253800116670e9/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ROwlAN4057K_ZDjniEPzewIgzxSxsWljzhghNSTNWeA" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Trailer</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/650352570510640012653475/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=cCWjT-6ehhLlRZH5Q9sZRqbc7a5XVtTa3Ji_uA5_VvI</link>
			<description>Take a seat at the table and learn about the biggest stories in financial markets, the economy and business. Each week our editors and correspondents explore how economics influences the world we live in and share their insights across a range of topics. From inflation and recession risk to all things crypto and even the commercial success of K-pop, we have you covered. Published every Thursday. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/650352570510640012653475/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=cCWjT-6ehhLlRZH5Q9sZRqbc7a5XVtTa3Ji_uA5_VvI</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 04:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:01:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/650352570510640012653475/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=cCWjT-6ehhLlRZH5Q9sZRqbc7a5XVtTa3Ji_uA5_VvI" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: Goldin rules</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6528257ed40c970012791a0c/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=IiNG4l93ZRBWKpvz8wTNQzGaoLsCrHbBy9uv_sSQH2k</link>
			<description>It’s that time of year when an economist is woken by an early call from the Nobel Committee in Sweden. This year, it was the turn of Claudia Goldin, whose work has revolutionised our understanding of gender in the labour market. And on this week’s podcast, we speak to her.Hosts: Mike Bird, Alice Fulwood and Tom Lee-Devlin. Guests: Arjun Ramani, from The Economist; and Claudia Goldin.Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our limited time offer. You will not be charged until Economist Podcasts+ launches.If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you’ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.For more information about Economist Podcasts+, including how to get access, please visit our FAQs page. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6528257ed40c970012791a0c/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=IiNG4l93ZRBWKpvz8wTNQzGaoLsCrHbBy9uv_sSQH2k</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 16:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/6528257ed40c970012791a0c/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=IiNG4l93ZRBWKpvz8wTNQzGaoLsCrHbBy9uv_sSQH2k" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Money Talks: The future of crypto, part one</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/653167ef6a17f8001243a94b/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=sy6uM5Hw9mwAz27wwxj5BHKm9CPubcM3MMoUeNxoRdY</link>
			<description>In downtown Manhattan, what is perhaps the biggest event in the history of crypto is playing out: the trial of Sam Bankman-Fried. SBF, as he’s known, is accused of masterminding a fraud that left $8bn in customer funds missing; he has pleaded not guilty. This week, we hear from author Michael Lewis, who was there for the rise and fall of SBF’s crypto empire. Next week, we speak to the man who wants to take his crown.Hosts: Tom Lee-Devlin, Mike Bird and Alice Fulwood. Guests: Michael Lewis.Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our limited time offer. You will not be charged until Economist Podcasts+ launches.If you’re already a subscriber to The Economist, you’ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.For more information about Economist Podcasts+, including how to get access, please visit our FAQs page. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/653167ef6a17f8001243a94b/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=sy6uM5Hw9mwAz27wwxj5BHKm9CPubcM3MMoUeNxoRdY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 17:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistmoneytalks/e/653167ef6a17f8001243a94b/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=sy6uM5Hw9mwAz27wwxj5BHKm9CPubcM3MMoUeNxoRdY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
