<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>The Hamilton Morris Podcast</title>
		<link>https://www.patreon.com/HamiltonMorris</link>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<category>Science</category>
		<image>
			<url>https://is3-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts126/v4/a6/99/35/a6993546-87c4-bc77-62c4-4e56b0058642/mza_1854238532438350957.jpg/313x0w.webp</url>
			<title>The Hamilton Morris Podcast</title>
		</image>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">36590770</guid>
			<title>#001 Interview With A Man Who Sold LSD To Steve Jobs</title>
			<description>I don't usually interview people involved with the distribution side of psychedelics, but this conversation touches on so many fascinating topics in the history of LSD that I thought other people might find it interesting. The conversation covers Steve Jobs, Kary Mullis, ergotamine tartrate, LSD distribution, and SARS-CoV-2. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/bf/50/bf504aaeeae0dc82c669790c6c680d1b88a49be568c7e62d2797e27685d0fae9.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:16:34</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20200430080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">37012316</guid>
			<title>#002 Conversation With A Clandestine Quaalude Cook</title>
			<description>Please enjoy the second installment of my "podcast"
</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/70/90/7090a50782706707963fa6606239ea943eee44cb1482bab982487522cda82b9b.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>00:49:29</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20200512080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">37646727</guid>
			<title>#003 Interview With An MK-801-Naut</title>
			<description>A most superlative discussion of NMDA antagonists! MK-801 is the strongest dissociative that has been used by humans, it is also one of the most mysterious and (arguably) one of the most dangerous. Episode three of my podcast features an interview with a teenager who ordered MK-801 and tested it on himself and his friends. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/08/ea/08eae72e5d33dbf5349a56406b49fdc2cf5fca7bf5f0c4bf648d04c901696dd7.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>00:43:51</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20200529080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">37745739</guid>
			<title>#004 An Interview With DEA Chemist Terry Dal Cason</title>
			<description>In this almost three hour conversation with senior forensic DEA chemist Terry Dal Cason we discuss MDMA chemistry, fentanyl, police brutality, and the ethics of prohibition. Terry Dal Cason is a complicated figure who the clandestine MDMA chemist Strike called, "The godfather of all clandestine ecstasy chemistry."</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/d7/21/d721001d5ac58eafc68ea90d71d40f5eb339d24f542d73c42d34227df1a0cd8b.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>02:51:57</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20200531080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">38669443</guid>
			<title>#005 Journal Club: LSD and the Head Twitch Response</title>
			<description>This podcast is the first of what I hope to be a series of "journal club" discussions with scientists about an important scientific paper. In this episode Jason Wallach and I discuss the strange origin of the head twitch response and how it became the most important behavioral correlate for 5HT2A agonism in non-human animals. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/2b/e0/2be08839188e6a74c71f7da37c043e8ed679efe61b6fa4ab6cc65045d6151724.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:07:52</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20200627080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">42647842</guid>
			<title>#006 Production update</title>
			<description>Hi, all. Here's a new podcast with an update with what I've been working on regarding Pharmacopeia. In this conversation I'm joined by producer Soren Shade.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/5c/ab/5cab61abe3211c84ab81dab0bc9b155d32257fd608dc08551c1ba0eb4fc69d1f.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>00:33:52</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20201012080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">44026069</guid>
			<title>#007 Production update 2</title>
			<description>The end is in sight. Enjoy a second installment of the production podcast in which I am joined again by friend and producer Soren Shade.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/95/91/95913aa71fc9714c4245720fabccb4e847d6d73b7f6b75c880c9596d75688d3b.mp4" />
			<ns0:duration>00:34:21</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20201118080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">44422985</guid>
			<title>#008 A Talk With Errol Morris</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with my father about his new documentary "My Psychedelic Love Story", which premieres Sunday, November 29th on Showtime. Many thanks for Josh Kearney for recording this discussion. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/92/22/9222c62f81c1ef08a6b93f4a62088f8d033048fec87a2ffa6d40fb85bbd9ab25.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:11:04</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20201129080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">46188962</guid>
			<title>#009 A Talk With Eric Andre</title>
			<description>Hi, all. It turns out Eric Andre is a fan of the show and he called me yesterday to talk, here is our conversation.

In other news, we are gearing up to print a third and final edition of the pamphlet. The first edition was only 500 copies and contained a couple typos, the second edition is 2,500 copies and the third edition will be 5,000 copies. The pamphlet has already raised more than $70,000 for the Michael J Fox Foundation and more than $10,000 for the original toad artist Gail Patterson. As stipulated in the episode, I also plan to donate some money to toad conservation efforts via the Tucson Herpetological Society, but I'm waiting on them to propose a specific plan for the money before making the donation. Thanks everyone who bought a copy and for those that didn't I will be sure to post here first when the new edition is available.

I've recorded a couple of new Patreon-exclusive interviews that I'm currently editing, one about the chemistry of N-hydroxy-MDA and another that is a long discussion of the meth episode and disparaging article about the show by Erik Davis.  

I hope to have those out by the end of the week.

(No audio files, only a YouTube video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oXRcly_jDoM&ab_channel=HamiltonMorris)</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="" />
			<ns0:duration>00:00:00</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210114080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">46893109</guid>
			<title>Interview With A European PCE Chemist</title>
			<description>Hi, all. I've been receiving interesting messages from a variety of different chemists recently. Here is a discussion with a chemist who synthesized and tested an unusual arylcyclohexylamine called PCE

EDIT: I was interested in learning more about his technique for producing NaCN. I've attached an interesting article from 1895 that describes a similar process as well as a long Science Madness thread. Cyanide's reputation is deserved, it is seriously a deadly poison, a chemist friend killed himself with it last year. This is not some corny, "Don't try this at home!" boilerplate. Seriously––do not try this at home. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/71/1d/711dd5c13efb1b38ab67a4afe4958e34bf267e2d37048920170292eb1087d5ab.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:10:46</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210131080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
			<title>EXPLOSIONS AND FIRE!</title>
			<description>Here I interview the great Australian chemistry YouTube titan Explosions and Fire.

Philip Eaton's original cubane synthesis and an article reviewing reported ingestions of C4 plastic explosive are attached.

Here is a link to the Explosions and Fire cubane synthesis videos: https://www.youtube.com/c/ExplosionsFire2/search?query=cubane

Here is a link to Sir Martyn Poliakoff's seemingly naive support for the elimination of industrially useful chemicals that could be employed in the manufacture of chemical weapons: https://www.youtube.com/watch?t=188&v=n7uJoi8DXiA&feature=youtu.be&ab_channel=PeriodicVideos

The story of the chemist who blew off his hands during an ETN recrystallization: https://www.sciencemadness.org/whisper/viewthread.php?tid=22554

My HBO piece that features NurdRage: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=35XGfnmTm8E&ab_channel=VICENews</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/c3/c9/c3c91d6ca715f4a772581cc4de4d085005dff209c126ac830aae73dad916cc48.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>02:01:48</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210214080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">48027722</guid>
			<title>#012 PCP Cops</title>
			<description>An interview with infamous undercover LAPD "dope cop" Frank Lyga about his career tracking clandestine PCP synthesists. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/19/56/1956900873869234eaffc3dffb87a3ec0598032b481f8c48eace3ce6b12dd25f.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:02:13</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210226080000</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">48249754</guid>
			<title>#013 Dr. David Juurlink</title>
			<description>Follow him on twitter @DavidJuurlink

Fitting that the 13th upload would be fraught with problems, but the third time's the charm!</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/38/c1/38c17fb35351607df685173a8a98b37645da5f66b3ed8e604e6340c9941d5525.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:18:09</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210302210455</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">48839628</guid>
			<title>#014 Cop Talk, Interview With A Self-Critical Police Officer</title>
			<description>In this podcast I tell a story of grotesque corruption and cronyism that radicalized me as a teenager and made me recognize the horrors of the war on drugs. I also interview a self-critical cop about what it's like to enforce drug laws. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/2c/4d/2c4d7df92538b71d9223830c04d73f0076af41c5c3f4dfcbd02a696becadbb24.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:16:53</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210316213623</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">49330103</guid>
			<title>#015 An Interview With Psychedelic Lawyer Richard Glen Boire</title>
			<description>(No description)</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 02:35:03 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/dc/dc/dcdcff3cc7c515684cd766f098391fd2875a96c42ea0abf6de3e5e5ac8be0f05.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:29:55</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210329023503</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">50507016</guid>
			<title>#017 Interview With Bill Richards</title>
			<description>Here is a discussion about psychedelics, pharmaceutical companies, and psychotherapy with living legend Bill Richards. I've attached his PhD dissertation below and here is a link to the episode of 60 Minutes described in the interview. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 18:40:49 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/df/b4/dfb4219e48df519b5ea0718246f04e27478471b35e788ba5875b0aab8273b5c0.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:00:26</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210426184049</ns0:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">50740223</guid>
			<title>#018 Clandestine Chromium Carbene Chemistry</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview a former organometallic chemist named Mike Roberts who conducted underground research on DMT, DET, DiPT, DOM, 2C-B, and mescaline while working as a graduate student at UCLA. After a year of continuous psychedelic use his studies ended when began to confuse reality with a dream. I've attached one of Mike Roberts chemistry publications below. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 23:08:18 </pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/92/49/924967e2bc662930bfe5668f443ae50a375898f96e39ef983a38ee64ad8de70a.mp3" />
			<ns0:duration>01:34:18</ns0:duration>
			<ns0:order>20210501230818</ns0:order>
</item>

	</channel>
</rss>
