<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Americast</title>
		<link>https://web.24syv.dk/channels/82</link>
		<description>A message to Americasters from the Zurch.</description>
		<language>da-DK</language>
		<itunes:image href="https://assets.listentonews.com/uploads/provider/logo/336/p07hbbyd.jpg"/>
		<item>
			<title>America looks set for Trump v Biden</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h8nk84.mp3</link>
			<description>The Americast team pore over the New Hampshire results after an evening in which Donald Trump looks to have the Republican nomination all but sewn up. Nikki Haley says she's a fighter and that the race &quot;is far from over&quot; but is there really a route back from here?Earlier in the evening, Sarah caught up with former White House press secretary Sean Spicer, who told us why he thought Trump’s various indictments have helped him in the polls so far.And, Ron DeSantis officially suspended his campaign before the New Hampshire primary. What next for him? We answer your questions about the Florida governor.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Sean Spicer, Former White House Press Secretary under Donald TrumpGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast. Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by George Dabby with Catherine Fusillo, Madeleine Drury and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Philip Bull. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h8nk84.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:37</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h8nk84.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Christiane Amanpour on Biden's Iran Dilemma</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h89257.mp3</link>
			<description>The world waits to see how the United States will retaliate to a drone strike that killed three American troops in Jordan, after an Iran-backed militia group claimed responsibility for the attack.Christiane Amanpour, the Iranian-British Chief International Anchor for CNN, is our star guest this week. We hear why Joe Biden now walks a tightrope between avoiding escalation in the Middle East, and projecting strength at home - all while Donald Trump looks on from the campaign trail.Also on the podcast, Marianna tells us about her new BBC Radio 4 podcast series called 'Why Do You Hate Me?'She’s been speaking to a survivor of the deadliest mass shooting by a single gunman in American history, who ended up believing online conspiracy theories that the entire event was a government plot. HOSTS: 
• Sarah Smith, North America editor 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUEST: 
Christiane Amanpour, Chief International Anchor for CNNGET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. US Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155 Listen to 'Why Do You Hate Me?' on BBC Sounds: https://www.bbc.co.uk/sounds/brand/p0h46gmnThis episode was made by George Dabby with Catherine Fusillo, Rufus Gray, and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h89257.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h89257.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America looks set for Trump v Biden</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h6rn9m.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald wins... and then lashes out at Nikki Haley. The Americast team pore over the New Hampshire results after an evening in which Donald Trump looks to have the Republican nomination all but sewn up. Nikki Haley says she's a fighter and that the race &quot;is far from over&quot; but is there really a route back from here?Earlier in the evening, Sarah caught up with former White House press secretary Sean Spicer, who told us why he thought Trump’s various indictments have helped him in the polls so far.And, Ron DeSantis officially suspended his campaign before the New Hampshire primary. What next for him? We answer your questions about the Florida governor.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Sean Spicer, Former White House Press Secretary under Donald TrumpGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast. Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by George Dabby with Catherine Fusillo, Madeleine Drury and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Philip Bull. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h6rn9m.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h6rn9m.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Election Trail: From Iowa to New Hampshire</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h5ws5q.mp3</link>
			<description>Hot on the heels of the Iowa caucus, Republican candidates Donald Trump, Nikki Haley and Ron DeSantis prepare for the next primary showdown in New Hampshire. Sarah and Justin unpack if it could prove to be a tougher test for Trump and a way back into the race for the other candidates.And, why are the Democrats infighting after Biden’s idea to bump the state from its prized primary calendar slot?HOSTS:
Sarah Smith, North America editor
Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenterGET IN TOUCH:
Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
Or use #Americast. Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by George Dabby with Catherine Fusillo, Madeleine Drury, Maia Davies and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h5ws5q.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h5ws5q.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump Wins Iowa Landslide</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h572s9.mp3</link>
			<description>The 2024 presidential election is officially underway.Americast hits the road for a record breaking caucus. Destination? Des Moines, Iowa. It’s not only the coldest caucus ever seen in Iowa, but it’s also the biggest landslide for a Republican nominee. The question is whether it’s enough to bury his main rivals Ron Desantis and Nikki Haley for good, or whether the runners up are still even in the running at all.The gang chew through the numbers with the famed pollster Frank Luntz, and Sarah gets a peek into the Trump family business by speaking to the former President’s son, Eric.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:• Eric Trump, Son of President Donald Trump
• Frank Luntz, Political strategist and pollsterGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by George Dabby with Rufus Gray and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Darren Wardrobe. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h572s9.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:51:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h572s9.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can Anyone Stop Trump in Iowa?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h4jsc0.mp3</link>
			<description>With the Iowa caucus just days away, Chris Christie drops out of the 2024 presidential race. Can anyone stop Donald Trump? The team takes a look at why Iowa dominates the political conversation every four years.Anthony Blinken is once again in the Middle East to broker peace in the region amid a barrage of attacks by Houthi rebels against Red Sea shipping.And on Saturday Taiwan heads to the polls for its presidential elections in a vote that could shape the future of relations between the US and China. With the help of Ivo Daalder, former US Ambassador to NATO, the team takes you inside the Americast Situation Room to monitor the biggest challenges the US faces around the world.HOSTS: 
• Sarah Smith, North America editor 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent GUEST: 
• Ivo Daalder, Former United States Permanent Representative to NATO GET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480 
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk 
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. This episode was made by George Dabby with Rufus Gray and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Dafydd Evans. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h4jsc0.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 22:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:09</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h4jsc0.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Epstein Files: Former US Presidents Named</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h354vc.mp3</link>
			<description>High-profile associates of Jeffrey Epstein named in US court papers.Former presidents Bill Clinton and Donald Trump are among the people named in US court papers detailing connections of late sex offender Jeffrey Epstein.The team assesses what we know so far, what’s to come, and how the story has played out on social media.And after weeks of controversy, Claudine Gay has stepped down as president of Harvard University following her comments on anti-Semitism. We speak to the reporter who got the scoop on the plagiarism story about why he thinks she had no choice but to step down.HOSTS: 
• Sarah Smith, North America editor 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUEST: 
• Aaron Sibarium, Reporter at The Washington Free BeaconGET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. This episode was made by George Dabby with Catherine Fusillo, Rufus Gray, Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h354vc.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h354vc.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Merry Cast: Past, Present and Future of US Politics</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h1xtgc.mp3</link>
			<description>Americast reimagines the Dickens classic, A Christmas Carol, to understand the changing landscape of American politics. They are joined by Heather Cox Richardson, historian and author of the hugely popular newsletter &quot;Letters from an American&quot;, who helps guide them through the past, the present and the future of the United States on this special Christmas edition.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Heather Cox Richardson, author GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by George Dabby with Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Jack Graysmark. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h1xtgc.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h1xtgc.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Colorado Kicks Trump Off the Ballot</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h113j0.mp3</link>
			<description>The Colorado Supreme Court has ruled that Trump cannot run for president in the state. The Trump team has called the decision “completely flawed” and will appeal to the US Supreme Court. But will this lead other states to follow suit? The Americast team brings in a constitutional expert – Kermit Roosevelt III – to dive into the 14th amendment and what could happen next. HOSTS: 
• Sarah Smith, North America editor 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUEST: 
• Kermit Roosevelt III, author and constitutional scholarGET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. This episode was made by George Dabby with Catherine Fusillo, Rufus Gray, Claire Betzer and Cordelia Hemming. The technical producer was Matthew Dean. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h113j0.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h113j0.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Beto on the Border: Ex Presidential Candidate on the US Immigration Crisis</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gznzyt.mp3</link>
			<description>In a week dominated by legal cases, the team takes you into the virtual Americast courtroom to dissect the various trials involving Donald Trump and Rudy Giuliani.Sarah’s back from her trip to the US/Mexico border and tells us how it relates to a funding deadlock in Congress for support to Ukraine. One person who lives on that border is former presidential candidate Beto O’Rourke. He dials in to chat about how the deadlock can be broken and enters his own predictions into the Americast time capsule…HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUEST: 
• Beto O’Rourke, Former Democrat presidential candidate GET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480 
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk 
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. This episode was made by George Dabby with Alix Pickles, Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gznzyt.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 23:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gznzyt.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Donald Trump: Dictator in Chief?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gybmfr.mp3</link>
			<description>The shadow looming over the fourth Republican debate was the party’s most recent president, Donald Trump. But while the other candidates traded blows at one another, Trump was conspicuously absent, instead taking part in a town hall event on Tuesday evening. He raised eyebrows when saying he would only be a dictator on ‘day one’ if elected president. The Americast team chew over Trump’s comments – and the Republican debate – before speaking to GOP candidate Asa Hutchinson, the former governor of Arkansas who’s still in the race for the White House.And, a clip of American university leaders has gone viral after they failed to say explicitly to Congress that calling for the genocide of Jewish people violated their schools code of conduct. The team assesses how we’ve reached this point. HOSTS: 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUEST: 
• Asa Hutchinson, Republican presidential candidate GET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480 
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk 
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. This episode was made by George Dabby with Alix Pickles, Catherine Fusillo, Claire Betzer and Maia Davies. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gybmfr.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:50</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gybmfr.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Rachel Maddow on Kissinger, Trump and Misinformation</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gwzdd9.mp3</link>
			<description>Former US Secretary of State Henry Kissinger has died at the age of 100.The team take a world tour of the polarising statesman’s legacy with his biographer.MSNBC host Rachel Maddow talks about Trump, misinformation and charting the rise of fascism in the US in her new book.And, what does New York Congressman George Santos have to say about efforts to expel him from the US House of Representatives? HOSTS: 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUESTS: 
• Rachel Maddow, broadcaster and author
• Thomas Schwartz, US historianGET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480 
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk 
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. This episode was made by George Dabby with Alix Pickles, Catherine Fusillo, Claire Betzer and Maia Davies. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gwzdd9.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gwzdd9.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sam Altman: A Silicon Valley Soap Opera</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gvcwjd.mp3</link>
			<description>Happy Thanksgiving Americasters!
 
OpenAI co-founder Sam Altman is returning as boss just days after he was fired by the board.
 
The team talk about the whole story: who he is, and who’s winning the AI arms race, with New York Times tech journalist Mike Isaac.
 
And – the lives of two turkeys, ‘Liberty and ‘Bell’, have been saved after they received a pardoning from Joe Biden in time for Thanksgiving.
 
A former White House chef reveals the favourite foods of past presidents.
 
HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent
 
GUESTS:
• Mike Isaac, New York Times tech journalist
• John Moeller, former White House chef
 
GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast
 
Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.
 
This episode was made by Chris Flynn with Alix Pickles, Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Ben Andrews. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gvcwjd.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:27</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gvcwjd.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>US x China: Friends Reunited?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gt6k5f.mp3</link>
			<description>Sarah didn’t quite make it to dinner with Xi Jinping at the APEC Summit, but we spoke to someone who did, an old friend he met in 1985 at a potluck in Muscatine, Iowa.Back in the present, the Chinese president has held talks with Joe Biden for the first time in over a year. What came from the meeting and where has it landed US/China relations?
 
And, Gen Z and Millennials will make up half of the electorate when it comes to the 2024 presidential election. The Americast team looks at the political power of social media with Gen Z TikTok influencers Harry Sisson and Isabel Brown.
 
HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent
 
GUESTS:
• Harry Sisson, TikTok influencer
• Isabel Brown, TikTok influencer 
• Sarah Lande, Iowa resident and friend of Xi Jinping
 
GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast
 
Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.
 
This episode was made by George Dabby with Alix Pickles, Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The series producer is George Dabby. The technical producer was Matt Hewitt. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gt6k5f.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 01:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gt6k5f.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump’s Poll Position</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0grtw1v.mp3</link>
			<description>As votes from Election Day 2023 were tallied up this week, wins for Democrats may have given a preview into next year’s presidential election. But new polls seem to point towards a rocky road to re-election for President Joe Biden. It’s not all good news for Trump, though. He and his children took the stand in New York, giving evidence in the civil fraud case brought against him. How might these problems play out as the 2024 presidential elections near? Expert pollster and political analyst Amy Walter joins the team to make sense of it all.HOSTS:
Sarah Smith, North America editor
Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST(S):
Amy Walter, Editor-in-Chief of The Cook Political ReportGET IN TOUCH:
Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by George Dabby with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The series producer is Daniel Wittenberg. The technical producer was Philip Bull. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0grtw1v.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0grtw1v.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Americanswers LIVE: One Year To Go</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gqh0v7.mp3</link>
			<description>Twelve months until the US election, Americasters join us on the recording to ask some of the big questions about an era-defining presidential poll and help the team put some predictions in the Americast time capsule.Will it be Biden v Trump again? What issues will define the race? Could we see a first female president sooner than it seems? And will Justin have a change of heart about Americast's Discord community? Listen back to our live episode.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Dafydd Evans. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gqh0v7.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gqh0v7.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Confessions From Trump's White House</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gp2ph7.mp3</link>
			<description>The aide to Donald Trump’s White House Chief of Staff opens up to Americast about her mistakes and why she believes that the former president should never be allowed near the Oval Office again.Cassidy Hutchinson explains why she wrote her candid memoir, which Trump’s team tells us “either belongs in the discount bin of the fiction section of a bookstore or should be repurposed as toilet paper.”There’s finally a new Speaker of the House of Representatives. But who is Mike Johnson?And Arnold Schwarzenegger tells Justin why he thinks Trump’s re-election hopes have terminated.Please note there is a brief suicide reference between 8:35 and 9:15.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Cassidy Hutchinson, White House aide under President TrumpGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastJoin us for our live episode, marking one year to go to the US election, on our Discord server at 18:00 GMT on Thursday, 2 November: https://discord.com/invite/64ZfGct4A3?event=1168526948046225498This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Philip Bull. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gp2ph7.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gp2ph7.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Leaders Of The Free World?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gmnxlh.mp3</link>
			<description>President Biden wanted to show America’s global strength during his flying visit to Israel this week, but does the United States still call the shots internationally? The Americast team reviews Biden’s high-stakes 30 hours in the region, talks about the misinformation swirling around the internet, and weighs in on America’s place in the world.Back in DC, House Republicans are still struggling to elect a Speaker after two rounds of voting. Anthony gavels the gang in for a crash course on the latest congressional chaos.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent
 
GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Rufus Gray, with Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is Daniel Wittenberg and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gmnxlh.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:37</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gmnxlh.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America and Israel: Unconditional Allies?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gl7lws.mp3</link>
			<description>President Biden has promised to support Israel with whatever it needs and forcefully condemned the attacks by Hamas on civilians. But what do Americans think about the unfolding conflict in the Middle East?The Americast team also hears from 2020 presidential candidate and co-founder of the Forward Party, Andrew Yang, on why third parties are important to US politics and what it’s like running for the Oval Office.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Andrew Yang, 2020 Democratic presidential candidateGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Rufus Gray with Claire Betzer and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Philip Bull and the sound designer was David Crackles. The series producer is Daniel Wittenberg. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gl7lws.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gl7lws.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We Need To Talk About Kevin McCarthy</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gjsgvv.mp3</link>
			<description>For the first time in US history, a speaker has been kicked out. A group of Trump-supporting Republicans carried out a coup to remove him from the chair of the House of Representatives.How did it come about? What does it say about the Republican Party? Put simply, what the hell happens now? Americast is called to order to shed light on the situation in Congress.And on the theme of political division, Naomi Klein explains her theory behind what’s making America hard to govern and why not everyone on the left wants to get behind Joe Biden.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUESTS:
• Naomi Klein, liberal writer and activist
• Victoria Spartz, Ukrainian-born Republican congresswomanGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Ben Andrews and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gjsgvv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gjsgvv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump's Debate Escape</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ghcj4v.mp3</link>
			<description>Why did Donald Trump skip another Republican debate? Sarah is sent to Michigan instead of California as Trump and Joe Biden race to show their solidarity with striking car factory workers.Marc Lotter, who ran the comms on Trump's last campaign and was press secretary for Vice-President Mike Pence, tells the Americast team about the ex-president's re-election strategy.He gives his take on why Trump doesn't need to debate his Republican rivals, which vice-presidential pick could help put him back into the Oval Office, and the only thing that could stop Trump from winning the Republican nomination.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Marc Lotter, Donald Trump's 2020 campaign communications directorGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Catherine Fusillo, Claire Betzer and Hayley Clarke. The technical producer was Gareth Jones. The series producer is Daniel Wittenberg.CLIP CREDITS:
• CBS Sports Network
• Fox BusinessBBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
0:05 – Taylor Swift at the NFL
6:55 – Trump skips another Republican debate
13:14 – Marc Lotter interview
32:40 – Is a government shutdown looming?</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ghcj4v.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ghcj4v.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Funding Ukraine… or America First?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gg1pct.mp3</link>
			<description>Some US politicians are growing impatient over supporting the war effort – and a lot could change if Donald Trump wins back the White House.Our very own Anthony was in the Oval Office to see President Zelensky meet its current occupant, Joe Biden, while Sarah watched them address the UN. We talk about how Washington views America’s role in the conflict.And Marianna chats to award-winning true crime podcasters, Suruthi Bala and Hannah Maguire, about the harmful effects of social media’s obsession with crime cases and whether that could extend to US politics.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUESTS:
• Suruthi Bala, 'RedHanded' podcast host
• Hannah Maguire, 'RedHanded' podcast hostGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Ricardo McCarthy and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
2:27 – Will the US election decide the war in Ukraine?
21:10 – TikTok frenzies and true crime in America
38:28 – Rep. Lauren Boebert “reaching across the aisle”</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gg1pct.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gg1pct.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Age of Biden</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gdphh3.mp3</link>
			<description>Is Joe Biden too old to win another go in the White House? And could his son derail his campaign? The Americast team talks through the challenges the president is facing in the run-up to the next election.Barack Obama's former spokesperson and podcaster Tommy Vietor gives us his thoughts on Biden's achievements and viral moments, as well as his 2024 chances, with some critics obsessed by his age and sceptical about Vice President Kamala Harris.And the gang tries to guess the Republican presidential candidate from the songs that supposedly &quot;stir their souls&quot;.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUEST:
• Tommy Vietor, host of 'Pod Save America' and 'Pod Save the World'GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo and Hayley Clarke. The technical producer was Daffyd Evans. The series producer is Daniel Wittenberg and the senior editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
03:10 – Joe Biden's age
15:50 – Tommy Vietor interview
35:00 – Republican soul songs</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gdphh3.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gdphh3.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Does The BBC Get Its Trump Coverage Right?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gc73xp.mp3</link>
			<description>How do we cover a headline-grabbing former president who falsely claims he never lost the election?Two of our bosses step into the worldwide HQ of Americast for the kind of conversation we normally have in our morning meetings: what past mistakes can we learn from and what’s the BBC’s strategy for reporting on Donald Trump’s campaign and his court cases?HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUESTS:
• Paul Danahar, BBC News Foreign Editor
• Adam Levy, BBC News Channel Executive ProducerGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo and Hayley Clarke. The technical producer was Emma Crowe and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
7:14 – Is Trump a special case?
21:59 – Does the BBC have a liberal bias?
28:33 – Should we show Trump's speeches live?
33:58 – How will the BBC cover the 2024 election?</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gc73xp.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gc73xp.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Pop Save America</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gb05yx.mp3</link>
			<description>Charting music's part in US politics, from 1970s disco to 'Rich Men North of Richmond', which has become a surprise No.1 hit. What does this country song, claimed by conservatives, tell us about American society? The Americast team talk to the BBC's 'Professor of Pop', Paul Gambaccini, about protest music in the States.And what happens when musicians refuse to be used by politicians? Karen Willis, manager of The Village People and the wife of its lead singer, tells us about the YMCA group's cease and desist letter against Donald Trump.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUESTS:
• Karen Willis, manager of 'The Village People'
• Paul Gambaccini, Radio 2 presenterGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Daffyd Evans and the editor was Damon Rose.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
19:16 – Karen Willis
28:18 – Paul Gambaccini</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gb05yx.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0gb05yx.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Republican Rumble</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g8nlj0.mp3</link>
			<description>While his challengers clashed in Milwaukee, Donald Trump skipped the first Republican debate of the campaign for the relative comfort of an interview with ex-Fox News anchor Tucker Carlson.Did any of the other presidential candidates surprise? It’s an Americast Wisconsin special as the team try cheese curds and sip beer at a bar near the venue and link up with Sarah, who’s in Atlanta waiting for Trump’s latest arrest, to break down the showdown and the no-show.And Marianna chats to local voters about how the politics has been playing out on their social media feeds.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Rufus Gray with Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Emma Crowe. The series producer is Daniel Wittenberg and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
00:00 – Trump’s Debate No-Show
04:07 – Debate Winners and Losers
18:36 – US Voters Social Media Panel
33:31 – Cheese Curd Wisconsinbly</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g8nlj0.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g8nlj0.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Big Republican Debate Preview with Jake Tapper</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g7djrs.mp3</link>
			<description>As the last Republican presidential hopefuls try to qualify for the opening debate of the primary in Milwaukee next week, Donald Trump is deciding whether to turn up or to surrender to a court in Georgia. Jake Tapper, who has moderated election debates for CNN, joins the Americast team to explain what they are like behind the scenes and how this one could play out.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Jake Tapper, CNN anchor and author GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Alix Pickles and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Gareth Jones and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
0:04 – Republican debate bingo
3:18 – Will Trump turn up?
12:17 – Jake Tapper</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g7djrs.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g7djrs.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Indictment Four Trump</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g6rqtx.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump has been criminally charged for the fourth time in a frenzied five months. Now he’s accused of trying to interfere with the result of the 2020 election in Georgia.The Americast team stays up late into the Atlanta and Washington nights (while Justin mans the Radio 4 studio) to talk through what’s in the indictment – and why this one could be the most challenging yet for Trump.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Josh McKoon, Georgia Republican Party chairmanGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg. The technical producer was Philip Bull and the editor was Sam Bonham.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
02:45 – Instant reaction
15:19 - Sarah interviews Josh McKoon
24:06 – Listener question</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g6rqtx.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 05:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:37</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g6rqtx.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>From Our US Correspondent</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g5y5zh.mp3</link>
			<description>As Donald Trump prepares for a possible fourth indictment, Americast wonders if the word “unprecedented” has lost all meaning. To find out, we gather together four BBC Washington reporters past and present to talk about how US politics has changed since their tenures, swap stories of presidential interviews, and share American memories through the medium of show and tell.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUESTS:
• Matt Frei, Channel 4 News presenter
• Nick Bryant, ex-BBC New York correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Rufus Gray with Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Gareth Jones. The series producer is Daniel Wittenberg and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.BBC SOUNDS CHAPTERS:
2:35 – The Presidents &amp; The Unprecedented
16:57 – Show &amp; Tell
27:18 – The 2024 Election</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g5y5zh.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g5y5zh.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Americanswers: Can Trump Still Win Again?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g4rbkd.mp3</link>
			<description>As Donald Trump pleads not guilty over the Capitol riot, will his third criminal indictment impact his election chances?Is the ex-president allowed to use campaign money to fund his legal battles? Could he really be president from jail? And is there no-one in the Democratic Party who will challenge Joe Biden?We’re back (and Justin has woken up!) to answer questions from Americasters with the help of political correspondent Liz Landers, who's standing in for Anthony (but doesn’t have his pink suit).HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUEST:
• Liz Landers, political correspondent GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo and Hayley Clarke. The technical producer was Philip Bull and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g4rbkd.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:25</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g4rbkd.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Capitol Punishment</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g485jk.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump has been charged with a third set of crimes. This time he's accused of plotting to overturn his election defeat after an inquiry into the storming of the Capitol two years ago on January 6th.Former FBI director James Comey, who was fired by Trump, joins this emergency Americast, as we look at what happens next and what it could mean for the ex-president's attempt to return to the White House.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUEST:
• James Comey, former FBI directorGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Lee Wilson. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g485jk.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:58</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g485jk.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>X-tra Terrestrials</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g3cqjs.mp3</link>
			<description>Viral memes and alien themes: the Americast News Feed returns as we scroll through the biggest stories trending on social media.Twitter X and Threads fight for online attention while Congress hears unworldly claims about the existence of UFOs.Hunter Biden’s legal troubles continue, and 81-year-old Senator Mitch McConnell freezes during a press conference.These topics and much more are unpacked on Americast’s podcast equivalent of a social network.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Catherine Fusillo, Natasha Fernandes and Hayley Clarke. The technical producer was Gareth Jones and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor was Tim Walklate.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g3cqjs.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g3cqjs.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Barbie's Hot Right Now</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g1vvt2.mp3</link>
			<description>Could global warming make some states uninhabitable? With parts of the US sweltering in record-breaking heatwaves, the Americast team wonders whether cities like Phoenix in Arizona can continue to survive by the end of the century.Meanwhile, Sarah enjoys cooler temperatures in Colorado and catches up with the UK Foreign Secretary James Cleverly at the Aspen Security Forum.And Hollywood strikes have held up the Barbie film's press tour, but could politicians learn a thing or two from its internet-breaking marketing campaign?HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• James Cleverly, UK Foreign SecretaryGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray, Natasha Fernandes and Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Dafydd Evans and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g1vvt2.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 22:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g1vvt2.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bidenwatch</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g09v03.mp3</link>
			<description>Joe sets his sights on Nato but is being criticised at home.The Americast team reconvene early from their holidays to react to Joe Biden’s brief visit to the UK. Justin is joined by Katty Kay and Anthony is pulled out of bed in Washington DC at 4:30am to join the new Americast Breakfast Club.BBC political editor Chris Mason is on hand too. And there’s one more question to answer: is the Commander in Chief actually a nice guy? He’s faced criticism for not publicly acknowledging his granddaughter. Is his family man image at risk?HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Katty Kay, USA special correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUESTS:
• Chris Mason, political editorGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Rufus Gray. The technical producer was Emma Crowe. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g09v03.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:58</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0g09v03.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>LGBT Rights Special: Padam Vice President</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fy4lj0.mp3</link>
			<description>Rainbow flags symbolising LGBT freedoms are being flown in many parts of the world this Pride month, but in some parts of America they are being lowered due to state bans. Why have these kinds of issues become so political?Bobby Berk, star of hit makeover show Queer Eye, joins the Americast team, along with a Republican activist, to tell us how LGBT people are feeling across the US political divide.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUESTS:
• Bobby Berk, ‘Queer Eye’ host
• Jerri Ann Henry, Republican LGBT rights activistGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Alix Pickles, Natasha Fernandes and Miranda Slade. The technical producer was Mike Regaard and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fy4lj0.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fy4lj0.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Let Bidens Be Bidens</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fwjwcb.mp3</link>
			<description>Hunter Biden will plead guilty to tax and gun offences to avoid prison. The Americast team looks at whether the sins of his son could knock Joe Biden’s re-election hopes.Talking of being in trouble with the law, has Donald Trump implicated himself in a recent interview with Fox News?And it’s a tale of two Anthonys, as our very own host travels with the US Secretary of State Anthony Blinken on a historic trip to China and then the UK, and reports back on how he was received by President Xi.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Alix Pickles, Rufus Gray and Natasha Fernandes. The technical producer was Dafydd Evans and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fwjwcb.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fwjwcb.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump: For He’s A Jolly Good Felon?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fv0qw6.mp3</link>
			<description>On the eve of his 77th birthday, Donald Trump has appeared in court to face charges of mishandling classified documents. He even found time to stop by a bakery – though not for a cake to celebrate.Sarah has made it through the media scrum in a humid Miami and the Americast team has assembled early this week to talk through another day of firsts in US political history.We also hear from Miles Taylor, former chief of staff of the United States Department of Homeland Security under President Trump, about why he believes that the man he once served now poses a threat to the nation’s safety.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Miles Taylor, former chief of staff at the US Department of Homeland SecurityGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Rufus Gray, Alix Pickles and Stephanie Mitcalf. The technical producer was Philip Bull. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fv0qw6.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fv0qw6.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Who’s Taking On Trump?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ft4jcw.mp3</link>
			<description>The Republican race for the White House is getting crowded. With eight candidates all gathering in Iowa to campaign, eat roast pork and ride motorbikes, the Americast team looks at who came out on top and whether any of them could beat Donald Trump, who is facing fresh criminal charges over his handling of classified documents.Harvard professor Steven Pinker, who sees himself as a liberal, tells us why he thinks academic freedom is under threat on US college campuses.And first, Sarah wanders through the White House with the BBC’s political editor, Chris Mason, who has flown with the prime minister to Washington.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Steven Pinker, Professor of Psychology at Harvard University GET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg, with Alix Pickles, Natasha Fernandes and Alex Collins. The technical producer was Gareth Jones and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ft4jcw.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 23:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ft4jcw.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Conspiracies: Inside the Rabbit Hole</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0frtlrj.mp3</link>
			<description>Journalists and podcast hosts Jon Ronson and Gabriel Gatehouse join Marianna for a special episode of Americast delving deep down the rabbit hole of conspiracies.The trio talk about why America is a breeding ground for conspiracies, how to spot them, and what happens if they’re true.We also look at whether conspiracies and misinformation might affect the outcome of the 2024 presidential election and what role artificial intelligence could play in their spread.HOST:
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUESTS:
• Jon Ronson, host of 'Things Fell Apart'
• Gabriel Gatehouse, host of 'The Coming Storm'GET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles, Natasha Fernandes and Alex Collins. The technical producer was Ben Andrews and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0frtlrj.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:07</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0frtlrj.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ron and Elon: A Failed Launch?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fq8djw.mp3</link>
			<description>It’s Elon Musk’s latest launch… not a rocket this time, but Ron DeSantis’ campaign for president, live on Twitter! But after some technical hiccups, is it a failed lift-off? The Americast team reviews how it went and tries to answer whether Florida's governor can win the White House.And after dining with Sarah and Anthony in DC, J Smith-Cameron, who plays Gerri in Succession, meets Marianna in London ahead of the show’s finale, and turns the tables by asking her what reporters can learn from how the show portrays the media.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• J. Smith-Cameron, ‘Succession’ actressGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Ivana Davidovic, Alix Pickles and Natasha Fernandes. The technical producer was Ben Andrews. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fq8djw.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fq8djw.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America’s Murder Capital</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fp6d8j.mp3</link>
			<description>Crime is a growing worry in many American cities and has divided Democrats. New Orleans had the unenviable title of the US murder capital in 2022 – what went wrong in a city better known for its smooth music than the sound of gunfire?The Mayor of New Orleans, LaToya Cantrell, tells us what she's doing to address the poverty and lack of opportunity which have plagued her city, and why she thinks she's being unfairly targeted over her track record.And after Prince Harry and Meghan's &quot;near catastrophic&quot; New York car chase, the Americast team asks how that could really happen in midtown Manhattan.HOSTS:
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUESTS:
• LaToya Cantrell, Mayor of New Orleans
• Anna Adams, BBC reporter in New OrleansGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Natasha Fernandes, Alix Pickles and Ivana Davidovic. The studio manager was Emma Crowe and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fp6d8j.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 23:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fp6d8j.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump, Texas and Title 42</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fmlm0k.mp3</link>
			<description>Has Donald Trump’s sexual assault verdict damaged his reputation? The Americast team explains why a top Texas Republican thinks he’s toast, even though Trump is fighting the ruling.Sarah is on the US border with Mexico in El Paso, where a controversial Trump immigration policy known as Title 42 is about to expire and a state of emergency has been declared. A Texas Congressman and Democrat, Joaquin Castro, tells us why he blames President Biden as well as Trump.And Santos Watch is back after the under-fire congressman George Santos was charged with fraud, money laundering and theft of public funds.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Joaquin Castro, Texas congressman (Democrat)GET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastCLIP CREDITS:
• ABC ‘Good Morning America’Find out more about our award winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles, Ivana Davidovic and Natasha Fernandes. The studio manager was Dafydd Evans and the sound designer was David Crackles. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fmlm0k.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fmlm0k.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>DeSantis vs Disney</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fljx4w.mp3</link>
			<description>Florida's Governor Ron DeSantis has escalated his feud with Disney, launching a lawsuit against one of the country’s biggest companies. The Americast team updates us with the latest details from the battle and how it might impact his presidential campaign.
 
And Americast's own reporting royalty/fairy queen, Katty Kay, rejoins the team from outside Westminster Abbey, where the finishing touches are being made ahead of King Charles' coronation. She analyses America's obsession with the British monarchy and whether recent events have changed anything. HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
 
GUEST:
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
 
GET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast
 
Find out more about our award-winning “Undercover Voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.
 
This episode was made by Ivana Davidovic, Natasha Fernandes and Alix Pickles. The technical producer was Dafydd Evans. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fljx4w.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fljx4w.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden's Final Campaign</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fjskp7.mp3</link>
			<description>Joe Biden is officially running again! The 80-year-old president has posted a video promising “freedom” for Americans and to “finish the job”.Jim Messina, who masterminded Barack Obama’s re-election campaign, tells the Americast team that Democrats should be praying every night for Donald Trump to be their opponent, why he thinks it makes sense for Kamala Harris to stay on as vice president, and how Biden’s team can make sure his age isn’t the elephant in the room.Sarah visits a college baseball park in North Carolina to see which way voters are swinging. And Marianna checks in with our Undercover Voters, but some of them are actually distracted by the shock exit of influential anchor Tucker Carlson from Fox News.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGUEST:
• Jim Messina, Barack Obama’s re-election campaign managerGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles, Natasha Fernandes and Rufus Gray. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fjskp7.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 23:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fjskp7.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Americast News Feed</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fhxvd8.mp3</link>
			<description>Scrolling through the biggest stories in America right now. With Fox News forced to defend its editorial standards, Donald Trump attacking “pudding fingers” Ron DeSantis and a conservative beer boycott spilling over, the Americast team take a few of this week’s most talked about topics and explain the context behind the clickbait.What’s been happening? Why does it matter? And why are we seeing so much of it all on social media?We also talk about the spate of shootings of people for tragically turning up in the wrong place and the effect of “stand your ground” laws on how gun owners view self-defence.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles, Ivana Davidovic and Isobel Gough. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fhxvd8.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fhxvd8.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The President in the Pub</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fgm0l4.mp3</link>
			<description>President Biden has been travelling up and down the island of Ireland, where he’s promised to “keep the peace” but has also cracked some jokes down the pub with his distant cousins. Sarah’s been following him and trying to find out why he’s actually there.And a ruling from a Texas judge seeking to ban an abortion pill across America is being batted between various courts. Joyce Vance, who was a US attorney under Barack Obama, explains what can happen when the legal system gets personal and why it could go as far as the Supreme Court.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Joyce Vance, former US attorneyGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles and Natasha Fernandes. The technical producer was Daffyd Evans. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fgm0l4.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fgm0l4.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Elon Musk Speaks to the BBC</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fg4vwv.mp3</link>
			<description>The multi-billionaire defended his ownership of Twitter in a last-minute interview live from the company’s Silicon Valley HQ.This extra episode of Americast features his rollercoaster conversation with the BBC’s James Clayton in full.It came out of an email exchange over the BBC’s labelling on Twitter as &quot;government-funded media&quot; – Musk replied himself and agreed to an interview &quot;tonight&quot;.Asked about the mass layoffs of Twitter staff, misinformation on the platform and his unusual work habits, Musk at times tries to do the interviewing himself and admits that owning Twitter has been &quot;quite painful&quot;.HOST:
• James Clayton, BBC North America tech reporterGUEST:
• Elon Musk, Twitter CEOGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fg4vwv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:59:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fg4vwv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump On Trial</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdy9yb.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump pleads not guilty to criminal charges.The former (and aspiring future) president has been accused of falsifying business records after an investigation into hush money paid to a porn star.Sarah is back, dialling in from the middle of the media circus in Manhattan, as the team talk through Trump’s historic day in court and answer Americaster questions about what comes next.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Sarah Smith, North America editor
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Natasha Fernandes, Alix Pickles and Cat Farnsworth. The technical producer was Rohan Madison. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdy9yb.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 02:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdy9yb.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Stopping The Shootings</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdds70.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump might be dominating the news again, but Nashville is still grieving after six people were murdered in the latest school shooting. The Tennessee tragedy was one of 130 mass shootings this year alone in America.For this extra episode, we return to the question we planned to bring you earlier this week: where does gun control go from here? We explore what would and wouldn’t make a difference.And celebrity lawyer Ben Chew, who was Johnny Depp’s lead attorney last year in a defamation case against his ex-wife Amber Heard, gives us his view of how future Trump court appearances might play out, as well as his verdict on Gwyneth Paltrow’s $1 ski crash trial.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Ben Chew, celebrity lawyerGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles and Natasha Fernandes. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdds70.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdds70.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump Indicted</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fd11d1.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump becomes the first ex-president to be charged with a crime. It comes after an investigation into hush money payments to a porn star.

What did he do? What could this mean for US politics? And how are Americans reacting to the breaking news?

The Americast team fire up their phones for an emergency episode as Trump shakes up politics – again.

HOSTS: 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent  

GET IN TOUCH: 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480 
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk 
• Or use #Americast  

Find out more about our award-winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.  

This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles and Natasha Fernandes. The technical producer was Ben Andrews. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fd11d1.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fd11d1.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump Indicted</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdnpmk.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump becomes the first ex-president to be charged with a crime. It comes after an investigation into hush money payments to a porn star.What did he do? What could this mean for US politics? And how are Americans reacting to the breaking news?The Americast team fire up their phones for an emergency episode as Trump shakes up politics – again.HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGET IN TOUCH: 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480 
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk 
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles and Natasha Fernandes. The technical producer was Ben Andrews. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdnpmk.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fdnpmk.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump Under Arrest?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fbnl7x.mp3</link>
			<description>America waits to find out if a former president will find himself in handcuffs.A close ally of Donald Trump joins the Americast team to explain why it could be a case of all publicity is good publicity.We go through the potted history of the Stormy Daniels scandal, break down how it’s playing out on social media, and look at what it means for Trump’s campaign to win back the White House.And TikTok is on trial as its CEO testifies to Congress, where the app’s security is being scrutinised. Can a platform that popular really be banned?HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Katty Kay, US special correspondent
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondentGUEST:
• Bryan Lanza, former Donald Trump communications directorGET IN TOUCH:
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.This episode was made by Daniel Wittenberg with Alix Pickles, Rufus Gray and Aiden Johnson. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fbnl7x.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0fbnl7x.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>&quot;Marianne Williamson For President&quot;</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f98zqx.mp3</link>
			<description>Sarah is on holiday so the BBC's US Special Correspondent Katty Kay steps into her breach on Americast, equipped with stories of Dr Anthony Fauci saving a guest at the prestigious Gridiron dinner.The team speak to Marianne Williamson, who found fame as Oprah Winfrey's 'spiritual advisor', and who now wants to usurp Joe Biden to become the Democratic nominee for President, despite newly-emerged allegations of bullying her staffers.There are other challenges for Biden this week, though - Marianna Spring talks us through how the president's controversial plans to approve oil drilling in Alaska are being received online.And a former economist at the United States Department of the Treasury, Brad Setser, explains how damaging the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank is for the US.Americast is presented by the BBC’s US Special Correspondent Katty Kay, Today host Justin Webb, social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Find out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 3301239480.This episode was made by Rufus Gray and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f98zqx.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 01:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:48:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f98zqx.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Elon Musk And The Twitter Trolls</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f7v6mp.mp3</link>
			<description>Twitter insiders have told the BBC that the company is now much less able to protect users from trolling, state-co-ordinated disinformation and child sexual exploitation. Marianna takes the rest of the Americast team though her BBC Panorama investigation into how one of the world’s most influential social media platforms is being transformed by Elon Musk. And she describes how the Twitter CEO has responded to her online.Tech journalist and host of the ON podcast, Kara Swisher, also joins Americast to talk about how social media companies could be regulated in the future. And in the week of International Women’s Day, one of America’s best-known feminist lawyers, Gloria Allred, discusses how far she thinks women’s rights in the US have come in the decades that she has been practicing law.  Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Find out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 3301239480.This episode was made by Rufus Gray and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f7v6mp.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f7v6mp.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trouble At Fox News</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f6gvk6.mp3</link>
			<description>America's conservative cable TV channel is being sued for airing false 2020 election fraud claims. And court documents suggest that Fox News anchors reported allegations that the vote was “stolen” from Donald Trump even though they knew they were false. The Washington Post’s media critic Erik Wemple joins the team to talk through what's been happening in the case and a bombshell deposition from Fox News owner Rupert Murdoch.When Coronavirus first spread around the world, everyone wanted to know where it came from. Did it jump from animals to humans in a wet market in the Chinese city of Wuhan? Or was it leaked from a virology lab?  No one is entirely sure. But this week not one, but two US intelligence agencies said their best assessment was a lab leak. Stephen Morrison, host of the Coronavirus Crisis Update podcast, gives Americast the latest and explains the political context in Washington. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Find out more about our award winning &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 3301239480.This episode was made by Cat Farnsworth and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f6gvk6.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 02:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:36</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f6gvk6.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America And The War In Ukraine</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f534pn.mp3</link>
			<description>A busy week for President Biden! On the first anniversary of the Russian invasion, he made a surprise trip to Kyiv to meet President Zelensky, pledging to support Ukraine for &quot;as long as it takes&quot;. Biden then gave a speech in Poland to reaffirm America's commitment to Nato. Sarah was on the trip and shares her impressions, and the Americast team also talk to Assistant US Secretary of State Karen Donfried.In Kentucky, a Christian university campus went viral on TikTok after one of its church services turned into a continuous worship session lasting two weeks. We speak to a student about the so-called &quot;Asbury Revival&quot;.And former President Jimmy Carter, 98, has been moved to hospice care. Carter served just one term between 1976 and 1980, but what will his legacy be? Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 3301239480.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk, Cat Farnsworth and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f534pn.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 01:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f534pn.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Aliens Or Air Balloons?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f3phlb.mp3</link>
			<description>As a growing number of flying objects are shot down in US airspace, the Biden administration is still trying to explain just what’s going on...and even fielding the odd question about aliens. Why are Americans so obsessed with extra-terrestrials?Meanwhile, on ground level, many are asking why national media took so long to start covering a major train derailment in Ohio that released hazardous chemicals into the air of a nearby village. In Florida, Governor Ron DeSantis has been talking up his move to ban an advanced high school African-American studies course, possibly laying the framework for his presidential bid. Americast talks to Harvard professor, Evelyn Brooks Higginbotham, who helped devise the course.And in South Carolina, Anthony has been at the launch of Nikki Haley’s presidential campaign. But does she really stand a chance of winning? Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 3301239480.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Cat Farnsworth. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f3phlb.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f3phlb.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Will Joe Biden run to be president (again)?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f27krd.mp3</link>
			<description>What clues were there in President Joe Biden’s State of the Union speech that suggest he's considering a run for a second presidential term? The Americast team take a look at what was in it and how his performance has gone down. The US president is already back on the road, but not all Democrats are keen for him to run again. The activist Norman Solomon explains why some on the left of the party would rather Biden stepped aside.And ahead of Super Bowl Sunday we find out what it takes to put together one of the iconic halftime shows with choreographer Fatima Robinson.Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 3301239480.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk, Alix Pickles and Khadra Salad. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f27krd.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f27krd.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Killing of Tyre Nichols</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f0r6f5.mp3</link>
			<description>After shocking video footage was released of the 29-year-old African-American being beaten to death by five black police officers in Memphis, we ask what might stop police brutality in the US.Sarah and her BBC colleague Chelsea Bailey share insights from their reporting trips to Memphis. And we also ask retired African-American LAPD Sergeant Cheryl Dorsey what should be done differently. With Donald Trump revving up his presidential campaign in South Carolina, the Americast team discusses the two other Republicans who are set to challenge him: Ron DeSantis and Nikki Haley. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480.
Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Rufus Gray. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f0r6f5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0f0r6f5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We Need To Talk About Congressman George Santos</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dz3gr0.mp3</link>
			<description>Lies, lies and more lies.We chat to Republican and newspaper publisher Grant Lally who's known George Santos for years. Why were the concerns he raised about the freshman congressman ignored? And what's behind America’s long-term weight issues? Public health policy advocate, Rhea Farberman, talks obesity. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480.
Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Jonny Hall. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dz3gr0.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dz3gr0.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Abortion in America</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dxmn74.mp3</link>
			<description>As America approaches 50 years since the Supreme Court made abortion access a constitutional right, the Americast team investigates how the country has changed since that ruling was overturned last June.As many states make abortion illegal, other “sanctuary states” are encouraging women to cross state-lines for abortions. Dr Anne Udall, CEO and president of Planned Parenthood in Oregon, tells us how her state and organisation are doing that.From one anniversary to another as America celebrated the birthday of Martin Luther King Jr this week; but alongside the usual commemorations, the unveiling of a new memorial has divided opinion.Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480. Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Michael Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dxmn74.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dxmn74.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden under investigation</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dw1x84.mp3</link>
			<description>A special counsel has been appointed to investigate President Joe Biden after aides found classified documents at his private office and home. The Americast team explains what we know so far, why this spells trouble for the president, and the comparisons between this story and the discovery of hundreds of classified documents at Donald Trump's Mar-a-Lago resort. President Biden has also been trying to get his immigration policy in order as his administration's approach faces criticism from both Republicans and Democrats. Cecilia Muñoz, a former political adviser to President Obama on immigration, helps the team get into the complexities of America's border politics. And we investigate the self-styled true crime ‘investigators’ of TikTok, who are gripped by the case of four students murdered in Idaho. We speak to one of them about the dangers of the public getting involved in criminal cases. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's social media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480. Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374. This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Michael Regaard. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dw1x84.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 01:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dw1x84.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Chaos at the Heart of US Government</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dtjt4j.mp3</link>
			<description>The House of Representatives tries (and so far fails) to elect a Speaker. The US House of Representatives has been in deadlock for days after the new Republican majority failed to elect their leading contender Kevin McCarthy as the new Speaker.  Americast chats to one of the Republicans voting against him, Representative Ralph Norman, about why they think McCarthy isn’t the man for the job. And the team goes over the key findings from the conclusion of the Jan 6 committee’s inquiry with one of the panel members, Democrat Representative Jamie Raskin. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's Ssocial media and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher. Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480. Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Emma Crowe. The assistant editor was Simon Watts. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dtjt4j.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dtjt4j.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is Elon Musk Curing Twitter?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dp82vm.mp3</link>
			<description>The online discussion continues... Since Americast spoke to Dr Anthony Fauci, he has been the subject of Elon Musk tweets. And that’s not all Musk has been up to! The team speaks to a former member of Twitter’s now disbanded Trust and Safety Council about what Musk is doing to online safety.And, as basketball star Brittney Griner is exchanged for notorious arms dealer Viktor Bout, a former White House insider takes us through the growing phenomenon of &quot;hostage diplomacy&quot;.Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation Correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher. Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374. Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Emma Crowe. The assistant editor was Sam Bonham. The senior news editor was Jonathan Aspinwall. Credit: Basketball commentary provided by ESPN Productions Inc.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dp82vm.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 22:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dp82vm.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dr Anthony Fauci Talks: Covid, China and Online Misinformation</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dmzdvk.mp3</link>
			<description>Americast speaks to the doctor who has served seven US presidents about the US coronavirus response, clashes with Donald Trump and his family being targeted by trolls. And the team discusses the president's troubled, son Hunter Biden. Just what is on THAT laptop?Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation Correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher. Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374. Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480. This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Emma Crowe. The assistant editor was Sam Bonham. The senior news editor was Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dmzdvk.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:08</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dmzdvk.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Growing Legalisation of Marijuana in the US</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dl8vkc.mp3</link>
			<description>As more states legalise marijuana, the team explore how America's relationship with the drug has changed. They interview a drug historian and a former adviser to Clinton, Bush Jnr and Obama on drug policy.Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation Correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374 Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk, Alix Pickles, Cordelia Hemming and Paige Neal-Holder. The studio director was Emma Crowe. The assistant editor was Sam Bonham. The senior news editor was Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dl8vkc.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dl8vkc.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is Elon Musk Killing Twitter?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0djdnxb.mp3</link>
			<description>The blue tick, Silicon Valley sackings and Donald Trump. What impact is all this having on America? A former content moderator at the company, who was fired by Musk, helps us answer that question. And while many say Twitter is going off-the-rails, we talk through the US railroads. What’s working for them and what isn’t?Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation Correspondent Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 03301239480.This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Emma Crowe. The assistant editor was Sam Bonham. The senior news editor was Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0djdnxb.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0djdnxb.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Donald Trump launches White House bid</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dgpyym.mp3</link>
			<description>The former US President says he will &quot;save&quot; the US by once again running for the White House. One of his advisers, Jason Miller, takes us through his plans.Americast is presented by North America editor, Sarah Smith, Today host, Justin Webb, the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation Correspondent, Marianna Spring, and North America correspondent, Anthony Zurcher.   Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-63530374 Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments and send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +443301239480.   This episode was made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor was Sam Bonham. The senior news editor was Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dgpyym.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 23:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dgpyym.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump v DeSantis</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dfcqhw.mp3</link>
			<description>As the midterm results continue to come in, the Americast team are back together in Washington DC taking a closer look at the rivalry between Florida Governor Ron DeSantis and former President Donald Trump. And long-time Republican donor for the Trump campaign Dan K Eberhart tells the team why he thinks the party should move in a different direction following the midterms. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today presenter Justin Webb, the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation Correspondent Marianna Spring and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher. Find out more about our ‘undercover voters’ here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-62742687 Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +443301239480 This episode is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dfcqhw.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dfcqhw.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Everything we know about the midterms (part two)</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0df01rh.mp3</link>
			<description>The Americast team are together in the studio in Washington DC for the first time as results in the midterms continue to come in. In their second episode of the night the team look at where the wins are for both the Republicans and the Democrats. They also explore where it leaves Ron DeSantis and Donald Trump as they look ahead to the elections in 2024.Americast is hosted by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher and the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring.Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-62742687.Email americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 00443301239480</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0df01rh.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0df01rh.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Everything we know about the midterms (part one)</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ddx04g.mp3</link>
			<description>The Republicans look set to take control of the House of Representatives, but the battle for control of the Senate is on a knife-edge. Sarah, Anthony and Marianna get together in Washington to talk through what's been happening so far in the midterms and why it all matters. Americast is hosted by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today host Justin Webb, North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher and disinformation correspondent Marianna Spring.  Find out more about our &quot;undercover voters&quot; here: www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-62742687. Email americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to 00443301239480.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ddx04g.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:27</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0ddx04g.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A history of US political violence</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dcj5ns.mp3</link>
			<description>President Biden says there is no place for &quot;political violence in America&quot;. His warning follows an attack on Paul Pelosi, the husband of US House of Representatives Speaker Nancy Pelosi, last week. Within hours of that attack a series of unsubstantiated claims began circulating on social media contradicting official accounts of what had happened. Those misleading claims then went viral after being amplified by new Twitter chief Elon Musk. The Americast team look at how the attack has led to the sharing of disinformation on social media and Justin and Sarah speak to author Josh Zeitz about the history of political violence in the US.Donald Trump Jr. tweets about our 'undercover voters' and Marianna Spring, the BBC's Social Media and Disinformation correspondent responds. And Anthony returns from Virginia to look at Biden’s record ahead of the midterms. 
   
Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today presenter Justin Webb, North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher and Marianna Spring.Find out more about our ‘undercover voters’ here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-62742687 Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +443301239480 This episode is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Michael Regaard. The assistant editor is Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dcj5ns.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:25</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0dcj5ns.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How crime is shaping the US elections</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0db4br1.mp3</link>
			<description>There are less than two weeks to go to the midterms. The Americast team look at why Republicans have seized upon the issue of crime and what the Democrats are trying to do to counter that. Professor of Criminology Charis Kubrin, talks the team through the perceived and real threat of crime in the US and the BBC’s 
Disinformation and Social Media Correspondent Marianna Spring, looks at how our ‘undercover voters’ are being targeted ahead of election day. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today presenter Justin Webb and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher. Find out more about our ‘undercover voters’ here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-62742687 Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +443301239480 This episode is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0db4br1.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 22:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0db4br1.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The US election deniers running for office</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d8hnpb.mp3</link>
			<description>The Americast team look at the threat that election deniers could pose to democracy if they are elected to office in the upcoming US midterms. The team chat to Alabama Secretary of State and Republican John Merrill and the BBC’s Disinformation and Social Media correspondent Marianna Spring examines whether election deniers are reaching voters through their social media accounts. Americast is presented by North America editor Sarah Smith, Today presenter Justin Webb and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher. Find out more about our Americast ‘undercover voters’ here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-62742687Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 330 1239480This episode is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d8hnpb.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d8hnpb.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Alex Jones: The billion dollar conspiracy theorist</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d6w7hr.mp3</link>
			<description>After claiming the 2012 shooting in Sandy Hook was a hoax, it’s a moment of reckoning for America’s conspiracy-theorist-in-chief Alex Jones as he is ordered to pay nearly $1bn in damages to the victim’s family members.Americast explores the huge cultural and social stories that define the increasingly polarised political debate. The team report on a changing country with on-the-ground insights from right across America. Today presenter Justin Webb and North America editor Sarah Smith join North America correspondent Anthony ‘The Zurch’ Zurcher. Each week on Americast, BBC’s disinformation and social media correspondent Marianna Spring will investigate the content that is recommended to US voters on social media.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d6w7hr.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d6w7hr.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How social media changed America</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d4xq3t.mp3</link>
			<description>The Americast team delve into how conspiracy theories evolve online and how misinformation is affecting US politics, with the help of our Undercover Voters and Barack Obama’s former deputy national security adviser Ben Rhodes.US Special Correspondent Katty Kay is back from her trip on Route 66 meeting voters ahead of the midterms. President Joe Biden and Florida’s Republican governor Ron DeSantis have put their political clashes on hold to show a united front over Hurricane Ian. The pair shook hands on the president’s visit to see the devastation left by the storm.This episode is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall. Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 330 1239480</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d4xq3t.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 22:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d4xq3t.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kiss My Midterms</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d3bhr7.mp3</link>
			<description>We’re racing towards the US midterms but don’t worry, the full Americast team is back together to get stuck into the key issues, characters and races, and which party might come out on top. With a little help from Cliff Young, pollster and President of US Public Affairs at Ipsos.And Marianna updates us on what our Undercover Voters are being targeted with.This episode is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall. Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 330 1239480</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d3bhr7.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d3bhr7.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump's heir apparent?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d1spwf.mp3</link>
			<description>There is growing political tension in America over immigration. States such as Florida, Texas and Arizona have sent thousands of migrants to cities like New York, Washington DC and the wealthy Massachusetts island of Martha's Vineyard. Sarah, Justin and Marianna look at how the row is playing out amongst voters and on social media.Americast also profiles Florida’s Governor Ron DeSantis who has been a key figure in the controversial tactic. This episode is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Louisa Lewis. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall. Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 330 1239480</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d1spwf.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d1spwf.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America and the Queen</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d0g6w5.mp3</link>
			<description>How is the US reacting?From Truman to Biden, the Queen met thirteen of the fourteen US presidents who held office during her reign and left a lasting impression on the United States. Justin, Sarah and Marianna look at the reaction to her death and catch up with the BBC’s Chelsea Bailey in Washington DC, who has been speaking to some of the Queen’s biggest fans.And after a five-year legal fight, an Ohio college will pay nearly $37 million to a local bakery that sued the school for libel following a 2016 shoplifting incident involving three Black students. Criminal defence lawyer Professor Jonathan Turley takes us through the case and wider implications of the ruling.  Americast is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Sam Bonham. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.Email Americast@bbc.co.uk with your questions and comments. You can also send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp, to +44 330 1239480.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d0g6w5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0d0g6w5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Erin Brockovich</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cz2t24.mp3</link>
			<description>Legendary environmental activist talks America’s contaminated water supply.The entire population of Jackson, Mississippi lost access to safe running water after excessive rainfall and flooding. But it’s not the first time there’s been issues with the city’s water supply, or the first case of contaminated drinking water in the US. Justin and Sarah speak to environmental activist Erin Brockovich, who won a case over safe drinking water in California, before being portrayed on film by Julia Roberts. They’re also joined by Corey Stern, the lawyer representing 1,600 Jackson residents in their lawsuits against the city and the state. The mayor of Jackson, Chokwe Antar Lumumba, now says “Even when we are not under a boil water notice, it’s not a matter of if these systems will fail, but when these systems will fail. Safe, drinkable, reliable, sustainable and an equitable water treatment facility is a much longer road ahead”.And President Joe Biden and former president Donald Trump have both been in Pennsylvania making some big speeches. The Americast gang break down what they said and how it played out on our undercover voters’ social media feeds.  Americast is made by Phil Marzouk, Alix Pickles and Chris Flynn. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Sam Bonham. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cz2t24.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cz2t24.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mar-a-Legal Trouble</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cxm8l4.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump, some top secret documents and the FBI. Welcome to episode one of the new-look Americast!Classified documents stored at former President's Florida home were likely concealed as part of an effort to obstruct an FBI investigation, says the US Department of Justice officials. Justin, Sarah and the Zurch chat to former FBI special agent Asha Rangappa, about how attempts to retrieve the documents went down and what could happen next. And Marianna introduces our undercover voters… Americast is made by Phil Marzouk and Alix Pickles. The studio director is Emma Crowe. The assistant editor is Sam Bonham. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cxm8l4.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cxm8l4.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Introducing... the New Administration</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cx57wn.mp3</link>
			<description>We're back! With Justin Webb, Sarah Smith, Marianna Spring and (of course) the Zurch. Join us every Wednesday for all the latest news and gossip from America.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cx57wn.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:07:50</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0cx57wn.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Thanks Americasters</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bvvbhw.mp3</link>
			<description>A message to Americasters from the Zurch.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bvvbhw.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 22:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bvvbhw.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Vlad's army</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bqwbdr.mp3</link>
			<description>Biden imposes sanctions on Russia over “beginning of invasion”…  
Former U.S. ambassador to Russia, Michael McFaul joins Emily, Jon and Anthony to discuss whether President Biden could have done anything differently. 
And… former homeland security aide to Donald Trump, Miles Taylor explains why he isn’t surprised classified information was found at the former president's home in Mar-a-Lago. He also addresses the claims that Trump clogged up the White House toilets with flushed paper…  
Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall. The studio director is Emma Crowe</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bqwbdr.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bqwbdr.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A New York?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bpb1fh.mp3</link>
			<description>Prince Andrew has settled the civil sex assault case brought against him in the US by Virginia Giuffre. He’s agreed to make a substantial donation to her charity in support of victims’ rights.Randy Zelin, a New York attorney, joins Emily, Jon and Anthony to discuss what we know and what we will probably never know about the deal.  Americast was made by Alison Gee and Phil Marzouk. The technical director is Emma Crowe and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bpb1fh.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 23:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bpb1fh.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Party in the USA</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bn89x9.mp3</link>
			<description>The American media’s been full of stories about Boris Johnson – so why is the US fascinated with the British prime minister? Mark Landler from the New York Times says there are plenty of similarities with Donald Trump, but also some significant differences.   Mike Pence has made it very clear he disagrees with his former boss: “President Trump is wrong,” he said. “I had no right to overturn the election.” Olivia Troye, who was the vice-president’s homeland security adviser, thinks he’s paving the way to run for president in 2024. With thanks to Opinion Video at The New York Times for permission to use their Jonathan Pie video.Americast was made by Alison Gee and Phil Marzouk. The technical director is Emma Crowe and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bn89x9.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 22:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bn89x9.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What the Truck?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0blm34j.mp3</link>
			<description>As Canadian truckers protest over vaccine regulations, Emily, Jon and Anthony take a look at what it means for the US and whether demonstrations could spread there too. Also, CNN journalists Marshall Cohen and Zachary Cohen talk us through their investigation into the  “fake electors” scheme that tried to overturn the 2020 presidential election result. The January 6 committee has now subpoenaed 14 people in connection with it. And now that Supreme Court Judge Stephen Breyer has announced he’s retiring, President Biden is expected to nominate the first black woman to the court. The Americast team hear why Senator Ted Cruz says he finds this “offensive”.  Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall. The studio director is Emma Crowe.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0blm34j.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 23:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0blm34j.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Crimea river</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bkkn17.mp3</link>
			<description>As the Ukraine crisis escalates, we hear why Kyiv is so important to Moscow.Retired Lt Col Alexander Vindman, who testified before Congress about the Trump-Ukraine scandal, explains why he thinks Biden has a much better understanding of Putin than Trump ever had. Also, the hot mic moment that caught Biden off guard, Anthony tries to take over the podcast with a filibuster, and we answer an A-level student’s question about Mike Pence and a steaming pile of horse poo.  Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bkkn17.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bkkn17.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Playing Chicken in Kyiv</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bjdkzf.mp3</link>
			<description>Joe Biden defends his first year of presidency in a rare press conference, but his comment about a possible Russian invasion of Ukraine is what gets Emily and Jon scratching their heads.  They speak to Elaine Kamarck, a former staffer to Vice-President Al Gore and President Bill Clinton, now with the Brookings Institution. She thinks Biden said more than he should have. Meanwhile, Anthony is travelling with Secretary of State Anthony Blinken to Ukraine, as the US makes a last ditch attempt at finding a diplomatic solution. He explains why there is no way there is going to be a shooting war between Americans and Russians over Ukraine.  And we hear the latest on Donald Trump’s legal troubles: the Supreme Court has allowed the release of his presidential records to the committee investigating the 6 January assault on the Capitol – and it turns out his New York triplex isn’t quite as big as he said. Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bjdkzf.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bjdkzf.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Duke in New York?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bgyw82.mp3</link>
			<description>A New York judge has ruled the civil sex assault case against the Duke of York can go ahead. Emily, Jon and Anthony explain why Prince Andrew’s lawyers argued it should be dismissed and why the court disagreed.The team also listen back to key moments from Emily’s interview with the prince in 2019.And Randy Zelin – a professor and attorney in New York - explains why there’s no good option left for the prince. Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bgyw82.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 05:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:39:11</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bgyw82.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Unhappy anniversary</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bfw9mz.mp3</link>
			<description>A year after the Capitol riot, the people who were there tell us it’s still dividing America today. US Democratic Congresswoman Stacey Plaskett calls it “an attempted coup” and says the country is “in an ideological civil war”.Fiona Hill – a former advisor to Donald Trump – says the way many Republicans have responded reminds her of Soviet disinformation campaigns.And Gabriel Montalvo, from the New York Young Republican Club, explains most people who went to the rally in Washington that day were peaceful. Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The assistant editor is Alison Gee ad the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bfw9mz.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 06:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:54:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bfw9mz.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Let's Talk About Texts, Cheney</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bb9656.mp3</link>
			<description>The committee investigating the assault on the Capitol have seen text messages urging White House staff to get the president to stop the riot. Donald Trump Jr and Fox News hosts were among those who messaged Mark Meadows, Trump’s then chief of staff.  Emily, Jon and Anthony pick over who said what, and when. Governor Gavin Newsom says he plans to copy Texas’s tactics on abortion laws to stop the sale and manufacturing of assault weapons in his state of California. But can his plan actually work? Professor of law Khiara Bridges tells us why she believes his proposal is more than just a PR stunt. And how a florist’s dream to decorate the White House for Christmas came true.  Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bb9656.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 23:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0bb9656.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>‘PS: Santa, please bring ammo’</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b8w6zr.mp3</link>
			<description>“Don’t do it.” The parents of the suspect in a school shooting in Michigan have been charged with involuntary manslaughter. Former NRA lobbyist Richard Feldman tells us why he thinks the Democrats should ditch the anti-gun rhetoric if they genuinely want gun reform. As Republican Congressman Devin Nunes resigns to become CEO of Trump’s new social media firm, journalist Dan Alexander explains why he feels that same company is a frightening proposition for many investors. Will Biden succeed in implementing his federal vaccine mandate? Professor Roger Field tells us whether the president has the law on his side. And we help one of our listeners fall asleep!
 
Today’s Americast was made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The studio director is Emma Crowe, the assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b8w6zr.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b8w6zr.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Foetal position: The end of abortion?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b7mpz3.mp3</link>
			<description>The case that could radically change abortion laws in the US</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b7mpz3.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 22:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b7mpz3.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We Need to Talk About Brandon</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b67bsp.mp3</link>
			<description>Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss who Brandon is and why Americans are chanting his name.Also, three white men have been found guilty of murdering a black jogger, Ahmaud Arbery, in Georgia. We hear testimony from the trial and reaction from his family. And after another high-profile trial, politicians have been offering internships to Kyle Rittenhouse - the young man acquitted of murdering two white men during a protest in 2020.  For some, he’s become an icon for the right to armed self-defence. Americast is produced by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The studio director is Emma Crowe, the assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b67bsp.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 23:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b67bsp.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Proud to be an Americast</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b4wwdg.mp3</link>
			<description>A judge’s “God Bless the USA” ringtone raised eyebrows when it went off in the Rittenhouse murder trial. And as the jury deliberates its verdict, Washington Post reporter Kim Bellware describes how this court case is the most acrimonious she has ever covered. Also, as a defiant Steve Bannon surrenders himself to the FBI, former Republican Congressman Doug Collins tells us why he thinks the Department of Justice has become Biden’s political arm. And Emily shares her memories of an evening with Trump’s former strategist – and a bottle of wine. Americast is made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The studio director is Emma Crowe, the assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b4wwdg.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b4wwdg.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ted Cruz v Big Bird</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b3gvw0.mp3</link>
			<description>Big Bird’s been tweeting about his Covid jab but Senator Cruz isn’t impressed, calling the post “government propaganda for your 5-year-old”.   Also, it’s officially infrastructure week… again. Congressman Andy Levin tells us why he changed his mind and voted for the bill on Friday. And journalist Dan Alexander joins us for a SPAC-tacular explanation of how Donald Trump plans to finance his new social media platform.
 
Today’s Americast was made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The studio director is Emma Crowe, the assistant editor is Alison Gee and the editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b3gvw0.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b3gvw0.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Americast Reunited</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b255p7.mp3</link>
			<description>As Virginia elects a new governor, Emily, Jon and Anthony get back together to ask why things went so wrong for the Democrats and so right for the Republicans.They’re joined by J. Miles Coleman of the University of Virginia Center for Politics, and former Republican congresswoman for Virginia, Barbara Comstock. There are anecdotes from President Biden’s European trip and candy from Air Force One too. Today’s Americast was made by Estelle Doyle and Phil Marzouk. The studio director was Emma Crowe. The assistant editor was Alison Gee and the editor was Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b255p7.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0b255p7.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Fall of Kabul</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09sh8cz.mp3</link>
			<description>Maitlis and Sopes return for an emergency episode to mark the end of America's decades long 'forever war'. We talk to US Airforce veteran Veronica Hoyer to ask if it was all for nothing? And the former US Ambassador to Afghanistan, P. Michael McKinley tells us he is being contacted by former friends and colleagues appealing for rescue as Taliban forces enter Kabul.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Sam Bonham
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09sh8cz.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09sh8cz.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>It's been a blast, Americast!</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09n653t.mp3</link>
			<description>We're signing off for a while, Americasters. Thanks for your company and your support. We'll be back next year to bring you all the build up to the midterm elections.So here's our last episode for now. As someone once said, &quot;Have a good life. We will see you soon&quot;. While you're here, please could you vote for Americast at the British Podcast Awards! www.britishpodcastawards.com/voteThis episode was made by our wonderful producers, Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena. It was mixed beautifully by Emma Crowe. The Editor is Dino Sofos.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09n653t.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 09:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:52:36</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09n653t.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Aliens Ate My Podcast</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09mcc20.mp3</link>
			<description>The truth is out there... or at least it's about to be. 
Former Blink 182 frontman and UFO hunter Tom DeLonge speaks to Emily, Jon and Anthony ahead of the highly anticipated unclassified Pentagon report on UFOs. 
And with the Democrats' Voting Rights bill blocked, we discuss how the fight is far from over for Biden. 
Also, Slate Editor and Americast favourite Dahlia Lithwick tells us everything we need to know about Supreme Court Season and that conservative supermajority. Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09mcc20.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 20:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:47:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09mcc20.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Putin His Foot Down</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09lq0qy.mp3</link>
			<description>We're behind the scenes at the Swiss Chateau where Biden and Putin meet for their first talks – but did they see eye to eye? Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss if the US-Russia relationship can go from rock bottom to recovery. Also, following a testing week for Vice President Harris, we ask her former Communications Director Gil Duran whether we're witnessing a President in the making. And he doesn’t want to go on about it but Sopes had to give up his seat at the pub for a VERY special guest...Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09lq0qy.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 21:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09lq0qy.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Summit Going On</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09l0y02.mp3</link>
			<description>As Joe Biden touches down in the UK for his first foreign trip, the G7 summit of world leaders in Carbis Bay, Jon speaks exclusively to the president’s national security advisor, Jake Sullivan, about how the US will protect the Good Friday agreement and its interests around the world, as well as its rivalry with China and Russia.Back in Washington DC, we hear how one Democratic senator from West Virginia, Joe Manchin, is causing a political impasse that’s paralysing his own party.Studio Director: Nick Jones
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan, Daniel Wittenberg and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09l0y02.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 19:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:50</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09l0y02.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Guess Who's Back?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09kdb73.mp3</link>
			<description>Ben Rhodes, the ex-White House deputy national security adviser and confidante to President Obama, comes on to talk about the global rise of authoritarianism and how American foreign policy helped shape what he calls the “the 9/11 generation.” And there’s a sensational comeback for one of the most influential men in Washington. Not Jon Sopel, another beauty (he’s still in London.) But Donald Trump, is preparing to hold the first post-presidential rally. We hear from POLITICO’s White House insider Anita Kumar about how Trump plans to stay relevant and why he’s always the elephant in the room for Joe Biden.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09kdb73.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09kdb73.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>George Floyd: One Year On</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09jlkv3.mp3</link>
			<description>It’s been a year since the world watched as the life of a black man was extinguished under the knee of a white police officer, sparking months of protests nationally and internationally. It was a moment that demanded change. So has law enforcement learned any lessons?Nick Bryant rejoins Emily and Anthony from Minneapolis as we ask former White House special advisor and Americast regular, Ron Christie, whether issues of race are uniting or dividing the United States. And we talk through the George Floyd Justice in Policing Act with Lynda Williams, the country’s most senior black police executive.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09jlkv3.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 20:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09jlkv3.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>BudPfizer</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09j2d1v.mp3</link>
			<description>The BBC’s legendary New York correspondent Nick Bryant swaps in for Sopes. He comes carrying a cocktail of stories, including how some states are using boozy incentives to boost their vaccination campaign. And as the President hardens his position on the Israel-Palestine conflict, we ask veteran pollster John Zogby why it puts Biden in a bind with his party. And hold on to your sequins! The Eurovision Song Contest is coming to the United States… and it’s going to get Political. We talk to one of its producers and America’s most fanatical Eurovision lover.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Daniel Wittenburg
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09j2d1v.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 22:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09j2d1v.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden and his trillion dollar legislative agenda</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3</link>
			<description>Following a long and bitter public spat, House Republicans have voted to remove their number three, Liz Cheney, from leadership - Emily, Jon and Anthony reflect on the massive moment. We go inside the room where it happened with Congressman Chris Stewart who explains why he decided to vote to remove Cheney. And, while the GOP is taking aim at itself, President Biden met with leaders of the House and Senate to discuss his trillion dollar legislative agenda.

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 10:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:11:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Republicans vote to remove Liz Cheney</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3</link>
			<description>Following a long and bitter public spat, House Republicans have voted to remove their number three, Liz Cheney, from leadership - Emily, Jon and Anthony reflect on the massive moment. We go inside the room where it happened with Congressman Chris Stewart who explains why he decided to vote to remove Cheney. And, while the GOP is taking aim at itself, President Biden met with leaders of the House and Senate to discuss his trillion dollar legislative agenda.

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 10:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cheney Reaction</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3</link>
			<description>Following a long and bitter public spat, House Republicans have voted to remove their number three, Liz Cheney, from leadership - Emily, Jon and Anthony reflect on the massive moment. We go inside the room where it happened with Congressman Chris Stewart who explains why he decided to vote to remove Cheney. And, while the GOP is taking aim at itself, President Biden met with leaders of the House and Senate to discuss his trillion dollar legislative agenda.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 09:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09hg3s4.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blocked</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09gqx9w.mp3</link>
			<description>Facebook's Trump ban is upheld for six more months. Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss the decision and what Nick Clegg has to do with it. And it's war for the Republicans as establishment figures face off against loyal Trump supporters in a battle for who controls the party - former Republican congressman Denver Riggleman joins us to discuss why Trump adversaries like him, Liz Cheney and Mitt Romney are being turned on by their own.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Caitlin Hanrahan and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09gqx9w.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09gqx9w.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What has President Biden achieved in 100 days? </title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09g6h1c.mp3</link>
			<description>What has President Biden achieved in 100 days?

Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss President Biden’s first 100 days in office and historic first address in Congress. Jim Messina who was Deputy Chief of Staff to Obama joins the team to mull over what the President has achieved, whether he’s bitten off more than he can chew and whether the Biden he knows will be running for re-election.

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09g6h1c.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09g6h1c.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Not Biden his time</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09g6h1c.mp3</link>
			<description>What has President Biden achieved in 100 days?Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss President Biden’s first 100 days in office and historic first address in Congress. Jim Messina who was Deputy Chief of Staff to Obama joins the team to mull over what the President has achieved, whether he’s bitten off more than he can chew and whether the Biden he knows will be running for re-election.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09g6h1c.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 20:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09g6h1c.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Guilty</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09f8nyy.mp3</link>
			<description>After just ten hours of deliberation, a jury finds Derek Chauvin guilty of the murder of George Floyd. Emily and Jon reflect on what this huge moment means. Correspondent Larry Madowo joins us from the crowded street where George Floyd was murdered and Ron Christie replaces his political hat with his legal hat to tackle your emergency Americanswers.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09f8nyy.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 03:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09f8nyy.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Anger and Protests in Minneapolis</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09dpchq.mp3</link>
			<description>As the Chauvin trial enters its third week in Minneapolis, the city’s streets saw the tragic death of Daunte Wright at the hands of the police. Jon speaks to BBC correspondent Larry Madowo for the latest from the city the world is watching. And we go into the Americast archives and take you back to the week which changed America - when George Floyd lost his life and protests broke out around the world. Studio Manager: Russell Newlove
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09dpchq.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 19:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:36</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09dpchq.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>GaetzGate</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09d0zl5.mp3</link>
			<description>Trump finally breaks his silence over the alleged sex crimes of Congressman Gaetz. Emily, Jon and Anthony get the inside track on Gaetz-Gate from one of the journalists who broke the story, New York Times correspondent Nicholas Fandos. Coca Cola and other companies have taken a stand against Georgia's new voting law and North America correspondent Larry Madowo explains how the so-called blue wall of silence is breaking at the George Floyd trial.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09d0zl5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 20:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:45:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09d0zl5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Trial of Derek Chauvin</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09cdnt5.mp3</link>
			<description>Biden builds bridges and Trump crashes weddings.

As the trial of Derek Chauvin is finally underway, Americast regular, Ron Christie, shares his thoughts on what the outcome could mean for the future of America. Congressman Garamendi joins us from his Californian ranch to explain why Biden’s big bill on infrastructure matters. America puts aside partisanship for March Madness - Englishman in New York Roger Bennett explains why the sporting tournament is like the World Cup meets Eurovision.

And ever wondered what a Donald Trump wedding speech would sound like? 

Studio Manager: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09cdnt5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 18:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:16:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09cdnt5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>March Madness</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09cdnt5.mp3</link>
			<description>Biden builds bridges and Trump crashes weddings.As the trial of Derek Chauvin is finally underway, Americast regular, Ron Christie, shares his thoughts on what the outcome could mean for the future of America. Congressman Garamendi joins us from his Californian ranch to explain why Biden’s big bill on infrastructure matters. America puts aside partisanship for March Madness - Englishman in New York Roger Bennett explains why the sporting tournament is like the World Cup meets Eurovision.And ever wondered what a Donald Trump wedding speech would sound like? Studio Manager: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09cdnt5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 18:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09cdnt5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bolder After Boulder?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09bw6nv.mp3</link>
			<description>Two familiar issues are already threatening to cause a major political headache for President Biden’s administration: gun laws and the southern border. We speak to gun control lobbyist Robyn Thomas from the Gifford Law Centre, and Florence Chamberlin, an El Paso based immigration attorney with the Kids in Need of Defense programme. And Joe Biden holds his first press conference as President, so how did he do? Jon, Emily and Anthony look at how the new President differed tonally from his predecessor, if not in content. AndStudio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Natalie Ktena, Frankie Tobi, Caitlin Hanrahan
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09bw6nv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:49:25</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09bw6nv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>O’Mericast</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09b181y.mp3</link>
			<description>Happy St Patrick’s Day! We Americanswer just how much of an influence the Irish have on American politics. And as Biden embarks on his stimulus victory tour, the team are joined by Obama’s National Economic Council director Larry Summers to discuss why the American Rescue Plan may have gone too far. Also, the Cuomo crisis continues and the Governor’s former employee Stephanie Stark shares her research on how voters respond to allegations of sexual assault at the polls. And why are Trump supporters sceptical about taking the vaccine?Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09b181y.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 22:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:52:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p09b181y.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>AmeriKerryAnswer</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p099bdn2.mp3</link>
			<description>The U.S. Special Presidential Envoy for Climate, John Kerry, has landed in London – and makes a podcast pitstop to Americanswer your questions. And as the George Floyd murder trial begins, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss America’s reckoning with race. Joined by Black Votes Matter co-founder LaTosha Brown and Editor-at-large of The 19th, Errin Haines, they discuss how the Meghan and Harry interview proves the monarchy is not immune from that reckoning and why the black vote is being targeted by a new bill in Georgia.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p099bdn2.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 01:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p099bdn2.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Star Mangled Banner</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p098f64z.mp3</link>
			<description>Trump’s back – but did his CPAC appearance hit the right notes? Emily, Jon and Anthony talk to Ron Christie about whether the former president’s speech shows he is on his way to 2024 candidacy. Also, we go inside the Orlando convention to hear from Trump’s most conservative supporters. And finally, has Biden been tough enough on Saudi Arabia for the murder of Jamal Khashoggi?Studio Director: Michael Regaard
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p098f64z.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 23:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p098f64z.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Status Cuomo</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097z0fz.mp3</link>
			<description>Political big beast Andrew Cuomo has landed himself in hot water with a nursing home scandal. As the NY Governor faces calls for his impeachment, Emily, Jon and Anthony speak to New York Assemblyman Ron Kim who alleges Cuomo threatened him for publicly criticising him. And as the US reaches a sobering pandemic milestone, how is President Biden faring in his aim to become the healer-in-chief? And remember former President Trump? He is finally ordered to hand over those long-awaited tax returns...

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097z0fz.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 07:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097z0fz.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Status Cuomo</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097z0fz.mp3</link>
			<description>Political big beast Andrew Cuomo has landed himself in hot water with a nursing home scandal. As the NY Governor faces calls for his impeachment, Emily, Jon and Anthony speak to New York Assemblyman Ron Kim who alleges Cuomo threatened him for publicly criticising him. And as the US reaches a sobering pandemic milestone, how is President Biden faring in his aim to become the healer-in-chief? And remember former President Trump? He is finally ordered to hand over those long-awaited tax returns...Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097z0fz.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 23:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097z0fz.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Caribbean Cruz</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097k15v.mp3</link>
			<description>While Texas battles devastating winter weather, Ted Cruz’s badly timed trip to Mexico leaves him at the centre of a political storm – Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss the power blackouts and the political fallout. Also, Americast’s favourite Texan Ryan returns to tell us how the sub-freezing temperatures have affected locals like him. And State House Representative Tony Tinderholt on what needs to be done to safeguard Texas in future.

Studio Director: Michael Regaard
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097k15v.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097k15v.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Caribbean Cruz</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097k15v.mp3</link>
			<description>While Texas battles devastating winter weather, Ted Cruz’s badly timed trip to Mexico leaves him at the centre of a political storm – Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss the power blackouts and the political fallout. Also, Americast’s favourite Texan Ryan returns to tell us how the sub-freezing temperatures have affected locals like him. And State House Representative Tony Tinderholt on what needs to be done to safeguard Texas in future.Studio Director: Michael Regaard
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097k15v.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 21:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p097k15v.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mitch Ado About Nothing</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096yhfl.mp3</link>
			<description>The Senate acquits Trump... again.

Emily, Jon and Anthony love nothing more than spending a cold Saturday night recording an Emergency Americast about the end of the Donald Trump impeachment trial. The 57-43 tally falls short of the two-thirds vote needed to convict the former President on a charge of inciting the Capitol riot. But will this be the last time Trump is put on trial? 

Studio Director: Holly Palmer
Assistant Editor: Sam Bonham
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096yhfl.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:13:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096yhfl.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mitch Ado About Nothing</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096yhfl.mp3</link>
			<description>The Senate acquits Trump... again.Emily, Jon and Anthony love nothing more than spending a cold Saturday night recording an Emergency Americast about the end of the Donald Trump impeachment trial. The 57-43 tally falls short of the two-thirds vote needed to convict the former President on a charge of inciting the Capitol riot. But will this be the last time Trump is put on trial? Studio Director: Holly Palmer
Assistant Editor: Sam Bonham
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096yhfl.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 01:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096yhfl.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Fight Like Hell!</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096w877.mp3</link>
			<description>The impeachment trial heats up.The Democrats have finished laying out their arguments against Donald Trump in the impeachment trial by looking at the insurrectionists themselves. So did Trump’s language incite them to violence? We speak to the man who warned against the former President’s use of threats following the election: Gabriel Sterling. The Georgia elections official speaks to Emily and Jon about his now viral intervention. And while the TV cameras have focused on the impeachment trial, President Biden has been addressing the pandemic, working up the country’s vaccination programme.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096w877.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 22:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096w877.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Americat</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096n32t.mp3</link>
			<description>From the viral court-zoom cat, to day two of Trump’s impeachment trial – it’s been a day of high legal drama in the USA.

Emily, Jon and Anthony talk us through the biggest moments in the Senate so far – including never-before-seen footage of the Capitol riots. Why is Donald Trump angry at his own legal team? And can Republicans be convinced to convict the former president?

Producers: Frankie Tobi, Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Sam Bonham
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096n32t.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 08:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:07</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096n32t.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Americat</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096n32t.mp3</link>
			<description>From the viral court-zoom cat, to day two of Trump’s impeachment trial – it’s been a day of high legal drama in the USA.Emily, Jon and Anthony talk us through the biggest moments in the Senate so far – including never-before-seen footage of the Capitol riots. Why is Donald Trump angry at his own legal team? And can Republicans be convinced to convict the former president?Producers: Frankie Tobi, Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Sam Bonham
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096n32t.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 03:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p096n32t.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump’s Bit Parts</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0966lrx.mp3</link>
			<description>Trump may have quit the Screen Actors Guild, but his presence in the GOP looms large as ally Marjorie Taylor Greene gets party support. Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss the Congresswoman, conspiracy theories and what we can make of her apology to Congress. Also, Republican Representative Robert Aderholt explains why he voted not to certify President Biden’s victory. And we bring you the Americast half-time show, a performance to rival this weekend’s Super Bowl!Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Natalie Ktena, Frankie Tobi
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0966lrx.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:52:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0966lrx.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden and climate change</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3</link>
			<description>Is the House GOP leader back to backing Trump? Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss why Kevin McCarthy took a trip to Mar-a-Lago to visit the former president. Meanwhile, the Republican party divide deepens as Congressman Matt Gaetz rallies against his GOP colleague in Wyoming. And we bring you a bumper Americanswer with an A-Level politics class takeover.

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We Need to Talk about Kevin</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3</link>
			<description>Is the House GOP leader back to backing Trump? Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss why Kevin McCarthy took a trip to Mar-a-Lago to visit the former president. Meanwhile, the Republican party divide deepens as Congressman Matt Gaetz rallies against his GOP colleague in Wyoming. And we bring you a bumper Americanswer with an A-Level politics class takeover.

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:16:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We Need to Talk about Kevin</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3</link>
			<description>Is the House GOP leader back to backing Trump? Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss why Kevin McCarthy took a trip to Mar-a-Lago to visit the former president. Meanwhile, the Republican party divide deepens as Congressman Matt Gaetz rallies against his GOP colleague in Wyoming. And we bring you a bumper Americanswer with an A-Level politics class takeover.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 19:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p095k5pw.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Who Let The Dogs Out?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0953nsy.mp3</link>
			<description>President Biden says Donald Trump's impeachment trial &quot;has to happen&quot;. House impeachment managers deliver the article of impeachment against Donald Trump to the Senate, formally triggering a trial. Meanwhile, President Biden continues to reverse many of the executive orders from the Trump era while emphasising his message of unity. Oh, and Rudy Giuliani is being sued by the Dominion voting machine firm for $1.3bn (£950m).Emily, Jon and Anthony are joined by Slate's Dahlia Lithwick.Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0953nsy.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 04:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:44:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0953nsy.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Americast's Got Talent with Piers Morgan</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094s4pt.mp3</link>
			<description>Piers Morgan tells us an incredible story about how Donald Trump was called on Air Force One last year by a prankster posing as... Piers Morgan.Piers also helps Emily and Jon find a Frank Sinatra impersonator to perform 'His Way', written by Americaster, Trevor Knight. Studio Director: Michael Regaard
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094s4pt.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 02:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094s4pt.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>It’s Biden Time</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094n2fq.mp3</link>
			<description>The new president begins dismantling Trump’s legacy... After all the festivities, Biden promises to get straight to work, signing executive orders and taking other actions that don’t require congressional approval. And at Americaster Francis’ request, we take some time to assessing Donald Trump’s achievements in the past 4 years. Also, what was the rationale behind Trump’s ‘generous’ letter to Biden?

Studio Manager: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094n2fq.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 08:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094n2fq.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>It’s Biden Time</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094n2fq.mp3</link>
			<description>The new president begins dismantling Trump’s legacy... After all the festivities, Biden promises to get straight to work, signing executive orders and taking other actions that don’t require congressional approval. And at Americaster Francis’ request, we take some time to assessing Donald Trump’s achievements in the past 4 years. Also, what was the rationale behind Trump’s ‘generous’ letter to Biden?Studio Manager: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094n2fq.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 06:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094n2fq.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>DT Flown Home</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094hnvy.mp3</link>
			<description>On his final day in office, President Trump gives his farewell address and gets ready to head back to Florida. And on the eve of their inauguration, Joe Biden and Kamala Harris hold a Covid memorial service to remember those who have lost their lives.

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094hnvy.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 12:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094hnvy.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>DT Flown Home</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094hnvy.mp3</link>
			<description>On his final day in office, President Trump gives his farewell address and gets ready to head back to Florida. And on the eve of their inauguration, Joe Biden and Kamala Harris hold a Covid memorial service to remember those who have lost their lives.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094hnvy.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 04:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094hnvy.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Donald and the Giant Impeach</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094209m.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump has become the only US president to have been impeached by the House of Representatives for a second time. Emily, Jon and Anthony speak to Republican Representative French Hill on why he believes this was the wrong action to take, and Democratic Senator Sheldon Whitehouse on what will happen next when this goes to trial in the Senate. This episode also contains harrowing details about Lisa Montgomery, the woman who was executed this week in Indiana. Not just about her execution - but our reporter, Hilary Andersson, also tells us about the awful crime she committed and abuse she suffered in her life. If you're affected by anything you’ve heard and require support or advice, you can contact the BBC Action Line - bbc.co.uk/actionlineStudio Director: Michael Regaard
Producers: Frankie Tobi, Natalie Ktena, Ben Weisz
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094209m.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:46:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p094209m.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>United State of Emergency</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p093j23k.mp3</link>
			<description>Emily Maitlis and Jon Sopel follow the the US election.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p093j23k.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p093j23k.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>United State of Emergency</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p093j23k.mp3</link>
			<description>Posting for the first time since his Twitter account was suspended for 12 hours, President Trump criticised the violent protests that saw five people lose their lives, and called for an ‘orderly transition of power’. But, what’s behind this change in rhetoric? Emily, Jon and Anthony talk through this and all the fallout from Wednesday’s dramatic events.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi and Ben Weisz
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p093j23k.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 21:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:09</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p093j23k.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Coup-nited States of America</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0939jdx.mp3</link>
			<description>Violent scenes of Trump supporters storming the US Capitol have shocked the world. On the day that Joe Biden’s electoral win was supposed to be confirmed, and the Georgia run-offs confirmed a Democratic majority in the Senate, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss the day’s extraordinary events.Studio Director: Emma Crowe 
Producer: Frankie Tobi
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0939jdx.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 04:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:48:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0939jdx.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>'Find me more votes'</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0931n0n.mp3</link>
			<description>Georgia takes centre stage as Trump’s phone call to its Secretary of State is leaked – Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss whether his latest attempt to cling to power is illegal. And in a big week for the Senate, could the results of the election be overturned?

Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0931n0n.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 20:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:17:36</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0931n0n.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>'Find me more votes'</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0931n0n.mp3</link>
			<description>Georgia takes centre stage as Trump’s phone call to its Secretary of State is leaked – Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss whether his latest attempt to cling to power is illegal. And in a big week for the Senate, could the results of the election be overturned?Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0931n0n.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0931n0n.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Americast Advent Calendar</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0927zvh.mp3</link>
			<description>Maitlis, Sopel and Anthony take a look back at 2020 - an extraordinary year, that featured a global pandemic, civil unrest sparked by the killing of an African American man, and the small matter or a presidential election.  But did any of their analysis prove to be right?? Merry Christmas and Happy New Year, Americasters! We'll be back next year. Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofosamericast@bbc.co.uk</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0927zvh.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 09:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>01:01:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0927zvh.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>From Russia with Bugs</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p091x3r8.mp3</link>
			<description>A large-scale and sophisticated hack targeting multiple US departments has been confirmed, with fingers being pointed at the Russian government. Our Moscow Correspondent Steve Rosenberg tells us why Russia say the claims are baseless, and, what the new era of US-Russian relations might look like under President-Elect Joe Biden. And big news... Sopes is back on home turf!Producers: Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p091x3r8.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 20:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p091x3r8.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump carries out federal executions in last days of his Precidency</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</link>
			<description>As covid cases continue to rise, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss how Biden will fight the pandemic. Also, how Texas is making a bid to overturn Biden’s win. And why is Trump carrying out federal executions in the dying days of his Presidency?

Studio Direction: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 12:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:11:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Texas makes a bid to overturn Biden's win</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</link>
			<description>As covid cases continue to rise, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss how Biden will fight the pandemic. Also, how Texas is making a bid to overturn Biden’s win. And why is Trump carrying out federal executions in the dying days of his Presidency?

Studio Direction: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 12:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:07:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How will Biden fight the Pandemic?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</link>
			<description>As covid cases continue to rise, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss how Biden will fight the pandemic. Also, how Texas is making a bid to overturn Biden’s win. And why is Trump carrying out federal executions in the dying days of his Presidency?

Studio Direction: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 12:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:10:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Eau d'Americast</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</link>
			<description>As covid cases continue to rise, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss how Biden will fight the pandemic. Also, how Texas is making a bid to overturn Biden’s win. And why is Trump carrying out federal executions in the dying days of his Presidency?Studio Direction: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Frankie Tobi and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 04:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0916dhv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>All Vaxxed Up</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p090jsn5.mp3</link>
			<description>As Biden asks people to ‘mask’ for his first 100 days, Emily, Jon and Anthony look at his policies and whether he will be a reassuring or radical President. Also, why is Anthony Fauci apologising to the UK? Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Natalie Ktena and Frankie Tobi
Lead Producer: Harriet Noble
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p090jsn5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 20:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p090jsn5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The kids’ table</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08zvdp5.mp3</link>
			<description>As Trump confirms he will leave the White House, Emily Jon and Anthony compare his testy press conference with the Bidens’ Thanksgiving message. Also, rumoured cabinet pick Heidi Heitkamp discusses Democrats and the rural vote. And we Americ-answer – is Trump going to pardon himself?Studio Director: Michael Regaard
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08zvdp5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 21:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08zvdp5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>'I concede NOTHING!!!!!'</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08zj5ql.mp3</link>
			<description>With the transition now formally underway, Jon, Emily and Anthony discuss whether a Trump tweet is the closest we will get to a concession speech. Also, why Biden’s diverse cabinet picks look like an Obama third term. And, could Trump reveal classified information post-presidency?Studio director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08zj5ql.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 19:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08zj5ql.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Democracy Dyes in Darkness</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08z44w4.mp3</link>
			<description>As Biden gets on with the business of transition, Jon, Emily and Anthony discuss the Trump campaign’s latest outlandish press conference – and how Rudy Giuliani’s hair-dye stole the scene. Also, how is the White House press pack reacting to the White House’s war on the media? And is Fox News abandoning President Trump? Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena 
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08z44w4.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 20:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08z44w4.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Barack Obama's Big Book</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08yx6r3.mp3</link>
			<description>Fresh from his surprise cameo in The Crown, Jon joins Emily and Anthony to discuss all the latest on the transition in limbo. Also, historian David Olusoga joins us to discuss Barack Obama's book and his exclusive UK interview with the 44th president. And how Trump’s election message could be an own goal in the battleground Georgia senate race.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalie Ktena and Sej Asar
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08yx6r3.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 20:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08yx6r3.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Orange is the new black</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08yf981.mp3</link>
			<description>As Biden increases his electoral college tally, Emily, Jon and Anthony go behind-the-scenes in the Trump camp with New York Magazine correspondent Olivia Nuzzi. Also, is Trump frightened of  prison? And we speak to former US Ambassador to the EU, Anthony Gardner, about whether Biden and Boris will be good for the UK-US relationship.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Natalie Ktena and Harriet Noble
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08yf981.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 23:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08yf981.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Americast Total Landscaping</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08y168c.mp3</link>
			<description>It's our election post-mortem. As Biden’s transition team steps up, Emily, Jon and Anthony are joined by red and blue strategists for a forensic look at the election. Also, is Trump’s firing of his Defence Secretary an act of revenge? And we Americ-answer who can be considered for President-Elect Biden’s cabinet.A big shoutout to BBC Builders Merchants Ltd in Dewsbury for being good sports.Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08y168c.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 19:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08y168c.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>President-elect Biden &amp;amp; Resident Trump</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xr2fv.mp3</link>
			<description>Joe Biden has won the race to become the next US president. And Donald Trump is on his way back from the golf course. Maitlis, Sopes and The Zurch discuss an extraordinary 24 hours in Washington. Studio Director: Nick Jones
Producer: Morgan Gisholt Minard
Assistant Editor: Emma Close 
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xr2fv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 21:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xr2fv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Big Boy Pants</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xnd3j.mp3</link>
			<description>As the counting continues, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss how a fresh Biden lead may have broken the Presidential stalemate. Reporter Julia Terruso takes us inside the Pennsylvania vote centre. And could there be a dark endgame for Trump’s legal suits? Also we Americanswer – if Trump loses, can he run again in 2024?Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalie Ktena and Caitlin Hanrahan
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xnd3j.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 22:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xnd3j.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Voice Note from Sopes’ Apartment</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xlss3.mp3</link>
			<description>Things are moving so quickly, but it looks like the presidency is slipping away from Donald Trump. We'll be recording a proper episode with the whole gang later. Until then, here's a quick update from Sopes. It's a bit like Letter from America, but recorded on an iPhone in his flat, after very little sleep.Producer: Natalie Ktena 
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xlss3.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 15:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:06:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xlss3.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Act II</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xd06s.mp3</link>
			<description>As Donald Trump prematurely declares victory, Emily, Jon, Anthony and Ron Christie discuss which paths to the White House are still in play.Also, will the swing states be decided in the Supreme Court? And our Texan Trump supporter Ryan returns to the podcast.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Natalie Ktena, Morgan Gisholt Minard, Caitlin Hanrahan
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xd06s.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 18:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xd06s.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hot Takes</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xbg2n.mp3</link>
			<description>What a night! Emily, Jon, Anthony and Nick Bryant get together to bring you the story of election night so far. We don’t have a winner, and it could be a long time until we do. We recorded this at midnight EST / 5am GMT.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Morgan Gisholt Minard, Caitlin Hanrahan 
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xbg2n.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 07:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08xbg2n.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Boss v The King of Europe</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08wygz1.mp3</link>
			<description>As the candidates roll out the red carpet, Emily, Jon and Anthony explain how Lil Wayne, Bruce Springsteen and Nigel Farage are attempting to bring out the votes. Campaign insiders Guy Cecil and Jenna Ellis make their final pitches for their candidate to be President. And the team bring you Americast’s ultimate guide to election night.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08wygz1.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 19:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:15</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08wygz1.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Workin’ our asses off</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08wqmf8.mp3</link>
			<description>With less than a week until election day, Jon, Emily and Anthony consider the candidates’ final pitches to the American people. BBC News at Ten's Clive Myrie joins us from Arizona where he’s been reporting on coronavirus and race. And remember Heather, our undecided voter who we heard from after the first debate? She’s back, and she’s no longer undecided…Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalie Ktena and Morgan Gisholt Minard
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08wqmf8.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 20:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:40:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08wqmf8.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Muted</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08w652f.mp3</link>
			<description>With record early voter turnout, Emily, Jon and Anthony discuss whether the candidates’ calm and focused performances will make a difference at the ballot. Also, one Texan tells us whether the night’s events have made him question his early vote. And how former President Barack Obama is trying to get inside Trump’s head.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08w652f.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 19:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:38:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08w652f.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hunter Biden's Laptop</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08vywst.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump thinks the media should be talking about the content of Joe Biden’s son Hunter’s old laptop; we explain why they’re not.  Plus with polls favouring Joe Biden, Emily, Jon and Anthony look at how Trump could beat the odds to a second term in the White House. And as the Democrats try to flip the Senate, we find out how sexting and the price of soybeans could shape the race. Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08vywst.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 19:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08vywst.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Crazy Uncle and Sleepy Joe</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08vj89h.mp3</link>
			<description>As Donald Trump and Joe Biden field voter questions at the same time on different TV networks, Emily, Jon and Anthony compare their performances. And we &quot;Americanswer&quot; why swing states are so swingy.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalies Ktena and Morgan Gisholt Minard
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08vj89h.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 20:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:07</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08vj89h.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Macho Macho Man?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08v6fbx.mp3</link>
			<description>Just over a week after leaving hospital, President Trump returned to the campaign trail with a big rally in Florida. It's a crucial state, and in this episode we explain why it might decide the election, and hear from the voters who could swing it.Studio director: Wayne Moses
Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalie Ktena and Morgan Gisholt Minard
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08v6fbx.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 23:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:41:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08v6fbx.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Debate Buzz</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08trmgv.mp3</link>
			<description>Jon, Emily and Anthony talk us through the flies, the highs and lows of the VP debate in Utah. And two undecided voters tell us if the candidates' sparring on race helped them make their pick.Studio director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08trmgv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08trmgv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump On Steroids</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08tgpls.mp3</link>
			<description>Emily, Jon and Anthony describe the scene as Donald Trump leaves hospital in a helicopter, takes off his mask and returns to the White House.Studio Director: Matt Howells
Producer: Harriet Noble
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08tgpls.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 02:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08tgpls.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Blood and Oxygen</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08tc0by.mp3</link>
			<description>The president has been admitted to hospital. But how much confidence can we have in what we’re being told about his condition after evasive comments from President Trump's doctor?Studio Manager: Jack Graysmark
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08tc0by.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 17:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08tc0by.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The president tests positive</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08t7194.mp3</link>
			<description>The president and his wife have tested positive for Covid. What does this mean for the election? Emily, Jon and Anthony gather for an emergency Americast.Producer: Harriet Noble
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08t7194.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08t7194.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>“Will you shut up man?”</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08szt8q.mp3</link>
			<description>After a tempestuous night in Cleveland we talk through the biggest moments of the first presidential debate.  And we hear from undecided voters about whether the fiery exchanges swayed them at all. Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalie Ktena and Morgan Gisholt Minard 
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08szt8q.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 19:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08szt8q.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Supreme decisions</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08sbttl.mp3</link>
			<description>The death of the US Supreme Court Justice, Ruth Bader Ginsburg, is still dominating the conversation in Washington. Jon and Emily look at who could replace her and when. Also on the podcast, Democratic rising star Jamaal Bowman explains how he’ll challenge the status quo in Washington. And Californian Republican candidate Erin Cruz discusses why she won’t dismiss the QAnon conspiracy theorists.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi, Natalie Ktena and Harriet Noble
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08sbttl.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 20:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:34:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08sbttl.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RIP RBG</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08s02v5.mp3</link>
			<description>Ruth Bader Ginsburg, US Supreme Court Justice and icon of liberal America, has died at the age of 87. We sound the emergency klaxon and gather to discuss how she became a cult figure, and what her passing might mean for the election.Studio director: Michael Campbell
Producers: Harriet Noble, Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Sam Bonham, Emma Close</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08s02v5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08s02v5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Demon Sperm</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08m6fl2.mp3</link>
			<description>President Trump is again backing hydroxychloroquine, an antimalarial drug with no proven effectiveness against Covid-19, but with the backing of a quack doctor who believes that women have sex with demons in their dreams. We also discuss why the Senate race is so fascinating this year, and how baseball is a microcosm of America. Studio director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Harriet Noble
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08m6fl2.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:40</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08m6fl2.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>You’ve Got Mail</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08mvwx5.mp3</link>
			<description>With 90 days to go until the election, how will Americans cast their ballots in the middle of a pandemic? We hear from ProPublica’s Jessica Huseman on why postal-voting is proving to be a controversial topic. And Jon and Anthony speak to Cassie Smedile, Deputy Communications Director for the Republican National Committee, about what message Donald Trump does want to send. Studio Manager: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi, Natalie Ktena, Harriet Noble
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08mvwx5.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:36:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08mvwx5.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kamala Harris makes history</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08nd5nl.mp3</link>
			<description>After months of speculation, Joe Biden has chosen California Senator Kamala Harris as his pick for VP. The Americast team assembles for an emergency episode, and Mayor of San Francisco and friend of Harris, London Breed, tells us why she thinks Biden made the right pick.Studio director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Morgan Gisholt Minard
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08nd5nl.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08nd5nl.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Unconventional Convention</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08p3bkv.mp3</link>
			<description>Anthony and Jon discuss the unconventional Democratic National Convention with the Reverend Leah Daughtry, CEO of the DNC in 2008 and 2016. And as the US Postal Service boss suspends new policies that were decried as an attempt to sabotage the election, we try to get to the bottom of what is actually going on.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producer: Harriet Noble 
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08p3bkv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:40</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08p3bkv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Run-DNC</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08p9m5l.mp3</link>
			<description>Joe Biden closed the Democratic National Convention calling for unity, telling voters ‘character and decency’ would be on the ballot come November. Jon, Anthony and Producer Morgan talk us through the key moments from the Dems this week - from Kamala Harris’ historic nomination, to Barack Obama’s unprecedented attack on Donald Trump.Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Frankie Tobi, Harriet Noble
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08p9m5l.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08p9m5l.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Saving the American Dream?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08pyjtv.mp3</link>
			<description>The Republican National Convention this year was set against the backdrop of the Coronavirus pandemic, and protests over the shooting of a black man by a police officer in Wisconsin. So how did Donald Trump make his case for another four more years in office? Emily and Jon are joined by Republican strategist Ron Christie to get stuck into the key moments from the week. Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Natalie Ktena, Frankie Tobi
Assistant Editor: Emma Close</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08pyjtv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08pyjtv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Make America Safe Again</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qbvqb.mp3</link>
			<description>Who do Americans trust to make them feel safer, and what difference could that make to November’s vote? With just over two months to go, Jon, Emily and Anthony discuss how much law and order will be an election issue. And why do so few Americans vote?Studio Director: Michael Regaard
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qbvqb.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:42</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qbvqb.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sir Kim Darroch</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qx9mm.mp3</link>
			<description>In an exclusive interview for BBC Newsnight, Maitlis speaks with the former UK ambassador to the US, Sir Kim Darroch, about the cables that led to his resignation. The ambassador quit last year after it emerged he described the US President's government as &quot;dysfunctional&quot;, &quot;inept&quot; and &quot;divided&quot; in the private letters.Producer: Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qx9mm.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:42</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qx9mm.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Military Disservice</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qzzzf.mp3</link>
			<description>Following allegations that Trump made derogatory comments against the military, Jon, Emily and Anthony discuss what this could mean for the veteran vote. And the BBC’s New York Business Correspondent Michelle Fleury explains how the post-covid economy may affect the election. On AmericAnswer.... what exactly happens if one of the candidates dies?Studio director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close
Editor: Dino Sofos</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qzzzf.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08qzzzf.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America on fire</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08rq1t8.mp3</link>
			<description>With wildfires devastating the West Coast, we look at whether environmental issues will sway voters’ minds. As polls in Florida tighten, we deep dive into the diverse Hispanic vote. And how could the election affect post-Brexit trade negotiations between the US and the UK?Studio Director: Emma Crowe
Producers: Harriet Noble and Natalie Ktena
Assistant Editor: Emma Close</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08rq1t8.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p08rq1t8.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>‘An Elderly Man with Poor Memory’: Biden’s Age Old Problem</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h9y4d1.mp3</link>
			<description>A bombshell report from Special Counsel Robert Hur has raised serious questions about President Joe Biden's memory, which the White House has been quick to rebuff. The report criticised the president for retaining classified information but rejected prosecution, arguing that Biden would likely present himself at trial as &quot;a sympathetic, well-meaning, elderly man with a poor memory&quot;.Americast dissects the details of this breaking story with Sarah Baxter, Director of the Marie Colvin Center for International Reporting and a former US correspondent.And as Tucker Carlson becomes the first Western journalist to sit down one-on-one with Vladimir Putin since the invasion of Ukraine, Justin and Anthony give their instant reaction to the interview as it drops.HOSTS: 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUEST: 
•  Sarah Baxter, Director of Marie Colvin Center for International Reporting in New YorkGET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast US Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155 This episode was made by George Dabby, Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo, and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Dafydd Evans. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h9y4d1.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0h9y4d1.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Global Story: Could Taylor Swift swing the US election?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hb3l0q.mp3</link>
			<description>Our colleagues on The Global Story made this episode on a subject we know is close to many Americaster's hearts. So we thought we'd put it in your feeds.It's presented by Europe editor Katya Adler. To look at Taylor Swift's potential political sway, she's joined by North America business correspondent Erin Delmore.Subscribe to The Global Story by searching for The Global Story on BBC Sounds.GET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastUS Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155This podcast was made by Alice Aylett Roberts, Richard Moran and Emilia Jansson. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The assistant editor is Sergi Forcada Freixas and the senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hb3l0q.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:50</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hb3l0q.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Putin Says Vote For Joe!</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hc7zjr.mp3</link>
			<description>Love is in the air…or is it? Vladimir Putin expressed his preference for the next American president on Valentine’s Day - but critics suspect there might be more to his endorsement than meets the eye. His comments come in the wake of Donald Trump’s disparaging declaration against NATO and that Russia should “do whatever the hell they want” to countries that don't pay up.And after our emergency episode on Special Counsel Robert Hur’s report on Joe Biden’s handling of classified documents, we respond to your questions about how, if at all, President Biden could be removed from office.HOSTS: 
• Sarah Smith, North America editor 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. US Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155 This episode was made by George Dabby with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo, and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Philip Bull. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hc7zjr.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:42:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hc7zjr.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America Shoots For the Moon Again: Houston, We Have Neil deGrasse Tyson</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hdlg14.mp3</link>
			<description>Back on earth, Donald Trump’s legal troubles are mounting and the Republican presidential hopeful now faces debts of over half a billion dollars. We assess how the former president will try to pay off these debts and what effect it might have on his run for the White House.And on the evening that the US returned to the moon, Neil deGrasse Tyson - one of America’s most famous astrophysicists - talks to us about why commercial space ventures are in fashion and why people are struggling to know where to get their facts.HOSTS: • Sarah Smith, North America editor 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480 
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk 
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. US Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155 This episode was made by George Dabby with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo, and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Mike Regaard. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hdlg14.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:48:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hdlg14.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How will the Alabama IVF ruling affect the US election?</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hfydcz.mp3</link>
			<description>US Supreme Court justices are considering two cases from Florida and Texas which could fundamentally alter the future of online free speech. Meanwhile, in Alabama, the state’s top court ruling on IVF has cast doubt on the future of the treatment, as the debate over reproductive rights enters new territory.We unpack what’s going on, how the cases could affect the lives of Americans, and how they could influence the upcoming election.HOSTS: 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GUEST: 
Mary Zeigler, legal historian, professor of law, and expert on the history, and politics of reproduction.GET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. US Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155 This episode was made by Chris Flynn, Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo, and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Hannah Montgomery. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hfydcz.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:37:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hfydcz.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump: The Sequel? An Americast x Panorama Special</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hgm6jv.mp3</link>
			<description>This afternoon the Supreme Court overturned a Colorado ruling that declared Donald Trump ineligible to run for President in the state. Justin and Marianna have been in the US to look at how despite legal, financial and polling challenges, he's on course for an epic election rematch with Joe Biden in November. Marianna’s also uncovered evidence of Trump supporters using AI to attract votes from African Americans.You can watch Panorama, Trump: The Sequel? here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/m001x0yl HOSTS:
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondentGET IN TOUCH:
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #AmericastFind out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF.US Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155This episode was made by Chris Flynn with Catherine Fusillo. The technical producer was Gareth Jones. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hgm6jv.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:43:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hgm6jv.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Super Tuesday: Everything Points to Trump vs Biden</title>
			<link>http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hgw3mn.mp3</link>
			<description>Fifteen states voted on super Tuesday to decide who the nominees for the Democratic and Republican parties will be. Donald Trump didn’t quite get the clean sweep he hoped for, but will Nikki Haley’s Vermont win be enough to keep her in the race?The Americast team discuss the issues that mattered most to voters on Tuesday, namely immigration and the economy, and how the race has become a battle of the incumbents. HOSTS: 
• Sarah Smith, North America editor 
• Justin Webb, Radio 4 presenter 
• Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent 
• Anthony Zurcher, North America correspondent GET IN TOUCH: 
• Join our online community: https://discord.gg/qSrxqNcmRB 
• Send us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 9480
• Email Americast@bbc.co.uk
• Or use #Americast Find out more about our award-winning “undercover voters” here: bbc.in/3lFddSF. US Election Unspun: Sign up for Anthony’s new BBC newsletter: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-68093155 This episode was made by George Dabby with Rufus Gray, Catherine Fusillo and Claire Betzer. The technical producer was Hannah Montgomery. The series producer is George Dabby. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hgw3mn.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:11</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="http://open.live.bbc.co.uk/mediaselector/6/redir/version/2.0/mediaset/audio-nondrm-download/proto/http/vpid/p0hgw3mn.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
