<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>The Hamilton Morris Podcast</title>
		<link>https://www.patreon.com/HamiltonMorris</link>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:author>Hamilton Morris</itunes:author>
		<itunes:image href="https://is3-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts126/v4/a6/99/35/a6993546-87c4-bc77-62c4-4e56b0058642/mza_1854238532438350957.jpg/313x0w.webp"/>
		<category>Education</category>
		<image>
			<url>https://is3-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts126/v4/a6/99/35/a6993546-87c4-bc77-62c4-4e56b0058642/mza_1854238532438350957.jpg/313x0w.webp</url>
			<title>The Hamilton Morris Podcast</title>
		</image>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">36590770</guid>
			<title>#001 Interview With A Man Who Sold LSD To Steve Jobs</title>
			<description>I don't usually interview people involved with the distribution side of psychedelics, but this conversation touches on so many fascinating topics in the history of LSD that I thought other people might find it interesting. The conversation covers Steve Jobs, Kary Mullis, ergotamine tartrate, LSD distribution, and SARS-CoV-2. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/bf/50/bf504aaeeae0dc82c669790c6c680d1b88a49be568c7e62d2797e27685d0fae9.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:16:34</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20200430080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">37012316</guid>
			<title>#002 Conversation With A Clandestine Quaalude Cook</title>
			<description>Please enjoy the second installment of my "podcast"
</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/70/90/7090a50782706707963fa6606239ea943eee44cb1482bab982487522cda82b9b.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>00:49:29</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20200512080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">37646727</guid>
			<title>#003 Interview With An MK-801-Naut</title>
			<description>A most superlative discussion of NMDA antagonists! MK-801 is the strongest dissociative that has been used by humans, it is also one of the most mysterious and (arguably) one of the most dangerous. Episode three of my podcast features an interview with a teenager who ordered MK-801 and tested it on himself and his friends. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/08/ea/08eae72e5d33dbf5349a56406b49fdc2cf5fca7bf5f0c4bf648d04c901696dd7.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>00:43:51</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20200529080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">37745739</guid>
			<title>#004 An Interview With DEA Chemist Terry Dal Cason</title>
			<description>In this almost three hour conversation with senior forensic DEA chemist Terry Dal Cason we discuss MDMA chemistry, fentanyl, police brutality, and the ethics of prohibition. Terry Dal Cason is a complicated figure who the clandestine MDMA chemist Strike called, "The godfather of all clandestine ecstasy chemistry."</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/d7/21/d721001d5ac58eafc68ea90d71d40f5eb339d24f542d73c42d34227df1a0cd8b.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:51:57</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20200531080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">38669443</guid>
			<title>#005 Journal Club: LSD and the Head Twitch Response</title>
			<description>This podcast is the first of what I hope to be a series of "journal club" discussions with scientists about an important scientific paper. In this episode Jason Wallach and I discuss the strange origin of the head twitch response and how it became the most important behavioral correlate for 5HT2A agonism in non-human animals. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/2b/e0/2be08839188e6a74c71f7da37c043e8ed679efe61b6fa4ab6cc65045d6151724.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:07:52</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20200627080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">42647842</guid>
			<title>#006 Production update</title>
			<description>Hi, all. Here's a new podcast with an update with what I've been working on regarding Pharmacopeia. In this conversation I'm joined by producer Soren Shade.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/5c/ab/5cab61abe3211c84ab81dab0bc9b155d32257fd608dc08551c1ba0eb4fc69d1f.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>00:33:52</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20201012080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">44026069</guid>
			<title>#007 Production update 2</title>
			<description>The end is in sight. Enjoy a second installment of the production podcast in which I am joined again by friend and producer Soren Shade.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/95/91/95913aa71fc9714c4245720fabccb4e847d6d73b7f6b75c880c9596d75688d3b.mp4" />
			<itunes:duration>00:34:21</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20201118080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">44422985</guid>
			<title>#008 A Talk With Errol Morris</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with my father about his new documentary "My Psychedelic Love Story", which premieres Sunday, November 29th on Showtime. Many thanks for Josh Kearney for recording this discussion. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/92/22/9222c62f81c1ef08a6b93f4a62088f8d033048fec87a2ffa6d40fb85bbd9ab25.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:11:04</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20201129080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">46188962</guid>
			<title>#009 A Talk With Eric Andre</title>
			<description>Hi, all. It turns out Eric Andre is a fan of the show and he called me yesterday to talk, here is our conversation.

In other news, we are gearing up to print a third and final edition of the pamphlet. The first edition was only 500 copies and contained a couple typos, the second edition is 2,500 copies and the third edition will be 5,000 copies. The pamphlet has already raised more than $70,000 for the Michael J Fox Foundation and more than $10,000 for the original toad artist Gail Patterson. As stipulated in the episode, I also plan to donate some money to toad conservation efforts via the Tucson Herpetological Society, but I'm waiting on them to propose a specific plan for the money before making the donation. Thanks everyone who bought a copy and for those that didn't I will be sure to post here first when the new edition is available.

I've recorded a couple of new Patreon-exclusive interviews that I'm currently editing, one about the chemistry of N-hydroxy-MDA and another that is a long discussion of the meth episode and disparaging article about the show by Erik Davis.  

I hope to have those out by the end of the week.

(No audio files, only a YouTube video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oXRcly_jDoM)</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="" />
			<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210114080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">46893109</guid>
			<title>#010 Interview With A European PCE Chemist</title>
			<description>Hi, all. I've been receiving interesting messages from a variety of different chemists recently. Here is a discussion with a chemist who synthesized and tested an unusual arylcyclohexylamine called PCE

EDIT: I was interested in learning more about his technique for producing NaCN. I've attached an interesting article from 1895 that describes a similar process as well as a long Science Madness thread. Cyanide's reputation is deserved, it is seriously a deadly poison, a chemist friend killed himself with it last year. This is not some corny, "Don't try this at home!" boilerplate. Seriously––do not try this at home. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/71/1d/711dd5c13efb1b38ab67a4afe4958e34bf267e2d37048920170292eb1087d5ab.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:10:46</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210131080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false" />
			<title>#011 EXPLOSIONS AND FIRE!</title>
			<description>Here I interview the great Australian chemistry YouTube titan Explosions and Fire.

Philip Eaton's original cubane synthesis and an article reviewing reported ingestions of C4 plastic explosive are attached.

Here is a link to the Explosions and Fire cubane synthesis videos: https://www.youtube.com/c/ExplosionsFire2/search?query=cubane

Here is a link to Sir Martyn Poliakoff's seemingly naive support for the elimination of industrially useful chemicals that could be employed in the manufacture of chemical weapons: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n7uJoi8DXi

The story of the chemist who blew off his hands during an ETN recrystallization: https://www.sciencemadness.org/whisper/viewthread.php?tid=22554

My HBO piece that features NurdRage: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=35XGfnmTm8E</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/c3/c9/c3c91d6ca715f4a772581cc4de4d085005dff209c126ac830aae73dad916cc48.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:01:48</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210214080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">48027722</guid>
			<title>#012 PCP Cops</title>
			<description>An interview with infamous undercover LAPD "dope cop" Frank Lyga about his career tracking clandestine PCP synthesists. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/19/56/1956900873869234eaffc3dffb87a3ec0598032b481f8c48eace3ce6b12dd25f.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:02:13</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210226080000</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">48249754</guid>
			<title>#013 Dr. David Juurlink</title>
			<description>Follow him on twitter @DavidJuurlink

Fitting that the 13th upload would be fraught with problems, but the third time's the charm!</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/38/c1/38c17fb35351607df685173a8a98b37645da5f66b3ed8e604e6340c9941d5525.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:18:09</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210302210455</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">48839628</guid>
			<title>#014 Cop Talk, Interview With A Self-Critical Police Officer</title>
			<description>In this podcast I tell a story of grotesque corruption and cronyism that radicalized me as a teenager and made me recognize the horrors of the war on drugs. I also interview a self-critical cop about what it's like to enforce drug laws. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/2c/4d/2c4d7df92538b71d9223830c04d73f0076af41c5c3f4dfcbd02a696becadbb24.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:16:53</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210316213623</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">49330103</guid>
			<title>#015 An Interview With Psychedelic Lawyer Richard Glen Boire</title>
			<description>(No description)</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 02:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/dc/dc/dcdcff3cc7c515684cd766f098391fd2875a96c42ea0abf6de3e5e5ac8be0f05.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:29:55</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210329023503</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">50507016</guid>
			<title>#017 Interview With Bill Richards</title>
			<description>Here is a discussion about psychedelics, pharmaceutical companies, and psychotherapy with living legend Bill Richards. I've attached his PhD dissertation below and here is a link to the episode of 60 Minutes described in the interview. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 18:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/df/b4/dfb4219e48df519b5ea0718246f04e27478471b35e788ba5875b0aab8273b5c0.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:00:26</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210426184049</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">50740223</guid>
			<title>#018 Clandestine Chromium Carbene Chemistry</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview a former organometallic chemist named Mike Roberts who conducted underground research on DMT, DET, DiPT, DOM, 2C-B, and mescaline while working as a graduate student at UCLA. After a year of continuous psychedelic use his studies ended when began to confuse reality with a dream. I've attached one of Mike Roberts chemistry publications below. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 23:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/92/49/924967e2bc662930bfe5668f443ae50a375898f96e39ef983a38ee64ad8de70a.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:34:18</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210501230818</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">50828755</guid>
			<title>#019 Kratom Survey With Dr. Oliver Grundmann</title>
			<description>A discussion about kratom pharmacology with kratom researcher Dr. Oliver Grundmann and producer/kratom tea purveyor Soren Shade. 

The two surveys I mentioned can be found below.

Kratom survey: tinyurl.com/kratomteasurvey

5-MeO-DMT survey: https://5meodmt.psychedelicsurvey.com/?fbclid=IwAR1I_wkuWCHjODC35ow57Ok4uSFYq37QRkNOmyit01HH_wa78iHJl3V3ZLg</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/e8/4c/e84ca5ea218b627c091a22da95e172de532a1ba7ea5822d2da11ee004912ebc6.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:08:18</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210504005008</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">51651964</guid>
			<title>#020 Dr. Etienne Van Zyl, Project Coast, And Methaqualone</title>
			<description>A long discussion with forensic chemist Dr. Etienne Van Zyl about the chemistry of methaqualone and the potential weaponization of psychoactive drugs by the apartheid government. Some of the attached literature is fascinating and worth a read, especially the book "Secrets and Lies" which is the most authoritative text on the crimes of Project Coast.  </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 23:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/59/5c/595cb512ed560886f5d3b232ded3e52aed0651d9eb1bfa6ef9dea383b779abaa.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:45:27</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210524231905</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">52046643</guid>
			<title>#021 Dr. Carl Hart</title>
			<description>At long last, I visited Dr. Hart's office at Columbia University for this discussion about drug policy, police brutality, opioids, Basic Instinct, and Kids.

</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 05:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/e4/e4/e4e454ec9f6883384ffd3cf3760e57112fee784ac2ceef7b0209cef9833d339e.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:35:54</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210603054308</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">53104899</guid>
			<title>#022 Studying Chemistry In Prison</title>
			<description>This is an interview with an MDMA chemist who was sentenced to ten years in prison and used his time behind bars to improve his understanding of chemistry and improve syntheses related to the one that allowed law enforcement to take his freedom. Tomorrow I will also post a video of my interview with Ed Domino.

</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/08/b6/08b66690fc32c06f115733a55b511b6f79c2b01f9a8afc033b9d32367769f925.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:12:26</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210630065036</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">53240173</guid>
			<title>#023 An Interview With Ketamine Pioneer Dr. Edward Domino</title>
			<description>I received some complaints about the vimeo player in the last podcast so I'm releasing an added audio only version that will play like the other podcasts for anyone that prefers it. This was a zoom call so the audio is not going to be great. 

Later this month I will release an interview that will contain the first ever published true history of the penis envy variety of Psilocybe cubensis, many misconceptions abound (I'm responsible for some of them) this will be the official account. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 04:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/51/f2/51f2d6cc8cd3bcb8a8e1a0d40eebf82777cf0cbb25acde144b78081ea1587bb7.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>00:52:17</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210703040318</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">53931022</guid>
			<title>#024 The True Story Of The Penis Envy Mushroom</title>
			<description>An interview 14 years in the making, for the first time the true story of the penis envy mushroom is told. Many apocryphal origin stories have been disseminated (sometimes by me) now, for the first time, the true story of how the most potent cubensis strain was created is told. 

</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 02:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/bd/b0/bdb0821a660601af3a3791c34f7d63cf721e008f30a9e61a753bdfe5ddde3d90.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:52:07</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210721021236</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">54362943</guid>
			<title>#025 Thomas Morton And I Discuss Addiction</title>
			<description>Thomas Morton (aka "Baby Balls") and I discuss the record number of drug overdoses reported in 2020 and what can be done to prevent this tragic loss of life . Thomas and I discuss the difficulty of assessing external indicators of addiction and his own opioid addiction and recovery. 

</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 01:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/bb/aa/bbaa99eaee86f8e2fda50ec51bc3f27a2066a50f0c809c5dccf9972748e6724c.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:51:22</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210801012145</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">55228463</guid>
			<title>#027 An Interview With Vyvanse Inventor Dr. Robert Oberlender</title>
			<description>In this interview I talk with the great medicinal chemist Dr. Robert Oberlender, he is the inventor of the multi-billion dollar blockbuster drug vyvanse and a ten year veteran of the David E. Nichols laboratory responsible for the synthesis and evaluation of a number psychedelics and empathogens such DOsB, DOiB, MDAI, and many others. 

</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 06:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/dc/9b/dc9b4c249d6ee0cd270f3b7a1c0c877d0584824dc1ebcbbda65af5f5cc7c1f07.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:46:34</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210823065332</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">55506298</guid>
			<title>#027 A Talk With Medicinal Chemist Dr. Mike Cunningham</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with my friend Dr. Mike Cunningham, a chemist at the lab of Dalibor Sames at Columbia University who is a cofounder of the psychedelic pharmaceutical company Gilgamesh

</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 02:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/67/13/6713982655923bc9712fa634d33bc2f253df153727bd895f679a726980304d9d.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:11:18</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210830023420</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">55653035</guid>
			<title>#028 A Talk With Jonathan Ott</title>
			<description>Jonathan Ott is a chemist, translator, and one of the greatest psychedelic researchers and historians to have ever lived, I tracked him down and talked to him about bufotenine in a cottage in England. 

</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/f9/6b/f96b9d5822de47674e976d045ed502a99e940c819bfe1905a0375392909e39c1.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:23:31</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210902005418</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">56787397</guid>
			<title>#029 Thai Kratom Policy With Pascal Tanguay</title>
			<description>Pascal Tanguay is a researcher who has lived in Thailand studying kratom for over a decade, our discussion covers the way the Thai media used kratom as a tool to justify increasing budgets for law enforcement and the traditions surrounding kratom use in Thailand. 

My friend (and former Pharmacopeia producer) Soren is still collecting information on kratom use in the United States. If you'd like to take the survey he created with Dr. Oliver Grundmann you can do so here: Tinyurl.com/Kratomteasurvey</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 04:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/ef/08/ef085a4b8f459024d16114331e5db19598d393c8150e7f20e5b416eba511037d.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:03:28</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20210930045045</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">56870816</guid>
			<title>#030 Dr. Ethan Nadelmann Of The Drug Policy Alliance</title>
			<description>Initially hoping to discuss the mechanics of how a drug is made illegal, I instead have a far-reaching discussion about drug policy with one of the greatest living experts on the subject. 

</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 18:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/10/b3/10b3b0fa19ee39de86f345d1a896f43dec6cd0344c40eb2b8a6ef1d0911a0c83.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:49:38</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211001183955</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">57491778</guid>
			<title>#031 An Interview With Dr. Andrew Weil</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with the legendary Dr. Andrew Weil about Albert Hoffman smoking toad venom, sexual abuse in psychedelic psychotherapy, Charles Manson, and Matcha 

If you'd like to watch a video of this interview it can be viewed here: https://vimeo.com/634063050

Password: catdander



I apologize for the fan sound in the first 12 minutes, it goes away during the interview.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/28/a9/28a9990ab853294b6b680c583f5872f33fc929c1ea654c1e938955fb0e669dac.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:14:59</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211017000035</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">58080277</guid>
			<title>#032 A Short Talk With Ann Shulgin</title>
			<description>A short talk with the great Ann Shulgin about Sasha Shulgin and her friendship with Darrell Lemaire. Two historical questions are described, I would love to know if any listeners have insight into them.

A dramatically improved version of the audio was just uploaded, now it is ready to go!</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 23:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/64/bb/64bb2ca86b0981d64b5ec9e12e52cbef7591a146afb509791eb5579e190265eb.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>00:29:07</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211030233303</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">58708009</guid>
			<title>#033 An Interview With Dr. Charles D. Nichols</title>
			<description>In this interview I talk with LSU pharmacology professor Dr. Charles Nichols about his father's influence on his scientific carrier and his groundbreaking research on psychedelics and inflammation.

</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/44/69/44693a7235fc4465f9c2ff5b6b88e85226e85427aac6c494d1ee92a612db4410.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:31:21</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211115001136</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">59224393</guid>
			<title>#034 A Four Hour Interview With Dr. David E Nichols</title>
			<description>https://c2.kemono.party/data/66/51/66515a32860b6d2e72c595a814816a216b3dc47e1176e3c77cab1cc6f4282f4c.mp3</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 05:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/66/51/66515a32860b6d2e72c595a814816a216b3dc47e1176e3c77cab1cc6f4282f4c.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>03:58:16</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211128051327</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">60163615</guid>
			<title>#035 Ergot Biochemistry With Dr. Daniel Panaccione</title>
			<description>In this interview I talk about the wide variety of different organisms that produce lysergamides with Dr. Daniel Panaccione, who proposes that many of the natural products we consider botanical in origin may actually be the product of fungal symbionts. 

Also in the intro I suggest that methylergometrine is a natural product, I want to be clear that it is not. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 07:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/26/a1/26a1d69f3e25a9c92c17ab2a91d84ae5ae097c07b5ee4c24deca57675e018dd3.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:31:01</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211221074150</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">60339541</guid>
			<title>#036 An Amanita Christmas With Dr. Povl Krogsgaard-Larsen</title>
			<description>An interview with GABA titan and gaboxadol inventor Dr. Povl Krogsgaard-Larsen about his discovery of gaboxadol, the toxicity of ibotenic acid, 3-hydroxy-isoxazole chemistry and self-experimentation. 

Chilton reference attached, many thanks to Gerald Billac</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 02:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/57/1d/571d93002255e1aff42bf85302058f638219931a641b3bfbfe54e035cecfae35.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:11:43</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211226020521</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">60492774</guid>
			<title>#037 The Origins Of Phyllomedusa Bicolor With Peter Gorman</title>
			<description>Website: https://pgorman.com/
Trip info and donation: gormanexpeditions.com/
First description of P. bicolor use in 1925: https://erowid.org/references/refs_view.php?ID=9053</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 07:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/53/2c/532caaa15c917701d2e94684f45f999f8ea0fdbe31af10dccfcec68f7e05fad3.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:42:50</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20211230070756</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">61222757</guid>
			<title>#038 Ethnobotanical Investigations With Dr. Mark Plotkin</title>
			<description>In this interview I talk with the great ethnobotanist Dr. Mark Plotkin about his relationship with Richard Evans Shultes and Amazonian ethnobotany

</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 05:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/ac/63/ac6323a584ffd438325108b4bd00d016844254b4b19b5dcc33fe77c8935561ee.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:04:56</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220116053647</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">61939438</guid>
			<title>#039 Drug-Induced False Memories With Dr. Manoj Doss </title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview the brilliant cognitive neuroscientist and Johns Hopkins memory researcher Dr. Manoj Doss about the influence of drugs on false memory formation and false memories in general.</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 05:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/b9/7c/b97c47deb31f481e3137abf191f0b7df808f20396630853b67bf6e36a5211e62.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:13:43</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220201052551</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">62525028</guid>
			<title>#040 Kratom Prohibition And Science With Drs. Chris McCurdy, Brian Pearson, And Oliver Grundmann</title>
			<description>Tomorrow five psychedelics are being prohibited by the DEA, today and tomorrow are the last times to comment on the scheduling action. Please take this time to express your disapproval of the government's ongoing attempts to place psychedelics in schedule I by commenting here:

https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2022/01/14/2022-00713/schedules-of-controlled-substances-placement-of-4-hydroxy-nn

Then please enjoy this conversation between Drs. Chris McCurdy, Brian Pearson, and Oliver Grundmann about new research on kratom and how it became one of the only drugs to evade prohibition after being proposed for placement in schedule I.

 If you'd prefer to watch a video it can be viewed here: 

https://vimeo.com/676939885

password: kratom</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/2b/38/2b388b5751eec034a4272bb45ca7b09db31f6468f57559a8e2ab11a9fbe4fa3f.mp4" />
			<itunes:duration>01:11:34</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220214002433</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">63197091</guid>
			<title>#041 Salvia Divinorum History With Dr. José-Luis Díaz</title>
			<description>In this interview I talk with the Mexican psychiatrist Dr. José-Luis Díaz about his pioneering field work and animal behavioral experiments with Salvia extracts in the 1970s. There is discussion of cats on saliva, maybe that should have been the title. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 01:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/44/77/44771da88bc66bceabd2d13bfb12958a7b55d950ca0429b43b80b9a32903989f.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:39:31</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220301015428</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">63629216</guid>
			<title>#042 Drug Meme Disinformation With @Namaste.At.Home.Dad</title>
			<description>In this podcast I meet with meme auteur Joelle Bouchard (@namaste.at.home.dad) to discuss the memesphere and the use of memes and social media in the spread of misinformation

https://www.instagram.com/namaste.at.home.dad/</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 17:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/95/11/9511ed853a3bceeb4e12cfe8903dba5384100f723c83b85a9a17e8c1688b7546.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:05:50</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220310172821</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">64066145</guid>
			<title>#043 Dissociative Addiction With Steve-O</title>
			<description>Steve-O tells the full story of his PCP use and how he found sobriety



Here is a link to the talk with Leonard Pickard in SF, it's $80, which in my opinion is too much. I will try to record my talk and post it here. 

https://www.bicycledaysf.org/speakers</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 07:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/a1/0e/a10efffa77dc4a1e4ab982037ca587af6c58dcafb8c59dd61051e350d3a00213.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:17:55</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220321073558</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">64560770</guid>
			<title>#044 New Natural Psychedelics With Dr. Dennis McKenna</title>
			<description>A far-ranging discussion with one of the greatest contributors to the science of psychedelics, this is a good one!


Website for the upcoming Ethnopharmacologic Search for Psychoactive Drugs. https://espd55.com/ (Note: This website appears to be under construction)

Dr. McKenna's academy website. https://mckenna.academy/

Online Amazonian biocultural archives https://biognosis.mckenna.academy/</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 05:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/86/d6/86d62c356d992522acbd9092020de7b758609031c7b75a7abbc1b6829826169c.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:51:40</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220401050055</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">65706229</guid>
			<title>#045 The Creation Of Synthetic Cannabinoids With Dr. Sam Banister</title>
			<description>This is a conversation with the cannabinoid-specializing medicinal chemist and pharmacologist Dr. Sam Banister of SDB-001 fame, we discuss his career in cannabinoid chemistry and his new venture to design psychedelic treatments for depression. 


Ignition!: An informal history of liquid rocket propellants
https://archive.org/details/ignition_201612

Enamine
https://cen.acs.org/people/Chemists-respond-invasion-Ukraine/100</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 07:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/57/73/5773d787e2534acf56aff4b9afc32cad0bfc74eee2a9c8151300a3aa67aa64ec.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:55:09</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220428071115</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">66315477</guid>
			<title>#046 Amphetamine Pharmacology With Dr. David Sulzer</title>
			<description>Dr. David Sulzer is a professor at Columbia University where he studies the pharmacology of amphetamine and dopamine transmission in the brain. He is considered one of the world's leading experts on amphetamine pharmacology and developed an important hypothesis ("the weak base hypothesis") for how amphetamine interacts with synaptic vesicles. </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 01:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/9d/d2/9dd24df77e74cdd17b837d3971cdf0302bdfb2789a43eb6ada11299e3e93076c.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:29:21</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220512012554</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">67221221</guid>
			<title>#047 The Mysterious Life Of Al Hubbard With Brad Holden</title>
			<description>Al Hubbard is one of the most mysterious and influential figures in psychedelic history, a uranium magnate, CIA-associated psychedelic psychotherapist. For the first time a book has been dedicated to Hubbard's life, I speak with the author Brad Holden about his research. 


https://www.arcadiapublishing.com/Products/9781467148061
https://bradholden.org
Atmospheric Power Generator - https://youtu.be/3EG-zjqs9xM
Atmospheric Power Explanation - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2rVdEhyMR6A
Psychedelic Party Footage - https://youtu.be/U-sfDEEcMQ8</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 02:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/27/79/2779071b65a6d1d2a368ce56a36c3c0930789449976dd41bbdda8a3497c9bf1e.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:10:46</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220602022520</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">68243828</guid>
			<title>#048 Interview With A Clandestine MDA Enantiopurifier</title>
			<description>A never before told tale of multi-ton MDA synthesis in the 1980s. Guided by a mysterious Monsanto chemist gone rogue, our interviewee embarked on a quest to synthesize vast quantities of MDA.


Subjects discussed include: Differential MDA enantiomer psychopharmacology, chocolate LSD dog food, and Raney nickel. 


https://pixels.com/featured/grateful-dreads-tweaked-anne-provost.html</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 17:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/66/66/6666704cff1839aa89b00574702077b5de0ce183d527f57716630e39af9f1a84.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:23:56</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220625175824</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">68761318</guid>
			<title>#049 5-HT1A Agonists And More With Dr. Uroš Laban</title>
			<description>Dr. Uroš Laban talks about receiving his PhD in the lab of Dr. David Nichols, the effect of novel 5-HT1A agonists and Mike Roberts being kicked out of UCLA weeks before receiving his PhD. </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 02:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/b2/6b/b26b406ce71f7e41c23fb6d224097db97b1409ba284c61728b3e873b6756732c.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:34:36</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220707021047</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">69005467</guid>
			<title>#050 Patreon Subscriber Q"A!</title>
			<description>I answer the first batch of questions here! Topics discussed include salvinorin A kinetics, pineal decalcification, panpsychism, and shared hallucinations. 


There were a lot of questions, I will try to answer a second batch of questions later this month. 


https://www.vice.com/en/article/yvebgv/salvia-velada-mazatec-shaman-ceremony-portfolio-v23n8


Lastly, at one point in this I say that ingestion of formic acid causes blindness. I assumed this was the case because formic acid is typically considered the toxic metabolite with methanol ingestion and many sources suggest it directly damages the optic nerve but I now wonder if that is truly the case. Case reports of high dose formic acid ingestion do not describe blindness so clearly there is some additional complexity in the matter. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 19:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/09/4c/094c65da81e711ca0270849cbe7af82afbe2c1c995e14354dcbbfb8dbb7581da.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:32:29</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220712192707</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">69068168</guid>
			<title>#051 Healing Vibrations With Dr. David Rabin</title>
			<description />
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 04:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/92/04/92041b9a83f5f4414d8f57059907d46af0c5ea1712dbd8d7a1fad677e712e4cc.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:26:31</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220714042628</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">69620551</guid>
			<title>#052 Cinco Sins Of Psychedelic Science With Dr. Manoj Doss</title>
			<description>In my second interview with Dr. Manoj Doss we recap a statistical controversy, discuss the five sins of psychedelic science, and what kinds of psychedelic stories deserve publicity. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 22:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/c9/fe/c9fe30a5929f1d77ed5e06489121c3c5606c44e93492ad75fe6afdcd54c6edf7.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>03:02:30</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220726224753</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">69717202</guid>
			<title>#053 The Inside Story Of The DEA Battle With Lawyers John Hunter And Matt Zorn</title>
			<description>This week the DEA officially withdrew their intention to prohibit five psychedelic tryptamines, this is the inside story of the legal battle behind the success featuring the great lawyers John Hunter and Matt Zorn.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 22:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/31/a1/31a1c0266f487f52ce7a3723d807280dbda45bb1a954d0153e00bf098e88c283.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:36:37</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220728220014</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">70219579</guid>
			<title>#054 The True Story Of Charles Innes</title>
			<description>An interview ten years in the making, for the first time the true story of Charles Innes is recounted. 

Charles Innes blinded himself while under the influence of PCP in 1971, a tragedy that may have inspired Nixon's war on drugs and a national PCP panic. The attached files provide evidence for many of the stories told by Innes. A video version of this interview is also being assembled for patrons and eventual release on YouTube. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 05:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/5b/99/5b99aa06ce8876ba53324e5b405e3f4e475e9ff36eaf360da2568ccfdb472391.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:53:36</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220808051123</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">70951568</guid>
			<title>#055 Michael Valentine Smith Unmasked</title>
			<description>For the first time the pseudonymous author of the 1973 clandestine chemistry classic "Psychedelic Chemistry" is interviewed about his motivations for writing the book, his own experience with psychedelic chemistry, his relationships with the Shulgins, and his later interest in 3D technology and philosophy. 

Here is also a link to the video of the interview, please note that this video link does not contain the introduction present in the audio-only version.

Password: Wittgenstein

https://vimeo.com/742512199 </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 04:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/01/af/01af9a05e5b32e3bb3b5c8807346b5aa5b0fb45991182bf2fa0c7522a91b3b72.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:36:46</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220824043613</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">71349495</guid>
			<title>#056 A Psychedelic Arrest With Aaron Genuth</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with my old friend Aaron Genuth about the role of psychedelics in Judaism, drug policy reform, and an unfortunate recent encounter with law enforcement. 

https://www.gofundme.com/f/help-aaron-with-legal-fees-and-unjust-charges

https://nypost.com/2015/02/24/cherry-company-owner-commits-suicide-amid-factory-raid/</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 06:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/b5/41/b5418b8f1463720e9598daa497a46612b89b539720c2278da33e906cde1036e1.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:31:47</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220901065903</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">72159748</guid>
			<title>#057 Michael Evans Brown Of The EMCDDA On New Psychoactive Substances</title>
			<description>An interview with the program director for the EMCDDA about the emergence of new psychoactive drugs in the 21st century. We discuss many unusual synthetic substances such as MT-45, PT-141, AM-2233, MDMB-FUBINACA, 5-IT, and more!



https://twitter.com/mevansbrown

https://youtu.be/dUKp33FzmUg

https://www.roxycinemanewyork.com/screenings/hamiltons-pharmacopeia/</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 20:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/67/99/6799b5cd5f47a01097ced1e955e55ceca948d3d854e7f0b51feeec70dfba0b33.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:43:53</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220918204712</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">72393248</guid>
			<title>#58 Designer Steroids With Patrick Arnold</title>
			<description>An interview with chemist and steroid researcher Patrick Arnold, the man behind DMAA, The Clear, and many other drugs that permanently changed the world of body building and competitive sports. </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 22:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c3.kemono.party/data/81/b4/81b49bdfbda4fa24b36de43eecd713ff7a13166eef5c1a0341af0cab2f83c0dd.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:37:16</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220923221307</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">72697211</guid>
			<title>#059 Tripping On Peyote With Jean-Michel Basquiat</title>
			<description>An excerpt from an interview with the legendary LSD distributor and NYC graffiti artist BIL-ROCK where he tells the story of Basquiat's first peyote trip with buttons from a predecessor of the Temple of the True Inner Light.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 19:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/4c/4a/4c4a0b66849b1077a09d50e1bd2aae865d2843724c69b3b86625e3077b10ae70.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>00:58:00</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20220930193703</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">73789212</guid>
			<title>#060 Chemistry TikTok Houses With Josiah "The Chemist"</title>
			<description>In this podcast I discuss the limits of YouTube Chemistry, chemistry TikTok houses, and selenium chemistry with Josiah "That Chemist"

https://www.youtube.com/@That_Chemist

https://mobile.twitter.com/That_Chemist



https://www.nytimes.com/1998/11/29/magazine/lethal-chemistry-at-harvard.html</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 04:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/27/5a/275a7ee244d380852cad63879f2f9af1d056d51fbe23eeb14d9e1102e85d344e.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:07:13</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20221026040124</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">73987290</guid>
			<title>#061 DIY Gene Editing With Dr. Josiah Zayner</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview gene hacking legend Dr. Josiah Zayner, founder of The Odin, a company dedicated to empowering people to do their own gene editing experiments. Dr. Zayner's work has been ridiculed in the media, censored from YouTube, and resulted in numerous government investigations. We discuss his battles with regulators and the beauty of scientific self-experimentation. 



https://www.the-odin.com/

https://twitter.com/4LOVofScience</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/47/7e/477ea07932c0c2d6a136fd22517b53d83e37b5a68d03ddf7f48582c84586297d.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:42:33</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20221030202201</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">74668323</guid>
			<title>#062 Crime Pays But Botany Doesn't With Joey Santore</title>
			<description>In this three hour interview battle I talk with renegade cactophile Joey Santore about how he became a botanist with a cult following, cactus ecology, Psilocybe zapotecorum fruiting, and MDMA neurotoxicity. 

Joey's Youtube

https://www.crimepaysbutbotanydoesnt.com/

George Ricaurte - https://maps.org/research-archive/mdma/studyresponse.html

Timeline of peyote criminalization - https://erowid.org/plants/peyote/peyote_law1.shtml

Uncle Chorn’s Cabin - http://www.uncle-chorn.com/

MagiCactus.com - https://www.magicactus.com/index.html

Ibogaine Cure Discovered In Brooklyn - https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Howard_Lotsof</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 03:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/0b/8a/0b8ab4f65f6eb09835e1c327d6e1bf995bd0178ac435f626bf940250b2459cd9.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>03:05:35</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20221115034747</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false" />
			<title>#063 A Beginner's Experience Making MDMA In A Clandestine Lab</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview a young chemist about how he got interested in clandestine synthesis and his first encounter with law enforcement. The production of MDMA from PMK Ethyl Glycidate is discussed in detail.

CBD to THC - https://www.reddit.com/r/CBeeD/

Sandmyer reaction - https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sandmeyer_reaction

Oxidation of THF → GBL - https://chemistry.mdma.ch/hiveboard/novel/000242315.html

5-MEO-DMT synthesis - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qipKKBmY_LQ

UK PMA deaths - https://www.release.org.uk/drugs/pmma-pma/history 

1996 Canada 2C-B scheduling - https://laws-lois.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/c-38.8/page-11.html 

2016 25B-NBOMe Canada scheduling - https://erowid.org/chemicals/2ci_nbome/2ci_nbome_law.shtml 

Charles Innes PCP trip - The True Story of Charles Innes (FULL)

Lizard Labs busted - https://www.shroomery.org/forums/showflat.php/Number/28046110 </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 05:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/a5/fc/a5fc1735b67c7d345c48de57dc4a399ef6254ef82249037f1e7338b054d392de.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:26:46</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20221128055641</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">76271384</guid>
			<title>#064 December Patreon Q&amp;A</title>
			<description>The most recent Q&amp;A where I answer patron questions. Several more podcasts will be released in the coming days. Enjoy!



https://vimeo.com/19045730

https://erowid.org/experiences/subs/exp_TCB2.shtml</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/3c/5a/3c5a0db1f7cab218a6b24cfae5f0df58b1a39bc29398a8559368871b35b52681.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:57:07</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20221223063027</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">76525101</guid>
			<title>#065 Dr. Andrew Gallimore On DMTx And ​Reality Switch Technologies</title>
			<description>This is a great and far-ranging discussion with chemist and neuroscientist Dr. Andrew Gallimore about his continuous DMT infusion project (DMTx) and his new book Reality Switch Technologies. Enjoy!</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 23:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/8d/cb/8dcbcb309407cdea09bf01454cb7343c15bf2fbd3b4c5a983037e719e6844e5d.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:06:42</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20221229232757</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">77080871</guid>
			<title>#066 The Golden Age Of Research Chemicals With Adam Strauss</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with my old friend Adam Strauss about our time spent buying and testing research chemicals during the dawn of the Chinese research chemical industry.

https://twitter.com/atomstrauss

https://www.instagram.com/atomstrauss</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 06:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/7e/db/7edb4f1db51c177b6290dcf0f6affa98dc7ec9284ec4d61bf1aa3a082b4e85d5.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:36:16</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230111061018</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">77890942</guid>
			<title>#067 Ketamine Telemedicine With Dylan Beynon</title>
			<description>In this podcast I discuss the ascent and regulation of ketamine telemedicine with Dylan Beynon, the founder of the largest ketamine telemedicine company in the world. 

</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/98/a3/98a359126307cfe4c888adbe1fd2dc84235ef8b2cba54c8d9282cf72528b60bd.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:26:36</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230129034515</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">78614236</guid>
			<title>#068 Psychedelic Journalism With John Semley</title>
			<description>In this interview I talk with Philadelphia Inquirer reporter John Semley who has spent years covering psychedelics and wrote a profile of Jason Wallach for Wired magazine. 



Twitter.com/johnsemley3000

https://www.wired.com/story/race-to-engineer-new-psychedelic-drugs/</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 05:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/a2/0c/a20c3bf8da661059ceb7284ed9bd295fe2e4bac9c24116c503296b5dbf8543d1.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:49:34</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230213050626</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">78764809</guid>
			<title>#069 The Alchemist With Dr. Tarik Peterson</title>
			<description>In this interview I hear the story of a chemist named Tarik Peterson who authored an unusually sophisticated clandestine chemistry manual in 1970 and conducted self-experiments with a variety of different psychedelics he synthesized including DMT, DET, pyr-T, aMT, 5-MeO-DMT, mescaline, MDA, PMA, TMA, TMA-2, and TMA-6</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 07:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/da/18/da185a6f44010c4aeb39de73404823ae9c69ee9efcd28c226cc4b952a9277ea0.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:51:22</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230216071602</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">79380853</guid>
			<title>#070 Unraveling Ariadne's Thread With Dr. Mike Cunningham</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with Dr. Mike Cunningham about his recent mechanistic work on the pharmacology of Shulgin's mysterious creation Ariadne as well as the chemistry of alpha-ethylphenethylamines and, more broadly, the potential of non-hallucinogenic 5-HT2A agonists.

References added!</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 06:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/12/c8/12c80dabebe1ac60bd3047d165a1edcf4d893019b0ae4fe4c567d32a8ada355c.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:09:39</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230301064744</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">80415139</guid>
			<title>#071 Chris Kasick On Citizen Sleuth, True Crime Podcasting, And Theranos</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview an old friend about his new film, a five-year investigation of a mysterious death that shines light on conspiracy theories, true crime podcasting, and the pursuit of truth...and also Theranos.

https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/citizen-sleuth-emily-nestor-jaleayah-davis-murder-b2304769.html

https://www.rogerebert.com/festivals/sxsw-2023-citizen-sleuth-last-stop-larrimah-the-new-americans-gaming-a-revolution

BONUS: Here is my SXSW talk with Nicolas Langlitz https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gIkh0Tsrqho&amp;ab_channel=TheNewSchool</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 02:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/78/69/78699037d6223d875832ab7794fc4ad651db887133a949cadcec6bfcd1ec7417.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>02:21:14</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230323023149</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">80895134</guid>
			<title>#072 Director Mark Lewis On Smoking Cane Toad Venom, Rats, And Chickens</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview the legendary documentary filmmaker Mark Lewis about his seminal 1988 film Cane Toads, as well as his subsequent documentaries on rats and chickens. Cane Toads contains one of the only reports of smoking Bufo Marinus venom and we discuss how he was able to learn about this practice in Australia. </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 02:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/12/5f/125ff83bd66b77a74488cf59f24c8da6e950b7c995e8e5646cd41449bb1eccee.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:30:29</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230401023149</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">81397839</guid>
			<title>#073 The Pharmacology Of Pornography With Janice Griffith</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview friend and famous adult actress Janice Griffith about drug use and the adult entertainment industry. Enjoy!</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2023 02:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c4.kemono.party/data/d8/ba/d8bae776e4e64ee30b3d7cb7330027182960dbf2e6ace1bfca147cd8877639b1.mp3" />
			<itunes:duration>01:50:40</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230412023149</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">82482398</guid>
			<title>#074 Meme Warfare With Don Caldwell Of KnowYourMeme.Com</title>
			<description>In this podcast I interview the meme researcher and archivist Don Caldwell about how memes are created and used to sculpt public opinion.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2023 01:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/89/68/8968730060721edd033871c2f6d44c9dd580c39fd72ca58d30b2d98c8bcbe892.mp3?f=Don%20KnowYourName%20for%20patreon%20final.mp3" length="130023424" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:30:22</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230504014434</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">82774192</guid>
			<title>#075 Jordan Rubin On The Bizarre History Of The Federal Analog Act</title>
			<description>In this interview I talk with lawyer Jordan S. Rubin about his new book Bizarro, which chronicles the work of two synthetic cannabinoid entrepreneurs who found themselves ensnared in a law so confusing the DEA's own experts can't agree on how it should be interpreted.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2023 01:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c6.kemono.party/data/ef/32/ef32e3f87ec33cc3ba97ffe42d758620ddb0c718a48b1a8ccb4fde1096ed9b80.mp3?f=Bizarro%20final%20patreon.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:49:28</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230510013358</itunes:order>
</item>		
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">83402286</guid>
			<title>#076 Patreon Q&amp;A May 2023</title>
			<description>In this Q&amp;A I discuss smoking ketamine, LSD licenses, penile perception on trihexyphenidyl, injection necrosis from xylazine containing &quot;tranq dope&quot;, therapeutic validation for alien abductees, neuropixel probes, and more!

Small correction: I say only five FDA approved antidepressants are thought to exert their therapeutic effect via modulation of dopamine, but there are actually six if you include bupropion. I meant to say five *other than bupropion.* Also, the numbers reflect stats as of 2022, so the numbers might be slightly off after the approval of auvelity

Darrell Lemaire on the nootropic effects of 2C-D:

https://erowid.org/chemicals/2cd/2cd_smartpills1.shtml

I found the article about shared trihexyphenidyl penis hallucinations in Greece(!):

http://web.archive.org/web/20080409203334/http://www.geocities.com/satanid/art.htm</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2023 00:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/4d/be/4dbe69e73ce2ec28b93ad746e1c90fc7165201a5b6741ff62a706ad01b4f40fc.mp3?f=Q%26A%20May%202023_1.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:08:45</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230523003512</itunes:order>
</item>	
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">83881669</guid>
			<title>#077 A Fireside Chat With Amanda Feilding About LSD And Trepanation</title>
			<description>This is the first of a series of Amanda Feilding interviews I hope to release in the coming months. We discuss her self-trepanation, LSD research, and her film &quot;Heartbeat in the Brain.&quot; I will upload video of the interview shortly.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2023 05:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/6e/ec/6eec2ea8911bf0e5da73e829cd55960dd360a30b529368c73db3835650dc4323.mp3?f=Amanda%20final%20for%20patreon.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:03:56</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230601054849</itunes:order>
</item>	
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">84786504</guid>
			<title>#078 Psychedelic Legal Priorities With Lawyer Matt Zorn</title>
			<description>In this podcast I talk with lawyer Matt Zorn about legal priorities within the psychedelic space, deregulation, patents, prohibition, and peyote.

https://ondrugs.substack.com/



Wonderland talk coming soon...</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2023 06:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/48/a5/48a5ab845663ce6972c4da88ac5ea029f9be5a7fc3d1df0ad28168a3d5e0907a.mp3?f=Matt%20Zorn%20final%20patreon.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:58:31</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230619064314</itunes:order>
</item>	
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">85338379</guid>
			<title>#079 June Q&amp;A And An Update From The MAPS Conference</title>
			<description>Here is the newest patreon subscriber Q&amp;A, we discuss pharmahuasca, psychedelic disruption of thermoregulation, fork sodomy, regional variations in amphetamine synthesis, and more!



Note: salt stoichiometry could also be determined by X-ray crystallography, melting point (probably), and other means but NMR seems like the fastest, easiest, most reliable method.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 06:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/85/1b/851b6dd614d4b69771f1b6881797dfaa9ed3eb471248d416fb59ad9f176fc234.mp3?f=Q%26A%20June%20final%20for%20patreon.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:12:08</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230630023731</itunes:order>
</item>	
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">86016341</guid>
			<title>#080: Dr. Jackie Von Salm &amp; Jeanine Yacoub On Sponges, Mushrooms, And New Tryptamine Psychedelics</title>
			<description>Recorded at the recent MAPS conference, this is a conversation with two chemists from Psilera Dr. Jackie von Salm and Jeanine Yacoub, M.S. We discuss tricyclic tryptamines found in nature, sponge natural products, and the future of psychedelic medicinal chemistry.

https://pubs.acs.org/doi/pdf/10.1021/acs.jnatprod.2c00716

https://www.psilera.com/

https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/2-Bromo-N-methyltryptamine

https://www.science.org/content/blog-post/patents-and-prophecy</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/f9/94/f99487a7f0a9b26c9bc50d6f8ef3f7ffe49d05231f380ce938c390e74502a0f1.mp3?f=Psilera%20final%20for%20patreon.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:20:35</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230713030724</itunes:order>
</item>
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">86620808</guid>
			<title>#081: Dr. Carl Hart And Dr. Nicholas Cozzi At The MAPS Conference</title>
			<description>In this podcast I feature two short interviews with Dr. Carl Hart and Dr. Nick Cozzi that were recorded at the recent MAPS conference. Subjects discussed include xylazine, Bill Maher being a "bitch-ass motherfucker", the kinetic isotope effect, and conformationally restricted tetrahydro-1-benzoxepin analogues of hallucinogenic phenethylamines.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2023 07:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c2.kemono.party/data/55/77/5577af93562c3893fb3ab610c0d0d605be7c5afd22fad603322705e1ad5f9a1d.mp3?f=MAPS%20final%20patreon%20nick%20cozzi%20carl%20hart.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:26:16</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230725070153</itunes:order>
</item>	
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">86867367</guid>
			<title>#082: July Patreon Q&amp;A</title>
			<description>In this Q&amp;A I discuss lemon tekking, 4-AcO-MET hydrolysis, DNA intercalation by harmine and more!

EDIT: New question added!

science.org/content/blog-post/myth-ethidium-bromide</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2023 23:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c5.kemono.party/data/fe/f0/fef0f4626eac0fb345df57d7a2aa1221dd0bde14ea53889a3511f70cc899ac6f.mp3?f=Q%26A%20July%20corrected%20final.%20mp3.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:23:46</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230729232818</itunes:order>
</item>	
<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">87406711</guid>
			<title>#083: Alan Rockefeller Talks Fungal Genetics, Taxonomy, And Identification</title>
			<description>Recorded after a mushroom foray at this year's Mycofest, I sit down with Alan Rockefeller to discuss Psilocybe taxonomy, wood lover's paralysis, the enigma strain, and fungal accumulation of heavy metals. 



Alan's website: https://www.mycena.llc/
Jason Slot - https://plantpath.osu.edu/our-people/jason-c-slot
DNA sequencing - https://ohiomushroomsociety.wordpress.com/

Hoosier Mushroom Society - https://hoosiermushrooms.org/index.php?/profile/3-stephen-russell/

Entheogen Genome Project - https://www.entheome.org/

Felix Blei - Simultaneous Production of Psilocybin and a Cocktail of β‐Carboline Monoamine Oxidase Inhibitors in “Magic” Mushrooms - https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7003923/

Psilocybe Niveo-tropicalis - https://mushroomobserver.org/observations/520898

Alan's Facebook Group - https://www.facebook.com/groups/MushID/</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2023 23:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://c1.kemono.party/data/37/f7/37f7e3949cd61ca14abaeea122c6ed5a1d80c876377ef0c11b514662c9250f4e.mp3?f=Alan%20final%20patreon.mp3" length="158334976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>01:03:05</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:order>20230808234342</itunes:order>
</item>		

	</channel>
</rss>
