<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>The Rachman Review</title>
		<link>https://web.24syv.dk/channels/88</link>
		<description>Gideon Rachman, the Financial Times chief foreign affairs columnist talks to the decision-makers and thinkers who are shaping world affairs. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
		<language>da-DK</language>
		<itunes:image href="https://assets.listentonews.com/uploads/provider/logo/340/-k0m8dyrh-rachreviewcoverpink.png"/>
		<item>
			<title>Introducing: Swamp Notes from The FT News Briefing</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65b938506764420017f8c0c4/media.mp3</link>
			<description>If you have questions about this year's US presidential election, we have answers.Swamp Notes is a new podcast from the FT News Briefing. Listen every Saturday morning as our journalists analyse and discuss the latest happenings in US politics. We’ll go beyond the horse race for the White House and offer a global perspective on the election.  You can subscribe to Swamp Notes here or wherever you get your podcasts. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65b938506764420017f8c0c4/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:01:11</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65b938506764420017f8c0c4/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Germans push back against extremist AfD</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65ba88fec7d0d30016d86881/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Germans have been staging mass protests against the far-right ideology of the AfD party. This followed revelations about a meeting late last year in which the party and its backers discussed the potential for mass deportations of people of foreign origin. Gideon discusses whether this could be a turning point in German politics with international affairs analyst Constanze Stelzenmüller. Clip: The GuardianFree links to read more on this topic: In praise of mass immigrationGerman far right defeated in regional electionGermany’s top court paves way for financing ban on extremist political partiesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65ba88fec7d0d30016d86881/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65ba88fec7d0d30016d86881/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The battle for the control of Poland’s institutions</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65b15c9bbed2b300175030cc/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Tusk’s re-election cheered democrats across Europe and paved the way for the biggest change in Poland since the fall of communism. He’s hoping to rebuild the country's institutions and began with a clear-out of state TV that had become a mouthpiece for the previous government. Now he's waging war with the president and constitutional court. Ben Hall, the FT’s Europe editor, discusses Tusk’s first month in office and what lies ahead with Andrzej Bobiński, managing director of Polityka Insight. Clips: CNBC, tvpFree links to read more on this topic:EU to sidestep Polish president’s veto to release billions in fundingPoland’s escalating power strugglePoland’s ‘iron broom’ shows that democrats can bite backSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65b15c9bbed2b300175030cc/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 05:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65b15c9bbed2b300175030cc/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Introducing Untold: The Retreat</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65a6c7a54584ae001781191b/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Introducing Untold, a new podcast from the special investigations team at the Financial Times. In its first series, The Retreat, host Madison Marriage examines the world of the Goenka network, which promotes a type of intensive meditation known as Vipassana. Thousands of people go on Goenka retreats every year. People rave about them. But some people go to these meditation retreats, and they suffer. They might feel a deep sense of terror, or a break with reality. And on the other side, they’re not themselves anymore. Untold: The Retreat launches Jan. 24.Subscribe and listen on: Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65a6c7a54584ae001781191b/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 05:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:01:57</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65a6c7a54584ae001781191b/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Putin’s nemesis in the west</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65a7da44dbbf3f0016de04a7/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Bill Browder tells Gideon the story of his battle against Russian corruption, which took off when his lawyer was murdered in a Russian prison in 2009. The war in Ukraine has turbocharged his campaign. Can he now take it further to persuade western governments to use frozen Russian assets for the benefit of Ukraine? Clip: World Economic ForumFree links to read more on this topic:Washington puts forward G7 plan to confiscate $300bn in Russian assetsThe west would harm itself with rash seizures of frozen Russian assetsWe must keep fighting Russia with banks as well as tanksFreezing Order — Bill Browder on the trail of dirty Russian moneySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65a7da44dbbf3f0016de04a7/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 05:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:37</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65a7da44dbbf3f0016de04a7/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can a wider Middle East war be averted?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/659ed5a981017600157c6163/media.mp3</link>
			<description>As Israel continues its offensive against Hamas in the Gaza Strip, more and more regional actors are being drawn in, from the Houthis in Yemen, to Isis in Iraq and Syria. Gideon discusses whether a widening regional war can be averted with Kim Ghattas, distinguished fellow at Columbia University's Institute of Global Politics. Clip: ReutersFree links to read more on this topic:US intensifies efforts to prevent Middle East conflagrationSenior Hizbollah and Hamas figures killed as fears grow of regional warThe edge of the abyss looms in the Middle EastSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/659ed5a981017600157c6163/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:58</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/659ed5a981017600157c6163/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The future of Europe</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/659590fd458bbd001500bf4f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>It's an important year for the European Union, which holds parliamentary elections in June. As geopolitical turbulence continues to test the strength of global alliances, will Europe pursue further integration or start to pull apart? Gideon discusses these questions, and the role played by European Commission presidents, past and present, with Charles Grant, director of the Centre for European Reform in London. Clip: European CommissionFree links to read more on this topic:Jacques Delors, who drove EU integration, dies at 98How migration is pushing Europe to the rightEU readies €20bn plan B to fund UkraineUkraine and its backers need a credible path to victorySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Simon Panayi.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/659590fd458bbd001500bf4f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/659590fd458bbd001500bf4f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The world in 2024</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6583161459de86001792f5a4/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Who will win the US presidential election? Will China continue its rapprochement with the west? What are the prospects for an end to the wars in Ukraine and Gaza? Gideon discusses these and other questions with the FT’s Martin Wolf, Karin von Hippel, director-general of the Royal United Services Institute, and Ian Bremmer, president of the Eurasia Group. Clip: CNNFree links to read more on this topic:Americans won’t be terrified into rejecting TrumpTime is of the essence in defending UkraineAmerica’s cultural supremacy and geopolitical weaknessPeace is impossible without resolving the leadership vacuum in Israel and GazaThe US retains the economic advantage in its rivalry with ChinaSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6583161459de86001792f5a4/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 05:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6583161459de86001792f5a4/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>COP28: is the Dubai deal enough for the climate?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6579c48c7a12a8001272c0ca/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Countries at the COP 28 climate summit in Dubai have reached a deal to transition away from fossil fuels. Gideon speaks to the FT’s Simon Mundy, who’s in Dubai covering the talks, about the agreement. Will it actually help the world reach global net zero emissions by 2050? You can raise money for the FT's charity, the Financial Literacy and Inclusion Campaign, by bidding to have lunch with Gideon or one of his colleagues at top restaurants which are donating meals for an excellent cause. Go to ft.com/appeal to see what's on offer.Free links:Countries reach ‘historic’ COP28 deal to transition from fossil fuelsCOP’s love-hate relationship with businessCOP28 president denies using UN climate summit to pitch oil dealsCOP28: The struggle to say ‘fossil fuels’ out loudSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe. Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon, Persis Love and Manuela Saragosa. Sound design is by Jake Fielding.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6579c48c7a12a8001272c0ca/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6579c48c7a12a8001272c0ca/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden and Xi mend ties</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65709ebe9c60b600119baa13/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A recent visit to the US by China’s president Xi Jinping has raised hopes of a bilateral rapprochement. But how stable is this more positive relationship and can a conflict over Taiwan be averted? Gideon discusses these questions with Washington-based China experts Evan Medeiros and Jude Blanchette. Clip: CNBCFree links to read more on this topic:America and a crumbling global orderMoody’s cuts China’s credit outlook to negativeUS, UK and Australia move to track ‘emerging threats’ in spaceEU must stand up for Taiwan at China summitSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65709ebe9c60b600119baa13/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65709ebe9c60b600119baa13/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trump closes in on a second term in office</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6567688a82b9f700125d3a89/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to FT colleague Ed Luce and Susan Glasser of The New Yorker about Donald Trump’s campaign to be the Republican nominee in next year’s US presidential election. Is his success all but assured and, if so, what does this mean for Joe Biden’s chances of re-election? Looking further ahead, what would a second Trump presidency mean for American democracy?Clip: CNNFree links to read more on this topic:The Nikki Haley wild card for 2024Ron DeSantis leads Donald Trump and Joe Biden in $250mn 2024 election advertising raceBiden can’t spin his way to re-electionDonald Trump would gut Joe Biden’s landmark IRA climate law if electedSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6567688a82b9f700125d3a89/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6567688a82b9f700125d3a89/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How united are Arab and Muslim leaders on Gaza?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/655cec37934612001210564e/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The war in Gaza has provoked mass demonstrations across the Arab and Muslim world and exposed the policy failings of regional leaders. Gideon discusses regional leaders’ response to the crisis with Sanam Vakil, director of the Middle East Programme at Chatham House in London. Is there now sufficient unity to bring about a new plan for Middle East peace? Clips: NBC News, Al-JazeeraFree links to read more on this topic:Israel, Oppenheimer and the laws of warThe world must start preparing for peacemaking in the Middle EastIsrael’s government meets as Joe Biden says Hamas hostage deal is closeArab foreign ministers press China to support end to Israel-Hamas fightingSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/655cec37934612001210564e/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/655cec37934612001210564e/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is the balance tilting towards Russia in Ukraine?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6554d5905eb5d3001298a846/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Some have described Russia’s war against Ukraine as being at a stalemate. But one side could quickly gain the upper hand. Gideon discusses the strengths and weaknesses of both sides with Jack Watling of the Royal United Services Institute in London. Clips: Deutche Welle; NBC NewsFree links to read more on this topic:Ukraine’s counteroffensive against Russia in maps — latest updatesRussia’s war economy leaves businesses starved of labourUkraine reaches deal with insurers for grain shipmentsDenmark could block Russian oil tankers from reaching marketsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6554d5905eb5d3001298a846/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6554d5905eb5d3001298a846/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Who will run Gaza once the war is over?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/654bae701111a400126c339a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Emile Hokayem, senior fellow at the International Institute for Strategic Studies in London, about Israel’s military campaign in Gaza. How long is it likely to last and what will be the repercussions for Israel and the wider region? Clips: Channel 4 News; AFPFree links to read more on this topic:Iran’s interests are trumping the Palestinian tragedyFrom the US to Ukraine, the Gaza war will change the world‘Dead man walking’: How Yahya Sinwar deceived Israel for decadesGaza: the history of an embattled territorySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/654bae701111a400126c339a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/654bae701111a400126c339a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The global power of the dollar </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65427d0b58f3b5001282f45f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Wally Adeyemo, US deputy Treasury Secretary, about the power of US financial sanctions to punish autocrats and dictators and curb terrorism. What exactly are these sanctions designed to do and how effective are they? Clip: PBSFree links to read more on this topic:US pushes allies for more sanctions on HamasChina capitalises on US sanctions in fight to dethrone dollarRussia is increasingly using China’s currency to evade sanctionsQatar’s super-fixer role in Israel-Hamas war brings praise and scrutinySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Simon Panayi.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65427d0b58f3b5001282f45f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 05:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65427d0b58f3b5001282f45f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Coups make a comeback in Africa</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6537a3de1a09ea00126a44f2/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Comfort Ero, president of the International Crisis Group, about what’s behind the recent resurgence of military coups in the Sahel region. Clip: BBCFree links to read more on this topic:US signals intention to engage with Niger juntaWhere is the next African coup?Niger is the graveyard of French policy in the SahelEthiopia’s plan to rebuild in the wake of a ‘brutal’ warSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6537a3de1a09ea00126a44f2/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6537a3de1a09ea00126a44f2/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can the Gaza conflict be contained?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/652ff9208333180013ee8ce1/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Baroness Catherine Ashton, former high representative of the EU on foreign affairs, about the role of diplomacy in helping to contain the Israel-Gaza conflict. Clip: The White HouseFree links to read more on this topic:The Israel-Hamas war in maps: latest updatesHumanity must prevail in GazaSupporting Israel and protecting Palestinians are not contradictory policiesIran is positioning itself to benefit from the Israel-Gaza conflictSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/652ff9208333180013ee8ce1/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/652ff9208333180013ee8ce1/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Israel and Gaza at war</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65267c631a58c900121ce1d4/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the historian and writer Lawrence Freedman about what led to the catastrophic events of the past week in Israel and what options the Netanyahu government has to respond to Hamas's deadly attack. Clips: 11Alive; NBC NewsFree links to read more on this topic:The Israel-Hamas conflict in maps‘Nothing is normal any more’: war with Hamas reshapes life in IsraelA bitter blame game will follow Israel’s wartime unityAll involved in the Israel-Hamas conflict should heed the warnings of 1982Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65267c631a58c900121ce1d4/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65267c631a58c900121ce1d4/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The problem with Bidenomics</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/651d9288de8b670011152536/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Will Bidenomics help the US Democrats win another term in office? Will the policies be effective in tackling the climate crisis? Adam Posen, president of the Peterson Institute for International Economics, thinks not. In the last in our series on Bidenomics, he tells Gideon why offering incentives to private sector businesses is, in his view, a bad strategy.Free links to read more on this topic:John Kerry: Energy transition is the ‘new industrial revolution’Adam Posen: ‘Russia and North Korea worked hard to be self-sufficient, it has not turned out well for them’The west shouldn’t give up on ‘gentle commerce’ just yetWTO warns about fragmentation of global trade into allied blocsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/651d9288de8b670011152536/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/651d9288de8b670011152536/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bidenomics and global trade</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/651426e7f134e30011aa29fc/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In the second of our three-part series, Gideon talks to WTO chief Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala about the impact of Bidenomics on countries' attitudes to free and open global trade and the WTO's role in protecting this. Clip: France 24Free links to read more on this topic:Western companies take slow steps towards China ‘de-risking’South American leaders issue ultimatum on EU trade pactUS and China to launch economy and finance working groups to stabilise tiesGlobal trade falls at fastest pace since pandemicModels can mislead us on the impact of global tradeSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/651426e7f134e30011aa29fc/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/651426e7f134e30011aa29fc/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What is Bidenomics and is it working?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/650b15ccc7a09c0011a4eb97/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In the first of a three-part series on Bidenomics, Gideon talks to Brian Deese, former head of the National Economic Council in the Biden White House. They discuss how big a change of direction this was for the US, what motivated the policy and whether it is working well enough to convince American voters to re-elect Joe Biden next year. Clip: Biden-Harris 24Free links to read more on this topic:White House embraces ‘Bidenomics’ as it seeks to woo sceptical votersInvestors must realise the pendulum of history is swinging to BidenomicsWhy Joe Biden is the heir to TrumpInside the $220bn American cleantech project boomSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/650b15ccc7a09c0011a4eb97/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/650b15ccc7a09c0011a4eb97/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Coming soon: Can AI help us speak to animals? </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65019bd4d614850011741803/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Subscribe now to the FT's Tech Tonic podcast: Some scientists believe that rapid advances in artificial intelligence may also hold the key to decoding animal sounds, allowing us to ‘translate’ them into human language. In a new season of Tech Tonic, FT innovation editor John Thornhill and series producer Persis Love explore how the same technology that powers ChatGPT is being applied to research in animal communication. Could we one day learn to ‘speak whale’ or even chat with bats? And if so, can we trust ourselves to do so responsibly?Presented by John Thornhill, produced by Persis Love, sound design by Breen Turner and Sam Giovinco. The executive producer is Manuela Saragosa and Cheryl Brumley is the FT’s head of audio. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65019bd4d614850011741803/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:01:09</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65019bd4d614850011741803/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Post-Brexit Britain</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6501e11dc8bec000123759a2/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Opinion polls now suggest that about two-thirds of British people think that Brexit has failed. So was it all a terrible mistake? Gideon talks to FT colleague Peter Foster about his new book, What Went Wrong With Brexit: And What We Can Do About ItClip: BBCFree links to read more on this topic:UK SMEs not ready for ‘avalanche’ of Brexit 2.0 rules and taxesLondon and the fight for its future as a fashion hubThe EU’s transformations will reshape its ‘British question’ too EU and UK to unveil €1bn in N Ireland funding to boost reconciliationSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6501e11dc8bec000123759a2/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6501e11dc8bec000123759a2/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The nuclear and biological weapons threat</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64f8b9e1b20f810011cea789/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Are our politicians doing enough to protect humanity from the potential risk of a nuclear war, a deadly pandemic or AI without guardrails? Gideon discusses these risks with Jason Matheny, president of the Rand Corporation in California and former director for technology policy on President Joe Biden’s National Security Council.Clips: YahooFinance; Dr Strangelove, Columbia Pictures (1964)Free links to read more on this topic:The US and Iran look for de-escalationRegulating artificial intelligence is a 4D challengeUS seeks to deepen Tokyo-Seoul security links to boost Pacific deterrenceGovernments are waking up to biosecurity risks — but we must act fastSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64f8b9e1b20f810011cea789/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 04:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64f8b9e1b20f810011cea789/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden’s plan for a US-Saudi-Israeli peace deal</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64ef45870ead910011cb6cf7/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Senator Chris Murphy, a member of the US Senate Foreign Relations Committee, about the strength of bipartisan support for Ukraine and about President Joe Biden’s proposed “grand bargain” that could see Saudi Arabia and Israel normalise diplomatic relations in return for American security guarantees. Clip: CBS NewsFree links to read more on this topic:Joe Biden makes his big Middle East push: a Saudi Arabia-Israel pactGrand Delusion — America’s imposition on incompatible Middle East realitiesUkraine launches biggest drone attack yet inside Russian territorySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64ef45870ead910011cb6cf7/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 04:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64ef45870ead910011cb6cf7/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The end of Prigozhin </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64e637ac51c1f00012644ebe/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to political commentator and economist Sergei Guriev about the lessons Russians and the outside world will draw from the apparent killing of Yevgeny Prigozhin. How does this affect the stability of the Russian regime and the outlook for the war in Ukraine? Clip: BBCFree links to read more on this topic:When democratic spin conceals a descent into dictatorshipRussia files lawsuit against billionaire oligarch Andrey MelnichenkoRussia fires ‘General Armageddon’ in Wagner crackdownVladimir Putin plans meeting on Russian currency controls after rouble’s slideRead a transcript of this episode on FT.comSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64e637ac51c1f00012644ebe/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64e637ac51c1f00012644ebe/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Introducing: The Russian Banker</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64de556e2cfe01001105e207/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Who is Sergei Leontiev? To the US asylum system, he’s an exiled Russian banker who was persecuted by the state and forced to flee. To Russia, he’s said to be responsible for massive fraud. On The Russian Banker, a new series from the Financial Times, reporters Courtney Weaver and Stefania Palma try to uncover the truth, and find a story that tells us about Russia today and how people in the west build stories about who’s good and who’s bad. The Russian Banker is a special series that will run on the Behind the Money podcast starting Aug. 30. Listen to The Russian Banker by subscribing to the Behind the Money podcast here. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64de556e2cfe01001105e207/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:01:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64de556e2cfe01001105e207/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sanctions, global terror and the drugs trade</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64dcc45b264b910012b07609/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the FT’s Miles Johnson, author of a new book called Chasing Shadows about the links between international crime and geopolitics. They discuss how wars and the breakdown of democratic accountability have contributed to the ability of criminals to operate across borders and, in some cases, with state backing.Free links to read more on this topic:Wagner leader generated $250mn from sanctioned empireUsing crypto for crime is not a bug — it’s an industry featureEcuador gripped by fear after presidential candidate killingNorth Korea and the triads: gangsters, ghost ships and spies | FT FilmSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Lulu Smyth and Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64dcc45b264b910012b07609/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64dcc45b264b910012b07609/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Japan’s role in US-China strategic rivalry</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64d243c19ada620011832bcd/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China’s assertiveness on the global stage has reinvigorated economic and political ties between the US and Japan. Leo Lewis, the FT’s Asia business editor, discusses what’s changed with Rahm Emanuel, the US ambassador to Japan. Want more? Free links:Corporate Japan back in the hunt for US dealsJapan looks to expand diplomatic corps in overseas charm offensiveTokyo could win ‘not China’ global hub status — but it must want itSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts – please listen, rate and subscribe. Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Lulu Smyth and Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen Turner.  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64d243c19ada620011832bcd/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 04:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64d243c19ada620011832bcd/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Will Donald Trump end up in prison or the White House?  </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64ca817a3489580011c5e6ca/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Donald Trump was indicted this week on charges related to his attempts to overturn the results of the 2020 presidential election. But the former president is also in the running for the 2024 presidential election and polls suggest he’s likely to win the Republican nomination. Gideon Rachman is joined by Professor Peter Trubowitz, director of the US Centre at the London School of Economics and Political Science, to discuss what this all means for Trump’s future and the future of American democracy. Want more?Trump and American democracy’s time of trial  Donald Trump indicted for ‘unprecedented’ attempt to overturn US election The cases against Donald Trump  Subscribe to The Rachman review wherever you get your podcasts – please listen, rate and subscribe. Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Lulu Smyth and Manuela Saragosa. Sound design is by Breen Turner. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64ca817a3489580011c5e6ca/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64ca817a3489580011c5e6ca/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sudan power struggle risks turning into civil war</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64c1337d0a9bc7001171af7f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The Sudanese people are being held hostage by warring generals in a power struggle that has already lasted 100 days. With no solution in sight, the fighting risks drawing in outside actors like Russia’s Wagner group and destabilising neighbouring countries. David Pilling, the FT’s Africa editor, discusses the state of the conflict and its repercussions for the region with political analysts Kholood Khair and Alan Boswell. Clips: Middle East Eye; VOA; Human Rights Watch; Sky News.More on this topic:Sudan’s descent into violence poses new threat to volatile Sahel regionThe crisis in Sudan calls for a new model of humanitarian aid‘The garden of war’: horseback killers return to DarfurSudan conflict delivers fresh blow to China’s African lending strategySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by David Pilling. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64c1337d0a9bc7001171af7f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:29</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64c1337d0a9bc7001171af7f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Spain's lurch to the right </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64b821bccf6b170011127c5a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The government of Socialist leader Pedro Sánchez looks set to lose Sunday's elections to the centre-right People's party. But the PP may be unable to form a government without the participation of the hard-right party Vox. Henry Mance, standing in for Gideon Rachman, discusses what this will mean for Spain with the Madrid-based political scientist Pablo Simón. Clips: Deutsche Welle; El PaísMore on this topic:Franco’s ghost fails to scare Spain away from the hard right‘Spain first’: Vox party on brink of sharing powerThe ex-Eta terrorist bringing down Pedro Sánchez in SpainWhy Spain’s election threatens the EU’s climate agendaSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Henry Mance. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64b821bccf6b170011127c5a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64b821bccf6b170011127c5a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Will this year’s climate talks be a washout?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64aee3ccd0183600113c7783/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The UAE, host of this year’s UN climate conference, has pushed for a “global stocktake” of progress towards Paris targets, aimed at triggering fresh climate action. But it has also been criticised for its choice of an oil executive, Sultan al-Jaber, as president of the talks. Henry Mance, standing in for Gideon Rachman, talks to Farhana Yamin, British lawyer and climate activist about what we can expect from COP28.Clips: COP 28, The National News, United NationsMore on this topic:UAE to set out vision for UN climate summitClimate graphic of the week: Global heat records alarm scientistsExtreme wildfires are here to stay. Can human beings really fight them?'Green nationalism' endangers the global energy transitionSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Henry Mance. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64aee3ccd0183600113c7783/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64aee3ccd0183600113c7783/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How much should we fear artificial intelligence?  </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64a5a2bdca46640010e2b27d/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Scientists have been sounding the alarm about the potentially catastrophic dangers posed by artificial intelligence. Gideon talks to Anu Bradford, professor at Columbia University and author of a forthcoming book on the global battle to regulate technology about the different approaches being taken in the US, Europe and China. Clips: Amanpour &amp;amp; company; C-SPANMore on this topic:How actors are losing their voices to AIWe must avoid the evils of social media with AIEuropean companies sound alarm over draft AI lawAI executives warn its threat to humanity rivals ‘pandemics and nuclear war’Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Simon Panayi. Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64a5a2bdca46640010e2b27d/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64a5a2bdca46640010e2b27d/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Has the Wagner revolt fatally undermined Putin?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/649c5231bd828b00113a7af0/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Edward Lucas, author and senior fellow at the Center for European Policy Analysis, about the stability of Vladimir Putin’s regime in Russia. With his weaknesses exposed by the Prigozhin rebellion, how will rival centres of power respond? Clip: BBCMore on this topic:The revolution will now be TelegrammedA huge humiliation’: failed Russian putsch exposes deep flaws in Putin’s regimeUkraine says ‘main event’ in counteroffensive still to comeWagner’s future in Africa in question after Russian mutinySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/649c5231bd828b00113a7af0/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 04:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/649c5231bd828b00113a7af0/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>When should countries intervene to prevent mass murder?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64934edf83b55d0010d13e00/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Indian opposition Congress politician and former diplomat Shashi Tharoor about the concept of the 'responsibility to protect', which allows countries to intervene militarily in order to protect a population from mass murder. This was first mooted by Kofi Annan in the late 1990s after the Rwandan genocide. Can it be applied today, and in what circumstances? Clips: Global News, C-SPANMore on this topic:Rwandan genocide fugitive arrested in South AfricaThere can be no impunity for the crime of aggression against Ukraine‘The garden of war’: horseback killers return to DarfurPol Pot’s prime minister loses appeal against genocide convictionSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64934edf83b55d0010d13e00/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64934edf83b55d0010d13e00/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Ukraine’s fightback could change the world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6489f564b69e4c0011a0afc7/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Karin von Hippel, director-general of the UK defence think-tank RUSI, about Ukraine’s counteroffensive and the discussions that are already taking place about a new world order once the fighting is over. Clips: Channel 4 NewsMore on this topic:Military briefing: Ukrainian troops make early gains against ‘well-prepared’ RussiansGermany’s first-ever security strategy names Russia as ‘greatest threat’ to peaceWestern allies plan to provide long-term security assurances to UkraineMilitary briefing: Russia has most to gain from Ukrainian dam breachSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6489f564b69e4c0011a0afc7/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6489f564b69e4c0011a0afc7/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>David Lammy on Britain’s place in the world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6480c6e1a9ca9500119f6d73/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon meets Britain’s shadow foreign secretary on the sidelines of the Shangri-La Dialogue, the main forum for discussion of security issues in the Indo-Pacific, in Singapore. They discuss Britain’s relations with China, Ukraine, Brexit and the Commonwealth. Clips: ShanghaiEye, CNAMore on this topic:US pledges to maintain military capacity to defend TaiwanThe Starmer Project: Labour’s surprisingly bold economic agendaUK seeks to revive post-Brexit trade links with Latin AmericaSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6480c6e1a9ca9500119f6d73/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 04:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6480c6e1a9ca9500119f6d73/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is the Ukraine war reaching a turning point?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64779d2062b0900011d404a0/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the FT’s Chris Miller about the recent upsurge in military operations between Ukraine and Russia. Is this the start of Kyiv’s long-awaited offensive and if so, what would constitute a successful fightback? Clip: NBCMore on this topic:Military briefing: Ukraine’s daring ‘shaping operations’ stretch Russian defencesRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesF-16s might not win Ukraine’s war, but they promise a more equal fightRussia claims it ‘fully liquidated’ pro-Kyiv militias who crossed borderSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64779d2062b0900011d404a0/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:17:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/64779d2062b0900011d404a0/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Modi’s moment in the spotlight</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/646e29791740730011d92804/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to strategist Raja Mohan about India’s rising geopolitical influence. As the countries of the world form alliances to counterbalance the power of China, India is being courted for its support. How is India responding, and what are the prospects that it could one day become a superpower itself? Clips: DD IndiaMore on this topic:The G7 must accept that it cannot run the worldBBC accused of defaming Indian PM Narendra Modi in Delhi lawsuitThis is the hour of the global southSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Jake FieldingRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/646e29791740730011d92804/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:22</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/646e29791740730011d92804/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>China’s next generation</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6464d3de09cd110011e1129f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to economist Keyu Jin about China’s goal of becoming the world’s biggest economy despite a falling population, the impact of the deterioration in US-China relations, and the way in which the aspirations of its younger generation are shaping policy in Beijing. The podcast was recorded in collaboration with Intelligence Squared. Clips: CGTN; Sky NewsMore on this topic:Xi Jinping’s Taiwan ambitions threaten China’s riseChinese tech entrepreneurs go on global offensiveChina’s raids on foreign firms hurt its own interestsChina’s economic recovery in doubt as industrial output falls shortSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6464d3de09cd110011e1129f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6464d3de09cd110011e1129f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Putin’s historical magical mystery tour</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/645bd6b562ead3001195da6b/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Russia expert Fiona Hill about the forthcoming Ukrainian counter-offensive, the state of Russia and the similarities between the leadership styles of Donald Trump and Vladimir Putin. Clips: Daily Telegraph, PBSMore on this topic:Russia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesUS rejects Kremlin claims it was behind drone attackRussian spy network smuggles sensitive EU tech despite sanctionsChina vows to retaliate against EU sanctions on its companiesIt is now battered Ukraine’s turn for an offensiveSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner. Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/645bd6b562ead3001195da6b/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 04:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/645bd6b562ead3001195da6b/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How far will the rehabilitation of Assad go? </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/645299c0cba1b400114068d5/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Leaders in the UAE, Saudi Arabia and Jordan have decided that they need to work with the regime in Syria to solve problems ranging from the return of refugees to curbing the local drugs trade. Gideon talks to Kim Ghattas about what has motivated this change of strategy and its chance of success in helping restore stability to the region. Clip: WSJMore on this topic:Arab world weighs price for Assad’s rehabilitationIran’s president visits Syria as he seeks to bolster Tehran’s sway over allySpy chief’s daughter highlights UN’s tangled relations with Syrian regimeSyria’s state capture: the rising influence of Mrs AssadRussia’s myth-making in Syria was a template for the horrors in UkraineSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/645299c0cba1b400114068d5/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 04:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/645299c0cba1b400114068d5/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is Turkey about to see the end of the Erdoğan era?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/644939f7e02da800114591bb/media.mp3</link>
			<description>President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan has been in power for 20 years - and he has every intention of carrying on. But the Turkish leader faces a serious challenge in May’s general election. A change at the top in Turkey could also have profound implications for the wider region. But would Erdoğan accept defeat? Gideon hears from Soner Cagaptay at the Washington Institute for Near East Policy about Erdoğan's psychology, his political following and how a united opposition could finally unseat him.Clips: Middle East Eye, CNNRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/644939f7e02da800114591bb/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/644939f7e02da800114591bb/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is there such a thing as a rules-based international order? </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/644025dbf659a80010a54aa2/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the US political theorist John Ikenberry about why the Ukraine war has been both a challenge and a spur for those who want to see liberal democratic values thrive. Clip: Global NewsMore on this topic:The new Washington consensusLula vows partnership with China to ‘balance world geopolitics’‘Dare to fight’: Xi Jinping unveils China’s new world orderIt is time to cut Russia out of the global financial systemSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/644025dbf659a80010a54aa2/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 04:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/644025dbf659a80010a54aa2/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Macron’s flawed diplomacy in China</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6436eb4fad0c130010e36710/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Emmanuel Macron sparked an international backlash over remarks he made to the press about Taiwan after a visit to China. The French president is also facing growing opposition at home after he pushed through an unpopular policy to raise the retirement age. Gideon talks to Célia Belin of the European Council on Foreign Relations about Macron’s image, his diplomatic gaffes and his struggle to win support for his policies at home. Clips: Sky, Daily Telegraph.More on this topic:Macron allies defend his comments on TaiwanTea with Xi: Macron gets personal touch as China visit highlights EU differencesThe jilted ally behind Macron’s pensions crisisSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6436eb4fad0c130010e36710/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6436eb4fad0c130010e36710/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine's other battleground: the economy</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/642db3b0c7800c00110689c7/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Hlib Vyshlinsky, director of Ukraine's Centre for Economic Strategy, about keeping Ukraine's economy alive while the war goes on. Despite a shortage of cash and labour, efforts are under way to try to build a more dynamic and transparent economy when the fighting is over.Clips: CTV, SkyMore on this topic:The breaking and making of UkraineSaving Ukraine’s economy: the grain giant fighting for survivalUkraine clinches $15.6bn IMF loanSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/642db3b0c7800c00110689c7/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 04:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/642db3b0c7800c00110689c7/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The rise and fall of Yevgeny Prigozhin  </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/642471ca4362ac0011496073/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the FT’s Max Seddon and Miles Johnson about Russia’s Wagner paramilitary group and its once secretive leader Yevgeny Prigozhin. They discuss how Prigozhin came to prominence during the fighting around Bakhmut in Ukraine and whether he can hold on to his position of influence with Russia’s president Vladimir Putin. Clips: euronews; NBC; CNNMore on this topic:‘Like Icarus’: Russian mercenary Yevgeny Prigozhin falls foul of Kremlin old guardWagner leader generated $250mn from sanctioned empireWagner Inc: a Russian warlord and his lawyersSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe. Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/642471ca4362ac0011496073/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 04:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/642471ca4362ac0011496073/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Divided Iran makes peace with its neighbours</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/641b269a0ea8a60011783567/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the FT’s Middle East editor Andrew England about his recent visit to Iran in the aftermath of some of the worst unrest since the establishment of the Islamic Republic in 1979. Iran’s reconciliation with Saudi Arabia and its growing trade with Russia may help the regime survive, but relations with the west have plummeted and hopes for a revival of the nuclear deal look bleak.Clips: Reuters; BBCRead More on this topic:Exiled son of Iran’s last shah steps up to lead galvanised diasporaSaudi rapprochement with Iran is an exercise in buying timeIran agrees to reinstall IAEA cameras at nuclear facilitiesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/641b269a0ea8a60011783567/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 14:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/641b269a0ea8a60011783567/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Israeli democracy at a crossroads </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6411fe6349ffab0011c28e47/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Israeli journalist Nadav Eyal tells Gideon why he believes Israel is on course for a full-blown constitutional crisis. The Netanyahu government’s plan to curtail the power of the judiciary, he says, will remove democratic checks and balances that are crucial for the survival of a liberal democracy. Opponents include business, the military and the country's intellectual elite, as well as many middle-class Israelis who will not accept the proposed changes.Clips: Anadolu Agency; NBCProtests by Israeli reservists raise stakes in battle over judicial changesIlliberal democracy comes to IsraelUS defence secretary cuts short trip to Israel ahead of mass protestsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6411fe6349ffab0011c28e47/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 05:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6411fe6349ffab0011c28e47/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is Mexico slipping into autocracy?  </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6408cf6623b51e0011d48709/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to academic and writer Denise Dresser about President Andrés Manuel López Obrador’s autocratic tendencies and why she thinks the leader she once voted for is dismantling democracy in Mexico. Clips: France 24, Andrés Manuel López Obrador Amlo’s strongman act is weakening MexicoThousands protest in Mexico against cuts to electoral watchdogMexico’s former security chief convicted in US of helping cartel smuggle drugsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6408cf6623b51e0011d48709/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 05:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6408cf6623b51e0011d48709/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bill Gates on Ukraine’s ‘shock to the system’</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63ffa3aeb6e2f50011503779/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The Microsoft co-founder and philanthropist talks to Gideon about his efforts to keep global development goals alive amid rising geopolitical tensions. They discuss shrinking aid budgets, climate, technology, China-US tensions and whether Gates remains an optimist about the future.Bill Gates warns Ukraine war is sapping Europe’s foreign aid budgetsElon Musk’s Twitter is ‘stirring up’ digital polarisation, says Bill GatesBill Gates loves trashSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63ffa3aeb6e2f50011503779/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 05:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63ffa3aeb6e2f50011503779/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine series: the battle for Bakhmut</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63f62813d9d27400129cc0df/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Christopher Miller moved to the Ukrainian city of Bakhmut in 2010 as a volunteer for the US Peace Corps. Now an FT correspondent in Kyiv, he tells Gideon about how the eastern city came to play a central role in the war and how he sees the conflict unfolding in the coming months.Clips: CNNMore on this topic:A 12-year journey to the heart of the war in Ukraine‘Hell. Just hell’: Ukraine and Russia’s war of attrition over BakhmutBehind the Money podcast: ​​The costs of Russia’s invasion of UkraineHow Ukrainian photographers captured a year of conflictRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63f62813d9d27400129cc0df/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63f62813d9d27400129cc0df/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine series: how long will the war last?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63ed247f91559c00113d36dc/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In the second episode in our special series, Gideon talks to war historian Hein Goemans about what it would take to end the fighting in Ukraine. FT podcast surveyMore on this topic:A year of war in Ukraine has left Europe’s armouries dryMilitary briefing: Russia prepares Ukraine spring offensiveThe keyboard warriors on Ukraine’s digital front lineRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63ed247f91559c00113d36dc/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 05:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63ed247f91559c00113d36dc/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine series: life in a war zone</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63e3d6b7803862001188080d/media.mp3</link>
			<description>In the first of a three-part series, Gideon talks to Ukraine MP Lesia Vasylenko about what it was like to wake up in a country at war, how Ukrainians surprised the world with their fightback, and the need for reparations and justice for the victims of Russia’s war crimes.More on this topic:FT podcast surveyVolodymyr Zelenskyy demands ‘wings for freedom’ as UK pledges fighter pilot trainingMilitary briefing: what the west’s shifting red lines mean for UkraineRussia’s budget deficit soars as energy revenues slump by almost halfRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe. Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63e3d6b7803862001188080d/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 05:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63e3d6b7803862001188080d/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to fix our flawed democracies</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63daaad2f6391d00115ea2f6/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Martin Wolf, the FT’s chief economics commentator, about his new book, The Crisis of Democratic Capitalism. They discuss why the post-war settlement between democratic governments and their people is no longer fit for purpose and what can be done to restore our faith in it.More on this topic:FT podcast surveyMartin Wolf: in defence of democratic capitalismThe great disruption has only just begunCEOs beware: cost-cutting isn’t the same as growthSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63daaad2f6391d00115ea2f6/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 05:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63daaad2f6391d00115ea2f6/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Philippines caught in the line of fire</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63d15e32eb0bad0010953688/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The Filipino people are paying a heavy price for regional tensions between China and the US, Philippine president Ferdinand Marcos Jr tells Gideon. He explains how he hopes to steer clear of conflict, build up the economy and focus on mitigating the economic damage caused by climate change.Clips: Inquirer.netMore on this topic:Ferdinand Marcos Jr says Taiwan tensions ‘very, very worrisome’ for PhilippinesUS military deepens ties with Japan and Philippines to prepare for China threatChina and Philippines vow to handle maritime tensions with ‘friendly consultations’US vice-president visits Philippine island off contested South China SeaSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe. Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63d15e32eb0bad0010953688/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 05:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63d15e32eb0bad0010953688/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The global battle against impunity </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63c84153eb0a7a00107cd962/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The war in Ukraine has had dire consequences for millions of people beyond Europe. Gideon talks to David Miliband, IRC president, about why Putin's challenge to the world order must not go unpunished.Clips: CNNMore on this topic:Geopolitics threatens to destroy the world Davos madeWar in Tigray may have killed 600,000 people, peace mediator saysHow the law finally caught up with notorious human trafficker KidaneSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe. Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63c84153eb0a7a00107cd962/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 05:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63c84153eb0a7a00107cd962/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America’s hard right</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63bf056d6c0bc80010702edf/media.mp3</link>
			<description>A small group of Republican party zealots, backed by former president Donald Trump, have forced their way into a position of power in the US Congress. Gideon talks to Jacob Heilbrunn, editor of the National Interest magazine in Washington and senior fellow at the Atlantic Council, about what they are seeking to achieve and whether they will end up playing into the hands of President Joe Biden if he seeks re-election.Clips: ABC, CNN More on this topic:Speaker Kevin McCarthy faces tough first week seeking to unify RepublicansJoe Biden’s claim to presidential greatnessThe debt ceiling is scarier this timeSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63bf056d6c0bc80010702edf/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63bf056d6c0bc80010702edf/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What next for Putin’s Russia?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63b5c4894e6e5100117b316e/media.mp3</link>
			<description>How has Russia changed since Putin embarked on his Ukraine war nearly a year ago? Gideon talks to Angela Stent of Georgetown University about the origins of Russia’s imperialist ambitions, its rupture with Europe and reliance on revived alliances with the global south.Clips: @Rumoaohepta7; Channel 4 News More on this topic: ‘Untrainable’: Russian army faces backlash over conscripts’ death in Ukraine attackTurning the tide in Russia’s war on UkraineRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Jake FieldingRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63b5c4894e6e5100117b316e/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63b5c4894e6e5100117b316e/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2022 Year In Review</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63a2dede6bde7700111ecbce/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon Rachman is joined by a panel of colleagues: FT editor Roula Khalaf, Moscow correspondent Max Seddon and US editor Edward Luce. This year was defined by Vladimir Putin's invasion of Ukraine. Will 2023 be any different? Meanwhile, in China, Xi Jinping was confirmed for a third term as the country's leader, with many believing he's now set to rule for life. Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon and Howie Shannon. The sound engineer was Breen Turner. -Read the latest on https://www.ft.com/world/uk-Follow @gideonrachman-Subscribe to https://www.ft.com/newslettersRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63a2dede6bde7700111ecbce/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 05:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63a2dede6bde7700111ecbce/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Qatar’s soft power play</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/639a19beb0e35400112817fc/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Qatar’s decision to host the World Cup was mired in controversy from the start but ultimately seems to have paid off, bringing the tiny Gulf emirate new friends and winning over old enemies. Gideon talks to Simeon Kerr, the FT’s Gulf correspondent, about what motivates the emirate to seek to deploy its vast wealth for political ends.Clips: Qatar Airways; France 24 More on this topic:Qatar wooed EU lawmakers ahead of football World CupHow the unlikeliest World Cup ever came to beQatar faces the harsh glare of World Cup publicityQatar World Cup provides rare source of unity to Arab statesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/639a19beb0e35400112817fc/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/639a19beb0e35400112817fc/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How threatened is Australia by the rise of China?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6390fe1deaccaf00110f40e3/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Australia’s relations with China have taken a dive in recent years, forcing Canberra to reassess regional security and trade ties. Gideon talks to Michael Fullilove, director of the Lowy Institute, Australia’s leading foreign-policy think-tank, about how Australia is adapting to the new reality.Clips: ABC, ChannelNewsAsia More on this topic:Australia, China and the judgment of the SolomonsAustralia’s defence dilemma: projecting force or provoking China?US to ‘deepen’ defence ties with Australia in face of China threatAustralian business hopeful of better ties with ChinaSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6390fe1deaccaf00110f40e3/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 05:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:15</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6390fe1deaccaf00110f40e3/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>China protests test the limits of Xi Jinping’s authority</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6387ab8cd1fc8600115c72ee/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Severe lockdowns associated with China’s zero-Covid policy have combined with economic woes to incite the most widespread protests since Tiananmen Square. President Xi Jinping is now under pressure to address this discontent. Gideon discusses what his options are with the FT’s Yuan Yang, who has recently returned to London from Beijing.Clips: BBCMore on this topic:Xi’s pandemic triumphalism returns to haunt himGuangzhou eases restrictions despite worsening Covid outbreakChina’s high youth unemployment stokes student Covid protestsRestless Beijingers rise up against Covid controlsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6387ab8cd1fc8600115c72ee/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 05:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6387ab8cd1fc8600115c72ee/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>90,000 migrants arrive in Italian ports</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/637e43d91e392f001051fbf5/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Italy has become one of the main entry points to the EU for irregular migrants but its new nationalist prime minister Giorgia Meloni has taken a hard line and is demanding Europe do more to help.Why has Meloni taken such a confrontational approach? Ben’s guest is Nicoletta Pirozzi, head of the EU programme at Italy’s Institute for International Affairs in Rome.Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Ben Hall. Produced by Fiona Symon and Howie Shannon. The sound engineer was Breen Turner. -Read the latest on https://www.ft.com/world/uk-Follow @gideonrachman -Subscribe to https://www.ft.com/newslettersRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/637e43d91e392f001051fbf5/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 05:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/637e43d91e392f001051fbf5/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Brazil’s Lula joins leftist leaders pushing for change in Latin America</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63752404a45feb0011afe72a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Brazil joins a group of Latin American countries that have elected leftwing leaders. What kind of change will they bring to the region and its relations with the rest of the world? Michael Stott, the FT’s Latin America editor, discusses these questions with Andrés Velasco, dean of the school of public policy at the London School of Economics and a former finance minister of Chile, and Chris Sabatini, senior fellow for Latin America at Chatham House in London.Clips: AP, VOA, BBC More on this topic:Lula seeks Brazil constitutional change to fund campaign pledgesAmazon destruction woes overshadow Brazil’s farming advancesChile’s Boric seeks ‘new path forward’ after voters reject constitutional changesLatin America moves to bring Venezuela’s Maduro in from the coldSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63752404a45feb0011afe72a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63752404a45feb0011afe72a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How the Ukraine war reshaped US alliances </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/636c09ec58edfe0012931b46/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Thomas Wright, director of strategic planning at the National Security Council in the Biden White House, tells Gideon how the war in Ukraine changed US thinking about the need for broader alliances.Clips: The White House, Channel 4 News More on this topic:Xi Jinping’s China and the rise of the ‘global west’US coal phaseout plan meets divided response at COP27China and the US remain locked in mutually assured co-operationSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/636c09ec58edfe0012931b46/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 05:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/636c09ec58edfe0012931b46/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>US midterms: Republicans on the rise</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6362be98509b7300125c02cc/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Joe Biden’s Democrats look set to lose control of Congress in this month's elections. But many of the Republicans poised to take office support Donald Trump's claim that the last presidential election was stolen. Gideon discusses his prospects for a return to the White House with journalist Susan Glasser, co-author of The Divider, a history of the Trump presidency.Clips: CNN, Forbes Breaking News More on this topic:Joe Biden fights to revive Democrats one week before midterm electionsThis will be the mother of all American midterm electionsBritain and America’s electoral geographies are brokenSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6362be98509b7300125c02cc/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6362be98509b7300125c02cc/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Xi consolidates his rule as economic problems mount</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/635979a58c5fe9001207766c/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to economist Linda Yueh of Oxford university about recent dramatic developments at the Chinese Communist party’s congress in Beijing. They discuss what the growing centralisation in China tells us about how Xi Jinping will handle the private sector, the property crisis and international tensions over Taiwan.Clips: CGTN; CNAMore on this topic:China’s limitless presidency means limited diplomacyChina’s growth stutters as exports fail to rescue economyChina’s wealthy activate escape plans as Xi Jinping extends ruleHit film Return to Dust has vanished from China’s cinemas. Why?Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/635979a58c5fe9001207766c/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:32:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/635979a58c5fe9001207766c/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>US-Saudi ties at an all-time low</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63503acc6c4ac100117abe8e/media.mp3</link>
			<description>There was outrage in Washington over Saudi Arabia’s decision to back Opec output cuts during a global energy crisis. What was the kingdom’s motive for putting its strategic partnership with the US at risk? As a regular visitor to Saudi Arabia, Emile Hokayem of the International Institute for Strategic Studies in London offers his view of the Saudi leader’s calculations and plans for a new global role for the country.Clips: France 24; CNN; Fox newsMore on this topic:The plight of expat workers at KPMG Saudi ArabiaJoe Biden’s limited room for manoeuvre on Saudi ArabiaThe new oil war: Opec moves against the USSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63503acc6c4ac100117abe8e/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63503acc6c4ac100117abe8e/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Russia's nuclear threat</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6347162e84830f0012f90fde/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Ukrainian cities have faced an onslaught of missiles from Russia this week in retaliation for the attack on the Kerch bridge that links Russia with occupied Crimea. Russia has threatened to go further and to use tactical nuclear weapons rather than face the defeat of its forces in Ukraine. But would it? Alexander Gabuev, a senior fellow for the Carnegie Endowment think-tank, tells Gideon he thinks Putin’s threat is deadly serious.Clips: BBCMore on this topic:Putin suggests Nord Stream gas exports to Europe could be restoredNato allies struggle to secure air defence systems for UkraineRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6347162e84830f0012f90fde/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 04:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:27</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6347162e84830f0012f90fde/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Protests show Iran’s social contract is broken</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/633db95db8bb2e00111cc2b7/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The death of a young woman detained by Iran’s ‘morality police’ has sparked nationwide protests that the government is struggling to control. Gideon talks to Iranian analyst Sanam Vakil about what the unrest tells us about the weakening authority of the regime that has been in place for the past 40 years.Clips: BBC, France 24More on this topic:How Iranian students are shaping anti regime protestsIran’s Ayatollah Khamenei blames US and Israel for street protestsMahsa Amini has become a potent symbol for women in IranSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Jake FieldingRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/633db95db8bb2e00111cc2b7/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/633db95db8bb2e00111cc2b7/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The remaking of Europe</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63348ab5559a970014e0a6ff/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Europe’s priorities have undergone a massive shift in response to Russia’s aggression against Ukraine. Gideon talks to political scientist Ivan Krastev about how central Europe is gaining influence within the EU as a result of the Ukraine war.Clips: United Nations; France24More on this topic:EU to put price cap on Russian oil in new sanctions packageThe 90km journey that changed the course of the war in UkraineDenmark, Germany and Poland warn of ‘sabotage’ after Nord Stream leaksEndless frictions with Brussels risk fuelling Euroscepticism in PolandThe EU should press Hungary hard on rule of lawSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner. Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63348ab5559a970014e0a6ff/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 04:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:32</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63348ab5559a970014e0a6ff/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What next for Global Britain?  </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/632b46eaafb41a00120b6d26/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Britain's new prime minister is facing huge challenges on both the domestic and international stage. Gideon talks to Bronwen Maddox, director of Chatham House, the Royal Institute of International Affairs, in London about how Liz Truss will deal with the Ukraine war, Brexit and relations with the US and China.Clips: Royal Family Channel; France 24More on this topic:Liz Truss admits UK trade deal with US is not on the agendaThe economic consequences of Liz TrussLiz Truss to launch UK defence review as she calls for Russian reparationsBritain enters the era of King Charles IIISubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/632b46eaafb41a00120b6d26/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/632b46eaafb41a00120b6d26/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Russia faces defeat in Ukraine</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/632206ab54c0ce0012517de4/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Ukraine’s rapid recapture of territory in recent days has put Russian forces on the back foot and raised the prospect of an early end to the war. Gideon talks to Lawrence Freedman, emeritus professor of war studies at King's College in London about the dramatic turnaround and what happens next.Clips from BBC, Russian state TVMore on this topicMilitary briefing - Ukraine offensive ‘dooms’ Russia’s aims for DonbasRussian army hobbled by shortage of soldiersUkraine faces ‘tough fight’ even as Russian forces retreat, says USRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/632206ab54c0ce0012517de4/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:27</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/632206ab54c0ce0012517de4/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Italy is facing a crucial election</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6317542f83710700135680a2/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Polls suggest that the largest single party will be the Brothers of Italy - and its leader Giorgia Meloni will therefore be prime minister. That’s causing consternation in some quarters because the party has roots in the fascist-influenced politics of post-war Italy. Gideon’s guest this week is Nathalie Tocci, the director of the Institute for International Affairs, a think-tank based in Rome.Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman.Produced by Howie Shannon. The sound engineer was Breen Turner. Read the latest on https://www.ft.com/world/ukFollow @gideonrachman Subscribe to https://www.ft.com/newslettersRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6317542f83710700135680a2/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 04:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6317542f83710700135680a2/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Will India soar or struggle in the coming years?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/630f95ad61dd900012373f8c/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon’s guest this week is Ramachandra Guha, who is often hailed as the most distinguished historian of modern India.He is also a noted critic of the government of Prime Minister Narendra Modi.Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman.Produced by Fiona Symon and Howie Shannon. The sound engineer was Breen Turner. -Read the latest on https://www.ft.com/world/uk-Follow @gideonrachman -Subscribe to https://www.ft.com/newslettersRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/630f95ad61dd900012373f8c/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/630f95ad61dd900012373f8c/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Who's winning the war in Ukraine?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63065ce6ef672b00125c214a/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Six months into the Ukraine war, Gideon talks to Phillips O'Brien, professor of strategic studies at the University of St Andrews, Scotland, about the balance of forces on each side. With Russian forces bogged down, is a Ukrainian victory now a possibility?Clips: The Guardian, Al Jazeera, The Aspen InstituteMore on this topic:Six months of war in Ukraine: ‘The enemy learned fast’Join the FT Telegram channel to receive Ukraine coverage alertsRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesThe global reach of Alexander DuginSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63065ce6ef672b00125c214a/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 04:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/63065ce6ef672b00125c214a/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Would China go to war over Taiwan?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62fd27a909158d001201c7d4/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Chinese-American academic Minxin Pei about China’s reaction to US House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s visit to Taiwan. What does it tell us about Xi Jinping’s leadership as he bids for a third term as president?Clips: The Sun; Daily TelegraphMore on this topic:Taiwan tensions force multinationals to rethink China riskChina ratchets up pressure on Taiwan after US congressional visitTaiwan greets Chinese military intimidation with parties rather than panicXi Jinping grasps ‘knife’ of internal security to complete grip on powerSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62fd27a909158d001201c7d4/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62fd27a909158d001201c7d4/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Whatever happened to Mandela’s dream for South Africa?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62f3ff857f77c400141ed555/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the South African writer and political activist, Songezo Zibi, about the need to build a coalition for change to help restore some of the high hopes that accompanied the end of apartheid.Clips: SABC, The SunMore on this topic:Bain barred from UK state contracts over ‘grave misconduct’ in South AfricaSouth Africa hopes private sector can help end Eskom power crisisSouth Africa’s Ramaphosa under fire after ranch burglary fuels questions over wealthHow three brothers ‘captured’ a countrySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62f3ff857f77c400141ed555/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 04:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:28:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62f3ff857f77c400141ed555/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to broker a deal between Russia and Ukraine</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62ea8f476c3e4e001294dec7/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Sergio Jaramillo was one of the architects behind Colombia’s landmark peace deal with Marxist guerrilla group Farc. Now, as a senior adviser at the European Institute of Peace, he explains if and how Ukraine and Russia could ever arrive at a ceasefire or peace negotiation. John Paul Rathbone, security and defence correspondent for the Financial Times, talks to Jaramillo about how negotiations are as important a part of military strategy as fighting on the battlefield, and what Europe should do to support Ukraine.Presented by John Paul Rathbone. Produced by Fiona Symon and Persis Love. Sound design by Breen TurnerClips: BBC, MSNBC, Associated Press﻿Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62ea8f476c3e4e001294dec7/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62ea8f476c3e4e001294dec7/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How social media platforms put profits before people</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62e1710fa677bf001343de2c/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Human rights lawyer Cori Crider co-founded Foxglove, a group that fights on behalf of those harmed by the misuse of technology. She talks to the FT’s Madhumita Murgia about why social media companies need to bear more of the cost for the poisonous content they host on their platforms.Clip: C-SPANWant to read more?A tale of two Facebook whistleblowersBig Tech makes concessions on EU’s new anti-disinformation codeEU approves groundbreaking rules to police Big Tech platformsCivil society must be part of the Digital Services ActSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen Turner﻿Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62e1710fa677bf001343de2c/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62e1710fa677bf001343de2c/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can Turkey help end the Ukraine grain crisis? </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62d849cf51a0c20013d3b60b/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Turkey’s president Recep Tayyip Erdoğan has been working hard to help open up an export route for Ukrainian grain via the Black Sea. But as he wins plaudits for this key mediating role, his nation is struggling with soaring inflation and a cost of living crisis. Andrew England, standing in for Gideon, talks to Asli Aydıntaşbaş of the European Council on Foreign Relations and Laura Pitel, the FT's Turkey correspondent, about what’s motivating Erdoğan.Want to read more?Erdoğan is an infuriating but indispensable allyUkraine grain deal and Syria top agenda for Putin’s talks with Iran and TurkeyFruit becomes a luxury in Erdoğan’s Turkey as inflation threatens re-election bidUkraine warns that only lifting Black Sea blockade can avert global food crisisSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62d849cf51a0c20013d3b60b/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62d849cf51a0c20013d3b60b/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Russia’s future: a giant Iran of Eurasia </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62cf05710e91d00011f0f5fa/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Alexander Gabuev, senior fellow at the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, tells Gideon why he believes Russia is destined to become a giant Iran of Eurasia. It will remain a significant military power, but one that is increasingly under the sway of China, the main destination for its energy exports.Clips: DW; Global NewsMore on this topic:Iran plans to provide drones to Russia for Ukraine war, says USPutin warns of ‘catastrophic’ energy crisis if west boosts sanctionsChina’s image loses its shine in EuropeSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62cf05710e91d00011f0f5fa/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62cf05710e91d00011f0f5fa/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine: a view from the Baltics  </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62c5c80ca908090012443224/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Kersti Kaljulaid, former president of Estonia, about the policy failures that led to the war in Ukraine. A weak response to Russia’s invasion of Georgia and Crimea gave Vladimir Putin the green light. Now the strength of Ukrainian resistance is giving the west another chance to &quot;put its house in order&quot;.Clips: Sky News, APMore on this topic:Europe’s new defence bloc: Nordics and Baltics unite in face of Russian threatEstonia’s PM says country would be ‘wiped from map’ under existing Nato plansWar in Ukraine: will the Baltics become the ‘new West Berlin’?Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by BreenRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62c5c80ca908090012443224/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 04:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:27</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62c5c80ca908090012443224/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Introducing: Hot Money</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62bc6ed0ad9470001548c4a6/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The FT just launched a new podcast on porn, power and profit. When FT reporter Patricia Nilsson started digging into the porn industry, she made a shocking discovery: nobody knew who controlled the biggest porn company in the world. Now, she and her editor, Alex Barker, reveal who is behind it and much more. This eight-part investigative podcast reveals the secret history of the adult business and the billionaires and financial institutions who shape it. Brought to you by the Financial Times and Pushkin. To listen to new episodes, search ‘Hot Money’ wherever you listen. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62bc6ed0ad9470001548c4a6/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 04:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:19</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62bc6ed0ad9470001548c4a6/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Wirecard: the investigation that brought down a German tech giant</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62bc78d5cf1ab400126c38a2/media.mp3</link>
			<description>It took years of digging and a lucky break to uncover the fraud at the heart of Wirecard. Gideon talks to Dan McCrum about the strange netherworld of financial speculators, private detectives, bumbling accountants and outright criminals that he encountered along the way.Clips: Bloomberg, Money TalksMore on this topic:Why we trust fraudstersLess work for EY auditors? What about more accountabilityWirecard middleman pleads guilty to hackingInside WirecardSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by BreenRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62bc78d5cf1ab400126c38a2/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 04:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:33:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62bc78d5cf1ab400126c38a2/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can EU unity on Ukraine hold?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62b355da8629780012e7b216/media.mp3</link>
			<description>European leaders have been united in their support for Ukraine against Russia’s aggression. But as costs mount they could face growing calls to compromise with Russia. Gideon talks to Ulrike Franke, senior policy fellow at the European Council on Foreign Relations, about how France and Germany in particular are handling the crisis. Clips: Euronews; CNN; France24More on this topic:Farewell to Russia and to the Sinatra doctrineOlaf Scholz says partnership with Putin’s Russia is ‘inconceivable’Ukraine weighs up impact of EU leaders’ trip to KyivSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by BreenRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62b355da8629780012e7b216/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62b355da8629780012e7b216/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Where money and power collide</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62aa14dd3c831c0012faedc5/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the billionaire investor Ray Dalio about the connections he's found between the rise and fall of markets and the rise and fall of nations. Clips: CBS, CNBC, BBCMore on this topic:  Policy errors of the 1970s echo in our timesFed begins quantitative tightening on unprecedented scaleTop investors split on direction of ‘tempestuous’ China’s marketsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by BreenRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62aa14dd3c831c0012faedc5/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62aa14dd3c831c0012faedc5/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Putin’s energy power play</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62a0e2cd9868ac001201d8e9/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Russia’s global power has rested in large part on its oil and gas reserves. Will Vladimir Putin’s decision to invade Ukraine and Europe’s decision to seek alternative supplies shrink this power irreparably? Gideon talks to the American expert Dan Yergin about the role played by energy in the Ukraine conflict and its implications for the rest of the world.Clips: BBC, ABC, Sky NewsMore on this topic:  Europe at risk of winter energy rationing, energy watchdog warnsLNG revolution: Germany’s plan to wean itself off Russian gas takes shapeSaudi Arabia is increasing supply — so why is the oil price holding firm?Trafigura warns oil prices could reach ‘parabolic state’ in threat to economySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62a0e2cd9868ac001201d8e9/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 04:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/62a0e2cd9868ac001201d8e9/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Poverty and inequality drive change in Latin America</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6297a137812a92001393d813/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Venezuelan economist Moisés Naím about the reasons for the collapse of the political centre in Latin America, and about the tactics used by populist politicians to rise to power in the region and beyond.Clips: Euronews; AP; Al Jazeera; NBC; Andrés Manuel López Obrador channelWant to read more?How the Colombia election could change Latin AmericaColombia’s Rodolfo Hernández goes from also-ran to the brink of powerConservative young Brazilians complicate Lula’s path to presidencySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen Turner﻿Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6297a137812a92001393d813/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 04:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/6297a137812a92001393d813/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine and the global food emergency</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/628e6a3ca80ea90015911b24/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Russia’s blockade of the port of Odesa is preventing Ukraine from exporting vital supplies of grain to a hungry world. A failure to resolve the problem will lead to food price rises and starvation, resulting in more migration and global unrest, according to David Beasley, head of the UN World Food Programme. He talks to Gideon about what needs to be done to avert catastrophe.Clips: NewsNation, ABC news, CNNWant to read more?Military briefing: Ukraine seeks way to break Russia’s Black Sea blockadePakistan seeks to renegotiate IMF loan as food prices surge‘Millions’ at risk of death as Ukraine war hits food supplies, Egypt warnsWorld’s poorest nations to receive aid amid soaring food pricesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/628e6a3ca80ea90015911b24/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 04:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/628e6a3ca80ea90015911b24/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine’s nationalists and the Azov battalion</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukraine-snationalistsandtheazovbattalion/media.mp3</link>
			<description>The roots of Ukrainian nationalism go back to the second world war, when one prominent group sided briefly with Hitler against the Soviet Union. Gideon talks to Princeton academic Kim Lane Scheppele about the legacy of this group and whether any remnants of its ideology still have influence over the country’s politics and military.Clips: NBC, Open Ukraine, Eurovision Song ContestMore on this topic:  ‘Don’t confuse patriotism and Nazism’: Ukraine’s Azov forces face scrutinyUkraine says rescue under way for troops at Azovstal steel mill in MariupolRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps — latest updatesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukraine-snationalistsandtheazovbattalion/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukraine-snationalistsandtheazovbattalion/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why do some countries remain poor?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whydosomecountriesremainpoor-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Why do some countries stay poor while others find a rapid path towards growth and development? Economist Stefan Dercon thinks it’s all about the willingness of those in power to prioritise development over protecting their own interests. He explains how he came to this view in conversation with the FT’s Africa editor, David Pilling.Clips: IMF, Africa NewsMore on this topic:  Gambling on Development, by Stefan DerconThe Rachman Review: the rising toll of famine and conflictEthiopia is a tragedy for the whole of AfricaSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by David Pilling. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whydosomecountriesremainpoor-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 04:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whydosomecountriesremainpoor-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why the global south won’t take sides on Ukraine</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukraineandtheglobalsouth/media.mp3</link>
			<description>When Russia invaded Ukraine, a group of countries in the global south, including India and South Africa, held back from the chorus of condemnation led by Europe and the US. Gideon discusses why they have adopted a neutral stance with Tanvi Madan of the Brookings Institution and Elizabeth Sidiropoulos, chief executive of the South African Institute of International Affairs.Clips: Reuters; Republic WorldWant to read more?Nato’s eastern front: will the military build-up make Europe safer?Indonesia under pressure as it weighs buying Russia’s ‘blood oil’How Russia’s war in Ukraine upended the breadbasket of EuropeXi Jinping faces a fateful decision on UkraineSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukraineandtheglobalsouth/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 04:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukraineandtheglobalsouth/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Putin’s nuclear threat and China ‘friendship’</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/putin-snuclearthreatandchina-friendship-/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Russia raised the spectre of nuclear war this week as it struggles to make headway in Ukraine. How seriously should this threat be taken and can Vladimir Putin rely on his friendship with China’s Xi Jinping? Gideon discusses these questions with US political scientist Graham Allison, author of the classic study of the Cuban missile crisis, ‘Essence of Decision’, and of a book on US-China relations, ‘Destined for War’.Clips: ABC, BloombergWant to read more?‘At war with the whole world’: why Putin might be planning a long conflict in UkraineBiden, Putin and the danger of VersaillesRussia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Jasiu SigsworthRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/putin-snuclearthreatandchina-friendship-/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 04:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:50</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/putin-snuclearthreatandchina-friendship-/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Le Pen, patriots and the anti-globalist movement</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/lepen-patriotsandtheanti-globalistmovement/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=tW9yFv1iLinRZc1YK5yiIq07gs4Y3i604SlEhvoVJsY</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to former World Trade Organization chief Pascal Lamy about the French election and what political trends in France tell us about nationalism and anti-globalist movements around the world.Clips: France 24Want to read more?‘She’s radiant’: what French voters like about Le Pen this timePatriots vs globalists replaces the left-right divideFrench election polls: the race for the presidencySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Jasiu SigsworthRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/lepen-patriotsandtheanti-globalistmovement/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=tW9yFv1iLinRZc1YK5yiIq07gs4Y3i604SlEhvoVJsY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 04:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/lepen-patriotsandtheanti-globalistmovement/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=tW9yFv1iLinRZc1YK5yiIq07gs4Y3i604SlEhvoVJsY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>“That was frightening as hell”: Ukrainian MP on working in a warzone</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/-thatwasfrighteningashell-ukrainianmponworkinginawarzone/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=PZwN8qu3sK1HnwYa8J3dXCeidP70x8Tv5sRIOR6bS0k</link>
			<description>In a country besieged by war, Ukrainian politicians continued to meet in their parliamentary building, despite the clear threat of attack from Russian troops. Ukrainian MP Dmytro Natalukha shares his experiences of keeping parliament running while Kyiv was under siege. As chairman of Ukraine’s economic affairs committee, Natalukha tells how the country’s economy has been ravaged, and how he expects the war will develop over the coming months.Clips: NBC News, BBC, DW News, CNAPresented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Persis Love. Sound design by Guldem Masa.﻿Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/-thatwasfrighteningashell-ukrainianmponworkinginawarzone/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=PZwN8qu3sK1HnwYa8J3dXCeidP70x8Tv5sRIOR6bS0k</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 04:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:51</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/-thatwasfrighteningashell-ukrainianmponworkinginawarzone/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=PZwN8qu3sK1HnwYa8J3dXCeidP70x8Tv5sRIOR6bS0k" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>French presidential election too close to call</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/frenchpresidentialelectiontooclosetocall/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4Ap4K-_VsFwFnewOW8x-9mm8M-JhRc2dAj01Va9q7AQ</link>
			<description>Far-right leader Marine Le Pen has put in an unexpectedly strong showing and looks set to go head to head with Emmanuel Macron in the second round of France’s presidential election. Gideon talks to the FT’s Anne-Sylvaine Chassany and Bruno Cautrès of Sciences Po about the issues French voters care about and what happens next.Clips: Reuters, HuffPost, France inter www.ft.com/rachman-reviewhttps://play.acast.com/s/therachmanreviewWant to read more?French election polls: the race for the presidencyRightwing presidential candidates’ immigration ‘obsession’ belies reality of modern FranceEmmanuel Macron warns he could lose French election to the far rightFrance votes: Macron’s frontrunner status conceals deep rifts in societySubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Jasiu SigsworthRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/frenchpresidentialelectiontooclosetocall/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4Ap4K-_VsFwFnewOW8x-9mm8M-JhRc2dAj01Va9q7AQ</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 04:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/frenchpresidentialelectiontooclosetocall/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4Ap4K-_VsFwFnewOW8x-9mm8M-JhRc2dAj01Va9q7AQ" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Putin and his entourage</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/putinandhisentourage/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=XL2d-31Zj20LbQQlpzv50I3AbvVwqcd_3QdReQhR0iQ</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Catherine Belton, author of the bestselling book Putin’s People, about who is likely to be influencing the Russian president as he decides whether to step back or press on with the war in Ukraine.Clips: Reuters, BBCWant to read more?Putin’s People: How the KGB Took Back Russia and Then Turned on the WestGermany and Austria plan for gas rationing over payment stand-off with RussiaWar in Ukraine: what explains the calm in global stock markets?Antigua investigates yacht with possible Abramovich tiesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Jasiu SigsworthRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/putinandhisentourage/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=XL2d-31Zj20LbQQlpzv50I3AbvVwqcd_3QdReQhR0iQ</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 04:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:03</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/putinandhisentourage/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=XL2d-31Zj20LbQQlpzv50I3AbvVwqcd_3QdReQhR0iQ" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Putin’s war is reshaping Europe’s alliances</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howputin-swarisreshapingeurope-salliances/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=wn70ixQ7diZFbP4I8OnYw-lRE8nVsop7mg-gWgqzvqA</link>
			<description>Europe has been united by opposition to Putin’s war in Ukraine, but will this new found unity last and will Russia be permanently isolated? Gideon talks to Alexander Stubb, former prime minister of Finland, about how the conflict is reshaping Europe’s alliances with the rest of the world.Clips: British PathéWant to read more? Nato to discuss extending Jens Stoltenberg’s term as secretary-generalBiden heads for Europe with mission to maintain west’s unity in response to RussiaWe should not abandon Russian citizens to a culture of brutalityPutin’s war demands a concerted global economic responseSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howputin-swarisreshapingeurope-salliances/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=wn70ixQ7diZFbP4I8OnYw-lRE8nVsop7mg-gWgqzvqA</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howputin-swarisreshapingeurope-salliances/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=wn70ixQ7diZFbP4I8OnYw-lRE8nVsop7mg-gWgqzvqA" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What would a Ukraine peace deal look like?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whatwouldaukrainepeacedeallooklike-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=lFQxjj_MQ9Qmi-xO81PYOFGXg8EUg82f4N4ULiZ6OwI</link>
			<description>Ben Hall talks to Rose Gottemoeller, an American diplomat who was deputy secretary-general of Nato from 2016 to 2019, about the kind of deal Russian and Ukrainian negotiators are working towards. Will Ukraine agree to give up its ambitions for Nato membership and pledge neutrality instead? How might the west guarantee its security and could Vladimir Putin tolerate an independent Ukraine?Clips: Sky News, BBC, NBCWant to read more?Ukraine and Russia signal progress in talksHow is Ukraine using western weapons to exploit Russian weaknesses?Life under occupation: how Ukrainians are resisting Russian ruleTracking Russia’s invasion of Ukraine in maps Subscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Ben Hall. Produced by Fiona Symon and Persis Love. Sound design by Breen TurnerRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whatwouldaukrainepeacedeallooklike-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=lFQxjj_MQ9Qmi-xO81PYOFGXg8EUg82f4N4ULiZ6OwI</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whatwouldaukrainepeacedeallooklike-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=lFQxjj_MQ9Qmi-xO81PYOFGXg8EUg82f4N4ULiZ6OwI" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Where is the Ukraine conflict heading?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whereistheukraineconflictheading-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=r303_vlZJ6tCTipKsfi0WItoJWFlZrlD02rJbjuIg98</link>
			<description>How long can the Ukrainians hold out? Will Vladimir Putin be stuck in a never-ending war and how would Russians tolerate that? Might western powers be dragged in? Ben Hall, the FT’s Europe editor, discusses these questions with John Paul Rathbone, defence and security correspondent, and Henry Foy, European diplomatic correspondent and former Moscow bureau chief. Clips: BBC, Nato NewsWant to read more? Ukraine accuses Russia of Mariupol hospital bombing ‘atrocity’Russia’s techies flee country they fear is ‘flying into an abyss’War in Ukraine: will the Baltics become the ‘new West Berlin’?Military briefing: Russian invaders exposed to guerrilla attacksSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Ben Hall. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Jasiu SigsworthRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whereistheukraineconflictheading-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=r303_vlZJ6tCTipKsfi0WItoJWFlZrlD02rJbjuIg98</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 05:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whereistheukraineconflictheading-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=r303_vlZJ6tCTipKsfi0WItoJWFlZrlD02rJbjuIg98" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ukraine failures tarnish Putin’s aura of invincibility</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukrainefailurestarnishputin-sauraofinvincibiliity/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qXCZ_8GJOoExXkvxb7mz3sPwk4sYxtCOhyCM06u8A5w</link>
			<description>Putin’s war in Ukraine is not going to plan, but it’s as yet unclear how the Russian leader will react to these failures. Gideon talks to strategic expert Lawrence Freedman about what the Russian military can realistically achieve and, in particular, how worried Nato should be about Russia’s decision to put its nuclear weapons on standby.Clips: BBC, CNN Want to read more?Another Stalingrad’: assault on Kharkiv shatters ties that once bound two nationsAir power counts for little in Ukraine war as caution prevails on both sidesWest takes Putin’s nuclear weapons threat seriouslyTracking Russia’s invasion of Ukraine in mapsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukrainefailurestarnishputin-sauraofinvincibiliity/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qXCZ_8GJOoExXkvxb7mz3sPwk4sYxtCOhyCM06u8A5w</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 05:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ukrainefailurestarnishputin-sauraofinvincibiliity/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qXCZ_8GJOoExXkvxb7mz3sPwk4sYxtCOhyCM06u8A5w" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Russia invades Ukraine</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/themoodinukraineandrussiaaswarlooms/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=WkjjbL6qh2Brb8YDJlcoECAC53qRuOR7vRdBpoz6-nY</link>
			<description>Russia has confirmed what western powers had long predicted and invaded Ukraine. On the eve of war, Gideon spoke to Sabine Fischer of the German Institute for International and Security Affairs, a Russian specialist recently back from Moscow, and to Polina Ivanova, FT correspondent in Kyiv, about the mood in the two capitals.Clips: RT, The White HouseWant to read more?EU hits Putin’s defence minister and chief of staff with sanctionsPutin’s denial of Ukrainian statehood carries dark historical echoesUkraine prepares to impose state of emergency and calls up reserve troopsPutin’s made-for-TV security debate gives him answers he wants to hear on UkraineSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/themoodinukraineandrussiaaswarlooms/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=WkjjbL6qh2Brb8YDJlcoECAC53qRuOR7vRdBpoz6-nY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/themoodinukraineandrussiaaswarlooms/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=WkjjbL6qh2Brb8YDJlcoECAC53qRuOR7vRdBpoz6-nY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Russia’s Ukraine threat galvanised western alliances</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howrussia-sukrainethreatgalvanisedwesternalliances/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=0dtlt-ccAlLLJRocsNrBPbkGHEr_Lq9ocEDoBJRtgeA</link>
			<description>After a week of frenetic diplomacy, the Ukraine crisis has yet to be resolved. But it has had a significant impact on reshaping western alliances. Gideon talks to Charles Grant, head of the Centre for European Reform, a London-based think-tank, about the impact of the Russian threat on US ties with Europe, and on Nato and the EU.Clips: The White House, Sky NewsWant to read more?Poland prepares for possible influx of refugees fleeing UkraineTop finance watchdog urges west to ‘think twice’ about Russia sanctionsCan the Minsk accords help de-escalate Russia-Ukraine tensions?Ukraine crisis pushes Russia and China into a closer embraceSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howrussia-sukrainethreatgalvanisedwesternalliances/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=0dtlt-ccAlLLJRocsNrBPbkGHEr_Lq9ocEDoBJRtgeA</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 05:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howrussia-sukrainethreatgalvanisedwesternalliances/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=0dtlt-ccAlLLJRocsNrBPbkGHEr_Lq9ocEDoBJRtgeA" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Drone warfare and the battle to control the skies</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/dronewarfare/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jP0L7HQnD7DMR94l73JLw9q6pGVsVto830j2QR2cs_w</link>
			<description>Governments and militias around the world, from Ukraine to Ethiopia, have a new and powerful weapon at their disposal: armed drones. Gideon talks to Ulrike Franke of the European Council on Foreign Relations about how this is changing the balance of power and causing growing concern about civilian casualties.Clips: WSJ, CBS,Sky NewsRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/dronewarfare/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jP0L7HQnD7DMR94l73JLw9q6pGVsVto830j2QR2cs_w</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 05:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/dronewarfare/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jP0L7HQnD7DMR94l73JLw9q6pGVsVto830j2QR2cs_w" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is the Orban era coming to an end?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/istheorbaneracomingtoanend-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eaXyXzJiRybICTHEwRH2nQ-vS6vqNarizJWO8ptitiw</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Hungary’s opposition leader Peter Marki-Zay about his chances of overcoming the powerful political machine created by Viktor Orban and his Fidesz party in April's elections.Clips: Fox News, ReutersRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/istheorbaneracomingtoanend-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eaXyXzJiRybICTHEwRH2nQ-vS6vqNarizJWO8ptitiw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 05:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:56</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/istheorbaneracomingtoanend-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eaXyXzJiRybICTHEwRH2nQ-vS6vqNarizJWO8ptitiw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Ukraine crisis: a view from Moscow</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theukrainecrisis-aviewfrommoscow/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eEvbE__M_ZgXnRZSFBmQtEg_8HwRaH6_6zyQonvlh98</link>
			<description>Russia’s military build-up on its border with Ukraine has set off alarm bells and led to a flurry of transatlantic diplomacy. Gideon talks to Dmitri Trenin, director of the Carnegie Moscow Center, about what President Vladimir Putin is seeking to achieve, and whether he can realise these goals without launching an attack on Ukraine.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theukrainecrisis-aviewfrommoscow/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eEvbE__M_ZgXnRZSFBmQtEg_8HwRaH6_6zyQonvlh98</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 05:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theukrainecrisis-aviewfrommoscow/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eEvbE__M_ZgXnRZSFBmQtEg_8HwRaH6_6zyQonvlh98" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What would a Ukraine conflict look like?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whatwouldaukraineconflictlooklike-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=kVpZQ9U_Mqf4W4A9yfoDnXBy4lW47s4kESq1cRAZG3s</link>
			<description>Diplomacy has so far failed to defuse the crisis in Ukraine and many fear that war is imminent. Gideon discusses the remaining diplomatic possibilities and, if they fail, what a war might look like, with Samuel Charap, a political scientist at the Rand Corporation think-tank in Washington.Clips: Sky News, CBS NewsRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whatwouldaukraineconflictlooklike-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=kVpZQ9U_Mqf4W4A9yfoDnXBy4lW47s4kESq1cRAZG3s</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 05:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whatwouldaukraineconflictlooklike-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=kVpZQ9U_Mqf4W4A9yfoDnXBy4lW47s4kESq1cRAZG3s" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The rising toll of famine and conflict</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/therisingtolloffamineandconflict/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5XmsSd8MVnCuwPMFBPepdFoi0gkihQp6S2WZRg3Ca9M</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to David Miliband, president of the International Rescue Committee, about the organisation’s 2022 watchlist, which reveals that people in 20 countries, representing 10 per cent of the world’s population, are at risk or in dire need of humanitarian aid, and the situation is getting worse. What has gone wrong and are there any solutions?Clips: DW, Live Aid, ReutersIRC’s 2022 Emergency WatchlistDavid Miliband’s speech to the Council on Foreign RelationsRead a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/therisingtolloffamineandconflict/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5XmsSd8MVnCuwPMFBPepdFoi0gkihQp6S2WZRg3Ca9M</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 05:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/therisingtolloffamineandconflict/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5XmsSd8MVnCuwPMFBPepdFoi0gkihQp6S2WZRg3Ca9M" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sudan’s painful struggle for democracy</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/sudan-spainfulstrugglefordemocracy/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=w3ry9x007mo8qzpO5WJRt0JZo5hI1piQMbdNyLm5HYk</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/c2a23023-df6b-49ed-af06-149bb0b35237Three years of demonstrations have proved the Sudanese people’s strong desire for democratic change after decades of military rule. But this week the latest attempt to secure a peaceful transition foundered with the resignation of Abdalla Hamdok, interim prime minister. Gideon Rachman discusses what happens next with London-based journalist Yousra Elbagir and Muzan Alneel, a writer based in Sudan.Clips: BBC, Euronews, CNN Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/sudan-spainfulstrugglefordemocracy/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=w3ry9x007mo8qzpO5WJRt0JZo5hI1piQMbdNyLm5HYk</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/sudan-spainfulstrugglefordemocracy/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=w3ry9x007mo8qzpO5WJRt0JZo5hI1piQMbdNyLm5HYk" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Gideon and his team review 2021</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/gideonandhisteamreview2021/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=hrqGnP70_IsHLXH_kLArcsvqqhF3dEpA7Sah8uyB_2o</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/03234d8d-0548-4e84-b7c9-5ed87b2b7a57For the last podcast of 2021 and to review the year, Gideon Rachman is joined by his FT colleagues Martin Wolf and Gillian Tett.We’re coming to the end of a tumultuous year, which began with the unprecedented storming of the US capitol by supporters of Donald Trump. And which ends with a pandemic still raging, inflation on the rise and Vladimir Putin threatening to invade Ukraine.Audio: BBC, ABC News Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/gideonandhisteamreview2021/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=hrqGnP70_IsHLXH_kLArcsvqqhF3dEpA7Sah8uyB_2o</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/gideonandhisteamreview2021/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=hrqGnP70_IsHLXH_kLArcsvqqhF3dEpA7Sah8uyB_2o" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The underside of globalisation</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theundersideofglobalisation/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=UNOxQwuk4JK5w2p_tsSH5LpaIjCRFHxcsi5o1LJw8wQ</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/ce91ffd7-0549-4187-8dda-61b20548d2c8Gideon talks to Mark Leonard, director of the European Council on Foreign Relations, about the ways in which global powers try to exert influence over others in an interconnected world. Mark Leonard is author of The Age of Unpeace: How Connectivity Causes Conflict.Clips: Reuters, BBC Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theundersideofglobalisation/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=UNOxQwuk4JK5w2p_tsSH5LpaIjCRFHxcsi5o1LJw8wQ</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 05:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:17</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theundersideofglobalisation/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=UNOxQwuk4JK5w2p_tsSH5LpaIjCRFHxcsi5o1LJw8wQ" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cyber power: a moment of reckoning</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cyberpower-amomentofreckoning/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5wwisJ32WhrF2xUE3nxXFyxQ76Ggnvn0ICAMK-1aNUM</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/402578f3-6ad6-45f8-8340-cb1e809fe95bIn this special interview, Sir Jeremy Fleming, head of the UK signals intelligence agency GCHQ, talks to FT editor Roula Khalaf and FT correspondent Helen Warrell about cyber threats from China and other state actors, the global competition for data and the &quot;Snowden effect&quot; on spy agencies.Clips: IISS, NBC Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cyberpower-amomentofreckoning/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5wwisJ32WhrF2xUE3nxXFyxQ76Ggnvn0ICAMK-1aNUM</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cyberpower-amomentofreckoning/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5wwisJ32WhrF2xUE3nxXFyxQ76Ggnvn0ICAMK-1aNUM" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is Russia on the brink of war with Ukraine?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/isrussiaonthebrinkofwarwithukraine-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=8xwKJsh7UXF-xHisObvIr1S_ZwNcDCUWAkXZpUkvETQ</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/34bb8aee-612e-4b2e-ab59-0d11518e1d82Gideon talks to Kadri Liik, a senior policy fellow at the European Council on Foreign Relations, about Russia’s military build-up on the Ukraine border and about how policymakers in Nato and the EU are responding.Clips: Nato News; VOA; BBC Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/isrussiaonthebrinkofwarwithukraine-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=8xwKJsh7UXF-xHisObvIr1S_ZwNcDCUWAkXZpUkvETQ</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:06</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/isrussiaonthebrinkofwarwithukraine-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=8xwKJsh7UXF-xHisObvIr1S_ZwNcDCUWAkXZpUkvETQ" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>China and the US: competition or conflict?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/chinaandtheus-competitionorconflict-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dpMucFWD-0lnmEMW7Ar49_xQS_AdATYRXs_bUvILYH0</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/c40abc3c-5a4b-4ebe-9f24-82241f2939f5Gideon talks to former White House official Evan Medeiros about the recent summit between the US and Chinese presidents. Was the relative cordiality of the meeting a sign of reconciliation or are the two powers heading towards a military confrontation?Clips: The White House, Deutsche Welle Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/chinaandtheus-competitionorconflict-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dpMucFWD-0lnmEMW7Ar49_xQS_AdATYRXs_bUvILYH0</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 05:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/chinaandtheus-competitionorconflict-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dpMucFWD-0lnmEMW7Ar49_xQS_AdATYRXs_bUvILYH0" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>COP26: success or failure?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cop26-successorfailure-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=pX35B1IpGyOgLV1CdP7X2GPHPNoj5eF-OHJiYqqjlfo</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/f1dbd73c-381c-475b-8b22-fa07abd6d92fGideon talks to Simon Mundy, author of Race For Tomorrow, about how he would assess global efforts to tackle climate change in the wake of this month’s gathering of world leaders in Glasgow.Clips: Bloomberg; NBC; ABC Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cop26-successorfailure-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=pX35B1IpGyOgLV1CdP7X2GPHPNoj5eF-OHJiYqqjlfo</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cop26-successorfailure-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=pX35B1IpGyOgLV1CdP7X2GPHPNoj5eF-OHJiYqqjlfo" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Poland’s challenge to the EU</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/poland-schallengetotheeu/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=N9QZ_jMusKkEXUw2zz9vLV6h12Cwa0akN1sC2uCcPis</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/e66fa8b7-7b92-4497-8585-cf43e8cd41fcPoland’s judicial reforms have put it on a collision course with the EU over human rights and the rule of law. Can the bloc adapt to accommodate its more awkward members or should it take a hard line? Gideon discusses the problem with Catherine De Vries, a professor of political science who specialises in the EU and is based at Bocconi University in Milan.Clips: BBC, Euronews. European Commission Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/poland-schallengetotheeu/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=N9QZ_jMusKkEXUw2zz9vLV6h12Cwa0akN1sC2uCcPis</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 05:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:08</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/poland-schallengetotheeu/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=N9QZ_jMusKkEXUw2zz9vLV6h12Cwa0akN1sC2uCcPis" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>COP26: climate goals at stake in Glasgow</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cop26-climategoalsatstakeinglasgow/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=uJuoMjxSai3qw_c9iH3iaZ7cBMBln9yAMjJyB2JYTp0</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/07579093-643e-4300-87c3-3b3e6b36526bGideon talks to Leslie Hook, the FT’s environment correspondent, about what to expect from the UN climate change conference in Glasgow. Will determination to give teeth to the Paris accord survive the global energy crisis?Clips: UN; ITV News; Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cop26-climategoalsatstakeinglasgow/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=uJuoMjxSai3qw_c9iH3iaZ7cBMBln9yAMjJyB2JYTp0</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 05:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cop26-climategoalsatstakeinglasgow/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=uJuoMjxSai3qw_c9iH3iaZ7cBMBln9yAMjJyB2JYTp0" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Israel’s new political landscape</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/israel-snewpoliticallandscape/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=EK0S8jfY44K4b7i5O4HZ98O2ZLmDiiQQv0J7XSougq0</link>
			<description>Read a transcript of this episode on FT.comhttps://www.ft.com/content/7dd6de54-58d0-4a5f-9c74-d599b513a668Benjamin Netanyahu, Israel’s longest-serving prime minister, finally left office this year. He is now on trial on corruption charges and Israel is ruled by the most diverse coalition in its history. Gideon discusses Israel’s new political landscape with Yohanan Plesner, president of the Israel Democracy Institute.Clips: IsraeliPM, Reuters  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/israel-snewpoliticallandscape/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=EK0S8jfY44K4b7i5O4HZ98O2ZLmDiiQQv0J7XSougq0</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 04:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:09</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/israel-snewpoliticallandscape/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=EK0S8jfY44K4b7i5O4HZ98O2ZLmDiiQQv0J7XSougq0" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Great power rivals of the 21st century</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/greatpowerrivalsofthe21stcentury/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Wk1sub7Aiy0j5ZJwt2Hsfb9oHLAZ5KrDgaaGp7qATcY</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to historian Paul Kennedy about how long America’s period as the world’s most powerful nation can last in the face of a rising China.Clips: British Pathé Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/greatpowerrivalsofthe21stcentury/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Wk1sub7Aiy0j5ZJwt2Hsfb9oHLAZ5KrDgaaGp7qATcY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 04:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:34</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/greatpowerrivalsofthe21stcentury/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Wk1sub7Aiy0j5ZJwt2Hsfb9oHLAZ5KrDgaaGp7qATcY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>American democracy under pressure</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americandemocracyunderpressure/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=FioAIpLlpXb4LQO-4MwlliTh-4YUzo6s82RrOuMJC_4</link>
			<description>Gideon discusses the strength of America’s political system with Jacob Heilbrunn, editor of the foreign policy magazine The National Interest.  Are fears about the Republican party’s commitment to democracy justified, and can Joe Biden win back the support of white, working class America?Clips: MSNBC, TODAY, CNN Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americandemocracyunderpressure/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=FioAIpLlpXb4LQO-4MwlliTh-4YUzo6s82RrOuMJC_4</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 04:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americandemocracyunderpressure/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=FioAIpLlpXb4LQO-4MwlliTh-4YUzo6s82RrOuMJC_4" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Populations on the move</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/populationsonthemove/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=1hgPwmrQ1DGtF3TI7IN18B_pqq7uEN-PyACikMS7kXk</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Parag Khanna, founder and managing partner of FutureMap, a global strategic advisory firm, and author of a new book on mass migration called Move: the forces uprooting us. Clips: PBS, Channel 4 News Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/populationsonthemove/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=1hgPwmrQ1DGtF3TI7IN18B_pqq7uEN-PyACikMS7kXk</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 04:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/populationsonthemove/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=1hgPwmrQ1DGtF3TI7IN18B_pqq7uEN-PyACikMS7kXk" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Germany’s traffic light coalition</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germany-strafficlightcoalition/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=G4a7Oly8krDxrnD07bXKMzP2KRQ2stdPSBOHkUMINhw</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Ulrike Franke of the European Council on Foreign Relations about Olaf Scholz’s election win, his Social Democratic party’s likely alliance with the Greens and Free Democrats, and whether this will lead to a change of direction for Germany. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germany-strafficlightcoalition/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=G4a7Oly8krDxrnD07bXKMzP2KRQ2stdPSBOHkUMINhw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 04:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germany-strafficlightcoalition/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=G4a7Oly8krDxrnD07bXKMzP2KRQ2stdPSBOHkUMINhw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Biden administration and the world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebidenadministrationandtheworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=NSndjXj99NV8bfP57vRcFaamidtTLbpeWSJUdmlY3aI</link>
			<description>Joe Biden says &quot;relentless diplomacy&quot; will be at the heart of American foreign policy. But the Aukus pact with Britain and Australia, reached without consulting other allies, angered European leaders, notably France’s Emmanuel Macron. Derek Chollet, counsellor at the state department in Washington, explains the rationale for the deal and why he thinks the diplomatic friction is likely to be shortlived.CLIPS: The White House, France 24 Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebidenadministrationandtheworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=NSndjXj99NV8bfP57vRcFaamidtTLbpeWSJUdmlY3aI</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 04:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:09</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebidenadministrationandtheworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=NSndjXj99NV8bfP57vRcFaamidtTLbpeWSJUdmlY3aI" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trudeau's future on the line in Canada's election</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/trudeausfutureonthelineincanadaselection-acastfc5fda06/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=zSn822Yhyb89zfjapOGs9A25thmSQAcicXMWaHjd_Jg</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Darrell Bricker, author of several books on Canadian politics and CEO of Ipsos Public Affairs, about Canada’s upcoming federal election. With the vote opening on September 20th, the two discuss what led to this early election, the campaign debates and whether Canada is on the brink of a major political shift. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/trudeausfutureonthelineincanadaselection-acastfc5fda06/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=zSn822Yhyb89zfjapOGs9A25thmSQAcicXMWaHjd_Jg</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 04:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/trudeausfutureonthelineincanadaselection-acastfc5fda06/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=zSn822Yhyb89zfjapOGs9A25thmSQAcicXMWaHjd_Jg" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Covid and the end of the post 9/11 era</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/covidandtheendofthepost9-11era/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qyKUiXok2Xgyeed5rDmpKZksIUClQkVRjqJRGYB0ApE</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Thomas Wright, director of the Center on the US and Europe at the Brookings Institution, about the aftermath of a global crisis when ‘no-one was home’ on the international leadership side. Clips: Global News, NBC News and AP Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/covidandtheendofthepost9-11era/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qyKUiXok2Xgyeed5rDmpKZksIUClQkVRjqJRGYB0ApE</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 04:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/covidandtheendofthepost9-11era/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qyKUiXok2Xgyeed5rDmpKZksIUClQkVRjqJRGYB0ApE" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America’s Afghan legacy</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-safghanlegacy/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=RaOvPP1BSQTZ54VJ4QjbWH8olJXrG05tVCOxQV7MI6g</link>
			<description>Sarah Chayes, a writer and former journalist who worked as a special adviser to the US military leadership in Afghanistan, talks to Martin Sandbu about what will be the legacy of America’s 20-year involvement.Clips: White House; ITV News; ABC 7 Chicago Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-safghanlegacy/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=RaOvPP1BSQTZ54VJ4QjbWH8olJXrG05tVCOxQV7MI6g</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 04:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:37</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-safghanlegacy/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=RaOvPP1BSQTZ54VJ4QjbWH8olJXrG05tVCOxQV7MI6g" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Peru’s triple crisis</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/peru-striplecrisis/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ge_3RafkvKs7-56ou_7yYUWW6ElsN2nOvyQhN03-CwM</link>
			<description>Years of political instability, the world’s highest coronavirus death rate, and the recent election of leftwing President Pedro Castillo have plunged Peru into crisis. Michael Stott, FT Latin America editor, talks to Oswaldo Molina, executive director of think-tank REDES and head of economics at Lima’s Pacific University, about the origins of this crisis and whether this is part of a wider trend in Latin America. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/peru-striplecrisis/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ge_3RafkvKs7-56ou_7yYUWW6ElsN2nOvyQhN03-CwM</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/peru-striplecrisis/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ge_3RafkvKs7-56ou_7yYUWW6ElsN2nOvyQhN03-CwM" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Iran under Raisi</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/iranunderraisi/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=hYNYwDvnY5lwU9Hlm7UV9OT048CtnRkNgaaP276-gi0</link>
			<description>How will Iran’s new president tackle growing disillusionment at home, a potentially hostile regime on its eastern border and negotiations to revive the nuclear deal? Andrew England, the FT’s Middle East editor, discusses what we can expect from Ebrahim Raisi with Sanam Vakil, deputy director of the Middle East North Africa programme at Chatham House in London.Clips: Al Jazeera, BBC, Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/iranunderraisi/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=hYNYwDvnY5lwU9Hlm7UV9OT048CtnRkNgaaP276-gi0</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 04:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/iranunderraisi/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=hYNYwDvnY5lwU9Hlm7UV9OT048CtnRkNgaaP276-gi0" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can climate damage be repaired?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/canclimatedamageberepaired-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=DkBqN7xq4NINdnyaX6I5UmVsGyGWCzIFY_segYJFspI</link>
			<description>Gideon Rachman talks to Professor Sir David King about the string of environmental disasters across the globe this summer. With the IPCC report this week confirming that climate change is accelerating, Sir King says that it is no longer enough to aim for net zero emissions, we must use technology to repair damage to the polar ice caps.Clips: BBC, Latin America News Agency (Reuters), Bloomberg Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/canclimatedamageberepaired-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=DkBqN7xq4NINdnyaX6I5UmVsGyGWCzIFY_segYJFspI</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 04:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/canclimatedamageberepaired-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=DkBqN7xq4NINdnyaX6I5UmVsGyGWCzIFY_segYJFspI" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is Lebanon a failed state?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/islebanonafailedstate-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qV75hESVFKrmKILN44EeIRM0oGdjvw01hNKYO-mflqg</link>
			<description>Gideon Rachman talks to Chloe Cornish, the FT’s Middle East correspondent, on how decades of misgovernance have led to Lebanon’s current political, economic and social crisis. Chloe recounts how the year since the explosion in Beirut, the country’s capital city, has been one of worsening struggle for the Lebanese people.Chloe’s piece, Lebanon’s year from hell: a diary, can be read hereClips: AP Archive, Reagan Library Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/islebanonafailedstate-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qV75hESVFKrmKILN44EeIRM0oGdjvw01hNKYO-mflqg</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 04:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:00</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/islebanonafailedstate-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=qV75hESVFKrmKILN44EeIRM0oGdjvw01hNKYO-mflqg" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ecocide: a new weapon in the fight to save the planet</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ecocide-anewweaponinthefighttosavetheplanet/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=uyjXGZquGa2yNAnigoa7ZSxcBHyDaeM52WbP6L5t0Tw</link>
			<description>Pilita Clark talks to Philippe Sands, human rights barrister, professor, author and an expert in international law who recently co-chaired a panel that produced a legal definition of the crime of ‘ecocide’. He says there is growing support for the introduction of a law that could put presidents and chief executives in the dock at the International Criminal Court in the Hague.Clips: CBS, ABC Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ecocide-anewweaponinthefighttosavetheplanet/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=uyjXGZquGa2yNAnigoa7ZSxcBHyDaeM52WbP6L5t0Tw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 04:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ecocide-anewweaponinthefighttosavetheplanet/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=uyjXGZquGa2yNAnigoa7ZSxcBHyDaeM52WbP6L5t0Tw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>India, China and the contested border</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/india-chinaandthecontestedborder/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Er_Ty-WKf9jtjIGBr836lihpPb3b9qUyXrmIPPjJfZ0</link>
			<description>The foreign ministers of India and China have held talks amid an enduring standoff that has opened up new fault lines over Asia’s future. Meanwhile, the US has shown a growing interest in its alliance with India, despite concerns about the Modi government's domestic policies. Gideon Rachman talks to Tanvi Madan, senior fellow at the Brookings Institution, about the triangular relationship between India, China and the US.Review clips: India Today Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/india-chinaandthecontestedborder/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Er_Ty-WKf9jtjIGBr836lihpPb3b9qUyXrmIPPjJfZ0</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 04:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/india-chinaandthecontestedborder/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Er_Ty-WKf9jtjIGBr836lihpPb3b9qUyXrmIPPjJfZ0" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How much trouble is Bolsonaro in?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howmuchtroubleisbolsonaroin-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=A7a_BRHea74ZH6tHU_7I9xn_rUbuSeSONDjxUErSXEc</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Oliver Stuenkel, a professor of international relations at the Getulio Vargas foundation in São Paulo about Brazil’s president Jair Bolsonaro. His government’s failure to tackle the coronavirus pandemic and recent corruption allegations have caused Bolsonaro's popularity to sink ahead of next year’s election. But is he already laying the ground for claims that the vote was fraudulent?Clips: EFE, Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howmuchtroubleisbolsonaroin-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=A7a_BRHea74ZH6tHU_7I9xn_rUbuSeSONDjxUErSXEc</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 04:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:26</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/howmuchtroubleisbolsonaroin-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=A7a_BRHea74ZH6tHU_7I9xn_rUbuSeSONDjxUErSXEc" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>South Africa’s pivotal moment</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/southafrica-spivotalmoment/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=TCmbild0xumvqTN82OPdplz2mzzSfBhw5QVc1rRz1E8</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Judith February, South African lawyer and journalist, about the case against former president Jacob Zuma. His refusal to cooperate with an inquiry into corruption during his nine years as president set a crucial test for the country’s democratic institutions. The decision to send him to prison marks a pivotal moment, says February. Clips: Eyewitness News, SABC News  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/southafrica-spivotalmoment/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=TCmbild0xumvqTN82OPdplz2mzzSfBhw5QVc1rRz1E8</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 04:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:18</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/southafrica-spivotalmoment/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=TCmbild0xumvqTN82OPdplz2mzzSfBhw5QVc1rRz1E8" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can Germany atone for its colonial-era genocide?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cangermanyatoneforitscolonial-eragenocide-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=BZh3XKC3lvWh7cd-sWsZrT78P3QMs9BOGRkx2gYEurM</link>
			<description>Gideon speaks to Esther Muinjangue, a former chair of the Ovaherero Genocide Foundation, and Franziska Boehme, a professor of political science, about the decades-long journey towards official recognition of Germany’s colonial-era atrocities in Namibia as genocide and why the apology that is now offered is not the reconciliation descendants of some of the victims sought.Review clips: AFP Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cangermanyatoneforitscolonial-eragenocide-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=BZh3XKC3lvWh7cd-sWsZrT78P3QMs9BOGRkx2gYEurM</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 04:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:23</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/cangermanyatoneforitscolonial-eragenocide-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=BZh3XKC3lvWh7cd-sWsZrT78P3QMs9BOGRkx2gYEurM" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Coming to terms with Putin's Russia</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/comingtotermswithputinsrussia/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ua378zANLp-s7dNZz7TOx-K4FGTTsgfRg3Zt25_b1ek</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Fiona Hill of the Brookings Institution about the recent US-Russia summit and what the former presidential adviser sees as the best way to deal with a state 'run by operatives' who don't play by the rules. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/comingtotermswithputinsrussia/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ua378zANLp-s7dNZz7TOx-K4FGTTsgfRg3Zt25_b1ek</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 04:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:46</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/comingtotermswithputinsrussia/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ua378zANLp-s7dNZz7TOx-K4FGTTsgfRg3Zt25_b1ek" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Martin Wolf on G7 opportunities missed</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/martinwolfong7opportunitiesmissed/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=yOt6FdRrj5_ul0tbfIJXiYTjvh_9d6HAtx_J7I8B7J0</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Martin Wolf, the FT’s chief economics commentator, about the pressing problems requiring international co-operation, and asks him if, in light of the G7 summit, the west is up to the task. Review clips: The Guardian, WION Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/martinwolfong7opportunitiesmissed/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=yOt6FdRrj5_ul0tbfIJXiYTjvh_9d6HAtx_J7I8B7J0</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 10:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:49</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/martinwolfong7opportunitiesmissed/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=yOt6FdRrj5_ul0tbfIJXiYTjvh_9d6HAtx_J7I8B7J0" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Can Asian prosperity survive US-China rivalry?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/canasianprosperitysurviveus-chinarivalry-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5iE2w9FYNyAPPVoFfh5YqqaldAgAG-H0vwRhALa7jrk</link>
			<description>South-east Asia has enjoyed a long period of sustained economic growth. But is this endangered by rising tensions between the US and China? Gideon puts this question to James Crabtree, executive director of the International Institute for Strategic Studies in Singapore.Clips: CGTN Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/canasianprosperitysurviveus-chinarivalry-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5iE2w9FYNyAPPVoFfh5YqqaldAgAG-H0vwRhALa7jrk</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 04:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:13</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/canasianprosperitysurviveus-chinarivalry-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=5iE2w9FYNyAPPVoFfh5YqqaldAgAG-H0vwRhALa7jrk" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Belarus: more than a moral dilemma</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/belarus-morethanamoraldilemma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=couccjQKE6YwFvTGgfSNP4jaloKr_qV6XV7AavfcnqQ</link>
			<description>The decision by Belarus to divert a plane to Minsk to arrest a dissident journalist was intended to send a message to opponents of President Alexander Lukashenko, whose 27 years in office have seen him dubbed Europe’s last dictator. However, the act has renewed international condemnation and calls for sanctions against the Lukashenko regime. In this episode Gideon talks to Katia Glod, a Belarusian political consultant, about what happens next now that the world is watching Belarus. Review clips: EU Debates, DW, CBS, CNN Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/belarus-morethanamoraldilemma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=couccjQKE6YwFvTGgfSNP4jaloKr_qV6XV7AavfcnqQ</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 04:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/belarus-morethanamoraldilemma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=couccjQKE6YwFvTGgfSNP4jaloKr_qV6XV7AavfcnqQ" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Washington’s will to find a Middle East solution</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/washington-swilltofindamiddleeastsolution/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vNnhXnL3oiYXaO3M2Xgp9C9zDtXCuQd3htCystcjOKE</link>
			<description>A ceasefire is in place and an 11-day war is over, but that may not move Israelis and Palestinians closer to a two-state solution according to Martin Indyk, of the Council on Foreign Relations. Indyk has experience at the negotiation table as a former US ambassador to Israel and US special envoy during the Israeli-Palenstinan peace talks. In this episode Gideon talks to him about the stance the Biden administration is taking in the Middle East.  Review clips: C-SPAN Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/washington-swilltofindamiddleeastsolution/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vNnhXnL3oiYXaO3M2Xgp9C9zDtXCuQd3htCystcjOKE</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 04:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/washington-swilltofindamiddleeastsolution/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vNnhXnL3oiYXaO3M2Xgp9C9zDtXCuQd3htCystcjOKE" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Myanmar on the brink</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/myanmaronthebrink/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dFuzxxhDf5s7QLFkFWqyCkB_lJIyyzsyUW08wDlhOXY</link>
			<description>The military coup in Myanmar threatens to roll back a decade of democratisation. In the months since the February coup, there have been strikes and protests as well as mass arrests and escalating violence as the junta attempts to quell rebellions. Gideon talks to Thant Myint-U, a Burmese historian and political analyst, about the situation in Myanmar and whether the country risks becoming a failed state.   Review clips: LBJ Presidential Library, AP, Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/myanmaronthebrink/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dFuzxxhDf5s7QLFkFWqyCkB_lJIyyzsyUW08wDlhOXY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 04:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/myanmaronthebrink/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dFuzxxhDf5s7QLFkFWqyCkB_lJIyyzsyUW08wDlhOXY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A crisis in the Middle East</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/acrisisinthemiddleeast/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=al-xrnOzl-zRR4QSAoyBvQsm47-2Kd38gOFRKxfwM0k</link>
			<description>Protests in Jerusalem at the beginning of the week have escalated to rocket launches, retaliatory airstrikes and civilian deaths. Gideon talks to Diana Butto, a Palestinian lawyer, and Noga Tarnopolsky, a journalist based in Jerusalem, about the political conditions that have kindled the worst fighting the region has seen in years. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/acrisisinthemiddleeast/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=al-xrnOzl-zRR4QSAoyBvQsm47-2Kd38gOFRKxfwM0k</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 04:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/acrisisinthemiddleeast/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=al-xrnOzl-zRR4QSAoyBvQsm47-2Kd38gOFRKxfwM0k" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why we should all give up meat</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyweshouldallgiveupmeat/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=deEuXB9QB9DW-69xQyE6ozQX0PfvvGAIUGK-v0YaOh4</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to the FT’s Henry Mance about why he became a vegan. He says it's not just about preserving wildlife and the environment, it’s also about being true to our human values. Henry’s book How to Love Animals: In a Human-Shaped World, was published last month. Review clips: BBC, NPR Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyweshouldallgiveupmeat/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=deEuXB9QB9DW-69xQyE6ozQX0PfvvGAIUGK-v0YaOh4</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 04:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyweshouldallgiveupmeat/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=deEuXB9QB9DW-69xQyE6ozQX0PfvvGAIUGK-v0YaOh4" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>India’s wake up call to the world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/india-swakeupcalltotheworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jYruyTMbgYjoOX0mRhiu2Srwxnr0-RDsQKUcke6p_eY</link>
			<description>Gideon Rachman talks to Abraar Karan, a physician at Harvard Medical School and a specialist in global health, about the current surge in coronavirus cases in India and why nationalistic approaches to curbing the pandemic will not help solve a worldwide health crisis Review Clips: NDTV, India Today, CNBC, US Department of State Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/india-swakeupcalltotheworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jYruyTMbgYjoOX0mRhiu2Srwxnr0-RDsQKUcke6p_eY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 04:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:36</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/india-swakeupcalltotheworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=jYruyTMbgYjoOX0mRhiu2Srwxnr0-RDsQKUcke6p_eY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Leaving Afghanistan</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/leavingafghanistan/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=YY7k7Nmc06w6JF4RyndEwkYb6_uWqX-OJnU4dEnv7Ts</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Tom Tugendhat, head of the UK parliament’s foreign affairs committee, about the US decision to finally withdraw from Afghanistan. How will this affect the credibility of the western powers and their ability to conduct successful military interventions abroad? Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/leavingafghanistan/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=YY7k7Nmc06w6JF4RyndEwkYb6_uWqX-OJnU4dEnv7Ts</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 04:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:10</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/leavingafghanistan/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=YY7k7Nmc06w6JF4RyndEwkYb6_uWqX-OJnU4dEnv7Ts" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Britain's legacy of empire</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britainsunhealthylegacyofempire/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=tYgnnBp1Oyg6b2ZPgxR0GQWeWJSYVA4VdkSD4LlnzG4</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Sathnam Sanghera about his book Empireland and the legacy of racism and nostalgia that Britain has yet to come to terms with.Warning: This episode contains references to racist language.Clips: Sky News; Conservative party Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britainsunhealthylegacyofempire/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=tYgnnBp1Oyg6b2ZPgxR0GQWeWJSYVA4VdkSD4LlnzG4</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 04:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britainsunhealthylegacyofempire/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=tYgnnBp1Oyg6b2ZPgxR0GQWeWJSYVA4VdkSD4LlnzG4" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Are the US and China entering a Cold War?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/aretheusandchinaenteringacoldwar-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dDoQAX--0dzwNi69TOSB9tMu7Ez_cW3eQW9ZhyxWeOM</link>
			<description>The US president has promised that, after four years of retreat from the global stage, “America is back”. Over the past few years, China has continued to expand its economic and political influence and matched its growing clout on the world stage with a bigger military that is flexing its might in the Pacific. In this episode Demetri Sevastopulo, the FT’s US-China correspondent, talks to Michèle Flournoy of the Center for a New American Security, a bipartisan think-tank in Washington, about how the Biden administration might handle Beijing. Flournoy served in the Pentagon during the Clinton and Obama administrations.Review clips: C-SPAN, CNN, DW, CNBC, The White House, UN Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/aretheusandchinaenteringacoldwar-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dDoQAX--0dzwNi69TOSB9tMu7Ez_cW3eQW9ZhyxWeOM</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 04:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:33</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/aretheusandchinaenteringacoldwar-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=dDoQAX--0dzwNi69TOSB9tMu7Ez_cW3eQW9ZhyxWeOM" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Britain shifts its military focus</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britainshiftsitsmilitaryfocus/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ULMhcTPR6BI2Z7EogblsEsukafQMUagsU1r7A_ZP0eU</link>
			<description>The UK’s defence forces are slimming down and harnessing the power of AI and satellites to meet the emerging threats of the 21st century. Helen Warrell, the FT’s defence and security editor, talks to General Sir Patrick Sanders, head of the UK’s Strategic Command, about the biggest transformation in Britain’s armed forces since the cold war.Clips: parliamentlive, Forces News Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britainshiftsitsmilitaryfocus/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ULMhcTPR6BI2Z7EogblsEsukafQMUagsU1r7A_ZP0eU</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 04:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:31:44</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britainshiftsitsmilitaryfocus/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=ULMhcTPR6BI2Z7EogblsEsukafQMUagsU1r7A_ZP0eU" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Europe's Mr Normal</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/europesmrnormal/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=O6dWnHoyuq-7rlqTnroS8v0Kti29-rUAO_qjnO1wvFA</link>
			<description>Ben Hall, the FT’s Europe editor, talks to Dutch historian Luuk van Middelaar about Mark Rutte’s re-election as prime minister of the Netherlands and his country’s changing role within the EU. Clips: Bloomberg, Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/europesmrnormal/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=O6dWnHoyuq-7rlqTnroS8v0Kti29-rUAO_qjnO1wvFA</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 05:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:20</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/europesmrnormal/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=O6dWnHoyuq-7rlqTnroS8v0Kti29-rUAO_qjnO1wvFA" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Spying in the digital age</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/spyinginthedigitalage/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=0b5-C2sPB1FJ11stGT67sWRckmXn7INXVVT8SA4nixs</link>
			<description>Helen Warrell, the FT’s defence and security editor, talks to cybersecurity expert Dmitri Alperovitch about the SolarWinds and Microsoft hacks. How extensive was the damage inflicted and how should the west respond to such attacks?Clips: CBS, CNN, NBC Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/spyinginthedigitalage/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=0b5-C2sPB1FJ11stGT67sWRckmXn7INXVVT8SA4nixs</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 05:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:28</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/spyinginthedigitalage/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=0b5-C2sPB1FJ11stGT67sWRckmXn7INXVVT8SA4nixs" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Could this year mark a turning point for climate?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/couldthisyearmarkaturningpointforclimate-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=DAWij3yoFkAP679QSHCo21eN8nFRyvIxY12jluiHt3c</link>
			<description>Britain is hosting this year’s UN climate summit, COP26, in Glasgow. Pilita Clark discusses what these summits have achieved over the past three decades and what needs to be done to make the talks a success. Her guest is Richard Kinley, a veteran of the talks who is now president of the Foundation for Global Governance and Sustainability think-tank.Clips: Joe Biden; United Nations; Bloomberg  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/couldthisyearmarkaturningpointforclimate-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=DAWij3yoFkAP679QSHCo21eN8nFRyvIxY12jluiHt3c</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 05:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/couldthisyearmarkaturningpointforclimate-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=DAWij3yoFkAP679QSHCo21eN8nFRyvIxY12jluiHt3c" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Italy’s make or break moment</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/italy-smakeorbreakmoment/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=bqEUqQw92bEB4UpYQwrnT_vJ1uoSvqp6dC4FeKjydw4</link>
			<description>Ben Hall, the FT’s Europe editor, discusses Italy as former European Central Bank chief Mario Draghi takes on the premiership. How Draghi decides to spend up to €200bn in grants and loans from the EU recovery fund will be crucial, not just for Italy, but for the future direction of the EU. Ben’s guest is Enrico Letta, a former Italian prime minister, who is now dean of the Paris School of International Affairs at Sciences Po.Clips: UKTI; France 24; Channel 4  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/italy-smakeorbreakmoment/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=bqEUqQw92bEB4UpYQwrnT_vJ1uoSvqp6dC4FeKjydw4</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 05:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/italy-smakeorbreakmoment/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=bqEUqQw92bEB4UpYQwrnT_vJ1uoSvqp6dC4FeKjydw4" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Michael Mann on the politics of global warming</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/michaelmannonthepoliticsofglobalwarming/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=JIArU-i3c3ZV71DIDehUIuG-DIDM7JDD3t-4sit2mb0</link>
			<description>Pilita Clark talks to Michael Mann, distinguished professor of atmospheric science at Penn State university, and one of the world’s best-known climate scientists. They discuss the evolution of the climate change debate, from the war on science to denialism, doomism and the forces of ‘inactivism’.Clips: Nobel Prize, Euronews, Extinction Rebellion, Fox news  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/michaelmannonthepoliticsofglobalwarming/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=JIArU-i3c3ZV71DIDehUIuG-DIDM7JDD3t-4sit2mb0</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 05:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:30:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/michaelmannonthepoliticsofglobalwarming/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=JIArU-i3c3ZV71DIDehUIuG-DIDM7JDD3t-4sit2mb0" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The world in review</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theworldinreview/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=FYKhQk-1dDGAxk3uYaDGUW7tmT1ctJOm4-_L4WMc2og</link>
			<description>In a special retrospective episode, Gideon Rachman looks at some of his favourite podcast conversations that illuminate the state of geopolitics today, asking whether the pandemic has permanently changed the world. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theworldinreview/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=FYKhQk-1dDGAxk3uYaDGUW7tmT1ctJOm4-_L4WMc2og</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 05:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:04</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/theworldinreview/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=FYKhQk-1dDGAxk3uYaDGUW7tmT1ctJOm4-_L4WMc2og" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Britain’s post-Brexit role as ‘global broker’</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britain-spost-brexitroleas-globalbroker-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=BBSQpa4lNGI90MR8_i0wuVCNwhjl9mub_d2sjLE1bR4</link>
			<description>Prime Minister Boris Johnson’s diplomatic skills will be tested as host of both the G7 and UN COP26 climate change summit this year. Gideon talks to Robin Niblett, director of the Chatham House think-tank and economist Linda Yueh, currently a visiting professor at the London School of Economics, about Britain’s future role on the world stage. Clips: Parliamentlive, APFurther reading; LSE Economic Diplomacy Commission Chatham House: Global Britain, Global Broker Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britain-spost-brexitroleas-globalbroker-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=BBSQpa4lNGI90MR8_i0wuVCNwhjl9mub_d2sjLE1bR4</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 05:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/britain-spost-brexitroleas-globalbroker-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=BBSQpa4lNGI90MR8_i0wuVCNwhjl9mub_d2sjLE1bR4" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Navalny’s crusade against the Kremlin</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/navalny-scrusadeagainstthekremlin/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Y-ygZ9jMXWA_Lbcsx-nqeET59wwsqvzLn2g0lRQZs1s</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to journalists Arkady Ostrovsky and Max Seddon in Moscow about why Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny decided to return home after he was poisoned and what his political movement can achieve if its leader is in jail. Max Seddon is the FT’s Moscow correspondent and Arkady Ostrovsky is author of The Invention of Russia, winner of the 2016 Orwell Prize, and a staff journalist for The Economist.  Clips: Reuters, RFE/RL Russian Service, Al Jazeera English, “Aquadiskoteka” by Cream Soda Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/navalny-scrusadeagainstthekremlin/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Y-ygZ9jMXWA_Lbcsx-nqeET59wwsqvzLn2g0lRQZs1s</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 05:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:43</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/navalny-scrusadeagainstthekremlin/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Y-ygZ9jMXWA_Lbcsx-nqeET59wwsqvzLn2g0lRQZs1s" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>António Guterres on the United Nations in a fractured world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/antonioguterresontheunitednationsinafracturedworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vxek6GlnNVxQRgOgAW_FAaWD60SilNtWZNIHSc0PPJY</link>
			<description>The pandemic, climate change and peacekeeping are all priorities for the UN in 2021, but these challenges require multilateral solutions at a time when the world's superpowers are drifting further apart. Gideon Rachman talks to António Guterres, secretary-general of the UN, about bridging security and military divides to solve pressing global problems.  Review clips: World Economic Forum 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/antonioguterresontheunitednationsinafracturedworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vxek6GlnNVxQRgOgAW_FAaWD60SilNtWZNIHSc0PPJY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 08:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:02</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/antonioguterresontheunitednationsinafracturedworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vxek6GlnNVxQRgOgAW_FAaWD60SilNtWZNIHSc0PPJY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>António Guterres on the United Nations in a fractured world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/antonioguterresontheunitednationsinafracturedworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vxek6GlnNVxQRgOgAW_FAaWD60SilNtWZNIHSc0PPJY</link>
			<description>The pandemic, climate change and peacekeeping are all priorities for the UN in 2021, but these challenges require multilateral solutions at a time when the world's superpowers are drifting further apart. Gideon Rachman talks to António Guterres, secretary-general of the UN, about bridging security and military divides to solve pressing global problems.  Review clips: World Economic Forum Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/antonioguterresontheunitednationsinafracturedworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vxek6GlnNVxQRgOgAW_FAaWD60SilNtWZNIHSc0PPJY</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 05:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/antonioguterresontheunitednationsinafracturedworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=vxek6GlnNVxQRgOgAW_FAaWD60SilNtWZNIHSc0PPJY" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Germany after Merkel</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germanyaftermerkel/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Ipo_THNX5NvNfwqgq_7ctLIhpU-TL155Q2eKTSfjFZU</link>
			<description>Germany’s ruling Christian Democratic Union has chosen Armin Laschet to replace Angela Merkel as party leader ahead of September’s federal elections, paving the way for the end of the Merkel era. Gideon discusses what a post-Merkel Germany will look like with Wolfgang Ischinger, veteran diplomat and chairman of the Munich Security Conference. Clips: UK Parliament, Welt Nachrichten 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germanyaftermerkel/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Ipo_THNX5NvNfwqgq_7ctLIhpU-TL155Q2eKTSfjFZU</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 08:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germanyaftermerkel/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Ipo_THNX5NvNfwqgq_7ctLIhpU-TL155Q2eKTSfjFZU" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Germany after Merkel</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germanyaftermerkel/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Ipo_THNX5NvNfwqgq_7ctLIhpU-TL155Q2eKTSfjFZU</link>
			<description>Germany’s ruling Christian Democratic Union has chosen Armin Laschet to replace Angela Merkel as party leader ahead of September’s federal elections, paving the way for the end of the Merkel era. Gideon discusses what a post-Merkel Germany will look like with Wolfgang Ischinger, veteran diplomat and chairman of the Munich Security Conference. Clips: UK Parliament, Welt Nachrichten Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germanyaftermerkel/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Ipo_THNX5NvNfwqgq_7ctLIhpU-TL155Q2eKTSfjFZU</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 05:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:30</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germanyaftermerkel/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=Ipo_THNX5NvNfwqgq_7ctLIhpU-TL155Q2eKTSfjFZU" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America’s political meltdown</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-spoliticalmeltdown/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MEkeCRaQgPAPDUx9JxV4OPUixTz8LDe6tzYMnJ1gSVs</link>
			<description>After the storming of the Capitol, can America recover its democratic values? Gideon discusses what the recent lawlessness means for the US and its place in the world with Anne-Marie Slaughter, head of New America, a think-tank. 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-spoliticalmeltdown/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MEkeCRaQgPAPDUx9JxV4OPUixTz8LDe6tzYMnJ1gSVs</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 09:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:23:25</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-spoliticalmeltdown/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MEkeCRaQgPAPDUx9JxV4OPUixTz8LDe6tzYMnJ1gSVs" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>America’s political meltdown</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-spoliticalmeltdown/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MEkeCRaQgPAPDUx9JxV4OPUixTz8LDe6tzYMnJ1gSVs</link>
			<description>After the storming of the Capitol, can America recover its democratic values? Gideon discusses what the recent lawlessness means for the US and its place in the world with Anne-Marie Slaughter, head of New America, a think-tank. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-spoliticalmeltdown/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MEkeCRaQgPAPDUx9JxV4OPUixTz8LDe6tzYMnJ1gSVs</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 05:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:21</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/america-spoliticalmeltdown/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=MEkeCRaQgPAPDUx9JxV4OPUixTz8LDe6tzYMnJ1gSVs" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>David Miliband on the global leadership vacuum</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/davidmilibandonthegloballeadershipvacuum/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4SY3-khLRm_D6APWAAftGECsFWT52l9yjP_I0c0EsAs</link>
			<description>The former British foreign secretary championed the UK to remain in the EU. As head of the International Rescue Committee, David Miliband has seen the consequence of a lack of global leadership in helping the world’s vulnerable populations. In this episode, the FT’s Gideon Rachman talks to Mr Miliband about whether a “global Britain” after Brexit and a new US administration might bring a turn towards greater international cooperation.   Review clips: BBC, IRCNote: this interview was recorded before a mob of Trump supporters stormed the US Capitol building and interfered with the certification of Joe Biden's presidential victory.  
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/davidmilibandonthegloballeadershipvacuum/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4SY3-khLRm_D6APWAAftGECsFWT52l9yjP_I0c0EsAs</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 08:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/davidmilibandonthegloballeadershipvacuum/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4SY3-khLRm_D6APWAAftGECsFWT52l9yjP_I0c0EsAs" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>David Miliband on the global leadership vacuum</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/davidmilibandonthegloballeadershipvacuum/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4SY3-khLRm_D6APWAAftGECsFWT52l9yjP_I0c0EsAs</link>
			<description>The former British foreign secretary championed the UK to remain in the EU. As head of the International Rescue Committee, David Miliband has seen the consequence of a lack of global leadership in helping the world’s vulnerable populations. In this episode, the FT’s Gideon Rachman talks to Mr Miliband about whether a “global Britain” after Brexit and a new US administration might bring a turn towards greater international cooperation.   Review clips: BBC, IRCNote: this interview was recorded before a mob of Trump supporters stormed the US Capitol building and interfered with the certification of Joe Biden's presidential victory.  Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/davidmilibandonthegloballeadershipvacuum/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4SY3-khLRm_D6APWAAftGECsFWT52l9yjP_I0c0EsAs</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 05:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:59</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/davidmilibandonthegloballeadershipvacuum/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=4SY3-khLRm_D6APWAAftGECsFWT52l9yjP_I0c0EsAs" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The best and worst of 2020</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebestandworstof2020/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eVs53Fs_4WdIVLzNN9dWMb7piba9H6iQIuZeCvQFG64</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Roula Khalaf, FT editor, and Martin Wolf, chief economics commentator, about the extraordinary events of 2020 - from Covid-19 to the US election and unexpected signs of reconciliation between Israel and Arab Gulf states. 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebestandworstof2020/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eVs53Fs_4WdIVLzNN9dWMb7piba9H6iQIuZeCvQFG64</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 07:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebestandworstof2020/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eVs53Fs_4WdIVLzNN9dWMb7piba9H6iQIuZeCvQFG64" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The best and worst of 2020</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebestandworstof2020/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eVs53Fs_4WdIVLzNN9dWMb7piba9H6iQIuZeCvQFG64</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Roula Khalaf, FT editor, and Martin Wolf, chief economics commentator, about the extraordinary events of 2020 - from Covid-19 to the US election and unexpected signs of reconciliation between Israel and Arab Gulf states. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebestandworstof2020/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eVs53Fs_4WdIVLzNN9dWMb7piba9H6iQIuZeCvQFG64</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 05:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:40</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thebestandworstof2020/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=eVs53Fs_4WdIVLzNN9dWMb7piba9H6iQIuZeCvQFG64" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>EU at a turning point</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/euataturningpoint/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=LnUtfnVcp3KvrRpQKpdVRfNJFs85sjqwevHnu1GhjWw</link>
			<description>EU leaders are facing showdowns on several fronts this week, with the UK over Brexit, and with Hungary and Poland over the rule of law. Gideon discusses what’s at stake with Professor Catherine De Vries of Bocconi University in Italy. 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/euataturningpoint/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=LnUtfnVcp3KvrRpQKpdVRfNJFs85sjqwevHnu1GhjWw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 07:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/euataturningpoint/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=LnUtfnVcp3KvrRpQKpdVRfNJFs85sjqwevHnu1GhjWw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>EU at a turning point</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/euataturningpoint/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=LnUtfnVcp3KvrRpQKpdVRfNJFs85sjqwevHnu1GhjWw</link>
			<description>EU leaders are facing showdowns on several fronts this week, with the UK over Brexit, and with Hungary and Poland over the rule of law. Gideon discusses what’s at stake with Professor Catherine De Vries of Bocconi University in Italy. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/euataturningpoint/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=LnUtfnVcp3KvrRpQKpdVRfNJFs85sjqwevHnu1GhjWw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 05:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/euataturningpoint/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=LnUtfnVcp3KvrRpQKpdVRfNJFs85sjqwevHnu1GhjWw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Thai students call for change</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thaistudentscallforchange/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=c8KT6UP8EiEmIC9ALcTMG0ZGhY-ADzCr7T4hDjRgQ2Q</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Thai opposition leader Thanathorn Juangroongruangkit and John Reed, the FT’s Bangkok bureau chief, about the student protests that have challenged Thailand’s traditional power structures by demanding constitutional change. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thaistudentscallforchange/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=c8KT6UP8EiEmIC9ALcTMG0ZGhY-ADzCr7T4hDjRgQ2Q</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 05:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/thaistudentscallforchange/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&amp;sig=c8KT6UP8EiEmIC9ALcTMG0ZGhY-ADzCr7T4hDjRgQ2Q" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ethiopia’s struggle with ethnic nationalism</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ethiopia-sstrugglewithethnicnationalism/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=UFxxGJyQ_cuYtaJc5hECb4DMeHQDLtm5MhjgkfBWZ74</link>
			<description/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ethiopia-sstrugglewithethnicnationalism/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=UFxxGJyQ_cuYtaJc5hECb4DMeHQDLtm5MhjgkfBWZ74</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 20:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:35</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ethiopia-sstrugglewithethnicnationalism/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=UFxxGJyQ_cuYtaJc5hECb4DMeHQDLtm5MhjgkfBWZ74" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ethiopia’s struggle with ethnic nationalism</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ethiopia-sstrugglewithethnicnationalism/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=UFxxGJyQ_cuYtaJc5hECb4DMeHQDLtm5MhjgkfBWZ74</link>
			<description>A country that enjoyed decades of economc growth and stability now risks being torn apart by ethnic divisions. Gideon discusses what’s behind the outbreak of violence with Gabriel Negatu, a senior fellow at the Atlantic Council in Washington, and David Pilling, the FT’s Africa editor.Clips: Reuters, Live Aid Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ethiopia-sstrugglewithethnicnationalism/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=UFxxGJyQ_cuYtaJc5hECb4DMeHQDLtm5MhjgkfBWZ74</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 05:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:52</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/ethiopia-sstrugglewithethnicnationalism/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=UFxxGJyQ_cuYtaJc5hECb4DMeHQDLtm5MhjgkfBWZ74" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Macron's world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/macronsworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=qWnNZETGNcnaAC8phehqx5T1f6uri3jOfHA8nTrqrVw</link>
			<description/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/macronsworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=qWnNZETGNcnaAC8phehqx5T1f6uri3jOfHA8nTrqrVw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 16:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/macronsworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=qWnNZETGNcnaAC8phehqx5T1f6uri3jOfHA8nTrqrVw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Macron's world</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/macronsworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=qWnNZETGNcnaAC8phehqx5T1f6uri3jOfHA8nTrqrVw</link>
			<description>Gideon discusses the international ambitions, and problems, of the French president with Sylvie Kauffmann, editorial director of Le Monde. Are Emmanuel Macron’s views on European integration and strategic independence winning out? Clips: Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/macronsworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=qWnNZETGNcnaAC8phehqx5T1f6uri3jOfHA8nTrqrVw</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 05:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:21:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/macronsworld/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=qWnNZETGNcnaAC8phehqx5T1f6uri3jOfHA8nTrqrVw" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden’s global goals</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/biden-sglobalgoals/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=ScJ78HlGd7NtbnVZ4wPRdTCZzCZvO08TfIqP0tePOnE</link>
			<description/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/biden-sglobalgoals/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=ScJ78HlGd7NtbnVZ4wPRdTCZzCZvO08TfIqP0tePOnE</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:41</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/biden-sglobalgoals/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=ScJ78HlGd7NtbnVZ4wPRdTCZzCZvO08TfIqP0tePOnE" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Biden’s global goals</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/biden-sglobalgoals/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=ScJ78HlGd7NtbnVZ4wPRdTCZzCZvO08TfIqP0tePOnE</link>
			<description>Ivo Daalder, president of the Chicago Council on Global Affairs, served as US ambassador to Nato during the Obama years. He joins Gideon Rachman to talk about how Joe Biden may seek to rebuild the US’s broken alliances and project a new image to the world. Clips: CBS 60 Minutes; Reuters. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/biden-sglobalgoals/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=ScJ78HlGd7NtbnVZ4wPRdTCZzCZvO08TfIqP0tePOnE</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 05:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:45</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/biden-sglobalgoals/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=ScJ78HlGd7NtbnVZ4wPRdTCZzCZvO08TfIqP0tePOnE" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>An American chasm</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/anamericanchasm-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=AiVHLMQUOdSUoFOPXERFHIK7LH3pMjsK5PN9BQbNo-I</link>
			<description>Americans woke on November 4 to find that the result of their presidential election remained unclear. President Donald Trump’s statements about the integrity of the vote and his plan to dispute the final result at the Supreme Court signalled that the US could face days or weeks of political uncertainty. In this special early edition episode, Gideon talks to Jeremy Shapiro, a former US state department official and the current research director of the European Council on Foreign Relations, about the razor-thin election results so far, why the Democrats did not achieve a ‘blue wave’, and why, even in the event of a Joe Biden presidency, Trumpism is not going to disappear.Review clips: Reuters 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/anamericanchasm-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=AiVHLMQUOdSUoFOPXERFHIK7LH3pMjsK5PN9BQbNo-I</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 19:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:17:54</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/anamericanchasm-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=AiVHLMQUOdSUoFOPXERFHIK7LH3pMjsK5PN9BQbNo-I" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>An American chasm</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/anamericanchasm-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=AiVHLMQUOdSUoFOPXERFHIK7LH3pMjsK5PN9BQbNo-I</link>
			<description>Americans woke on November 4 to find that the result of their presidential election remained unclear. President Donald Trump’s statements about the integrity of the vote and his plan to dispute the final result at the Supreme Court signalled that the US could face days or weeks of political uncertainty. In this special early edition episode, Gideon talks to Jeremy Shapiro, a former US state department official and the current research director of the European Council on Foreign Relations, about the razor-thin election results so far, why the Democrats did not achieve a ‘blue wave’, and why, even in the event of a Joe Biden presidency, Trumpism is not going to disappear.Review clips: Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/anamericanchasm-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=AiVHLMQUOdSUoFOPXERFHIK7LH3pMjsK5PN9BQbNo-I</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 18:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:17:55</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/anamericanchasm-/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=AiVHLMQUOdSUoFOPXERFHIK7LH3pMjsK5PN9BQbNo-I" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Susan Glasser on the pandemic election</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/susanglasseronthepandemicelection/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=r3jVqmL7eaNY59MLHQZZGSKtdWsN0JbwohQXVtxUFuI</link>
			<description>The columnist has written about life in Trump’s Washington for The New Yorker magazine for almost four years. As voters head to the polls to elect the next US president, Gideon Rachman talks to Glasser about what to expect on November 3 — and after, if there is not a decisive victor and the election ends up in the courts.Review clips: C-SPAN, CNN, Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/susanglasseronthepandemicelection/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=r3jVqmL7eaNY59MLHQZZGSKtdWsN0JbwohQXVtxUFuI</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 05:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:39</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/susanglasseronthepandemicelection/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=r3jVqmL7eaNY59MLHQZZGSKtdWsN0JbwohQXVtxUFuI" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bringing history back to Burma</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/bringinghistorybacktoburma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=2SNGRMkdZQzUufFnHnNcAl1v1yFcs-IY3aQTRGxHqBE</link>
			<description>Western nations have tended to regard the recent history of Myanmar, formerly Burma, as a struggle between democracy and dictatorship. But the country’s colonial past and climate change have also played a key role in its complex problems, Burmese historian Thant Myint-U tells Gideon Rachman. Clips: ReutersThant’s book, The Hidden History of Burma, is published by Atlantic. 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/bringinghistorybacktoburma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=2SNGRMkdZQzUufFnHnNcAl1v1yFcs-IY3aQTRGxHqBE</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 16:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:05</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/bringinghistorybacktoburma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=2SNGRMkdZQzUufFnHnNcAl1v1yFcs-IY3aQTRGxHqBE" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bringing history back to Burma</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/bringinghistorybacktoburma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=2SNGRMkdZQzUufFnHnNcAl1v1yFcs-IY3aQTRGxHqBE</link>
			<description>Western nations have tended to regard the recent history of Myanmar, formerly Burma, as a struggle between democracy and dictatorship. But the country’s colonial past and climate change have also played a key role in its complex problems, Burmese historian Thant Myint-U tells Gideon Rachman. Clips: ReutersThant’s book, The Hidden History of Burma, is published by Atlantic. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/bringinghistorybacktoburma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=2SNGRMkdZQzUufFnHnNcAl1v1yFcs-IY3aQTRGxHqBE</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 04:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:27:14</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/bringinghistorybacktoburma/media.mp3?tk=eyJ0ayI6ImRlZmF1bHQiLCJhZHMiOnRydWUsInNwb25zIjp0cnVlfQ==&amp;sig=2SNGRMkdZQzUufFnHnNcAl1v1yFcs-IY3aQTRGxHqBE" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why humans wage wars</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyhumanswagewars/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon Rachman talks to historian Margaret MacMillan about her study of warfare through the ages and why she fears that, while the manner in which we wage war has changed, our propensity to stumble into conflict remains the same. Clips: ReutersMargaret MacMillan’s book War: How Conflict Shaped Us is published by Random House   
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyhumanswagewars/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:42</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyhumanswagewars/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why humans wage wars</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyhumanswagewars/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon Rachman talks to historian Margaret MacMillan about her study of warfare through the ages and why she fears that, while the manner in which we wage war has changed, our propensity to stumble into conflict remains the same. Clips: ReutersMargaret MacMillan’s book War: How Conflict Shaped Us is published by Random House   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyhumanswagewars/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 04:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:22:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/whyhumanswagewars/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>American entanglement in the Middle East</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americanentanglementinthemiddleeast/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Philip Gordon, a senior fellow at the Council on Foreign Relations, is a long-time Washington insider who worked on Middle East policy for the Obama administration and is now an informal adviser to the Biden campaign. In this episode, Gideon Rachman talks to him about the US presidential election and American policy in the Middle East — the subject of his new book, Losing the Long Game. After decades of American engagement in the region, Gordon shares his thoughts on why no recent US president has been able to ignore it.Review clips: C-SPAN--Read the FT's New Cold War series here: https://www.ft.com/content/4fda1b2c-48f5-42e0-9b87-58816adf2a78 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americanentanglementinthemiddleeast/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 17:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:12</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americanentanglementinthemiddleeast/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>American entanglement in the Middle East</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americanentanglementinthemiddleeast/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Philip Gordon, a senior fellow at the Council on Foreign Relations, is a long-time Washington insider who worked on Middle East policy for the Obama administration and is now an informal adviser to the Biden campaign. In this episode, Gideon Rachman talks to him about the US presidential election and American policy in the Middle East — the subject of his new book, Losing the Long Game. After decades of American engagement in the region, Gordon shares his thoughts on why no recent US president has been able to ignore it.Review clips: C-SPAN--Read the FT's New Cold War series here: https://www.ft.com/content/4fda1b2c-48f5-42e0-9b87-58816adf2a78 Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americanentanglementinthemiddleeast/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 04:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:25:24</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/americanentanglementinthemiddleeast/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>China’s second world war obsession</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/china-ssecondworldwarobsession/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China’s authorities have started to celebrate the country’s role in the second world war after long regarding it as a subject best forgotten. Gideon talks to the historian Rana Mitter about what’s behind this revised outlook on such a tormented period in the country’s history. Rana Mitter’s book China’s Good War is published by Harvard University Press. Clips: Reuters and ‘The Eight Hundred’ official trailer 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/china-ssecondworldwarobsession/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 17:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:11</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/china-ssecondworldwarobsession/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>China’s second world war obsession</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/china-ssecondworldwarobsession/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China’s authorities have started to celebrate the country’s role in the second world war after long regarding it as a subject best forgotten. Gideon talks to the historian Rana Mitter about what’s behind this revised outlook on such a tormented period in the country’s history. Rana Mitter’s book China’s Good War is published by Harvard University Press. Clips: Reuters and ‘The Eight Hundred’ official trailer Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/china-ssecondworldwarobsession/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 04:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:35:31</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/china-ssecondworldwarobsession/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mexico's populist president</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/mexicospopulistpresident/media.mp3</link>
			<description>When Andrés Manuel López Obrador, also known as Amlo, took office in late 2018 he promised a fourth political transformation of the country. Gideon Rachman talks to Jude Webber, the FT’s Mexico and Central America correspondent, about how Amlo’s plans to end 'neoliberalism' and fight corruption are faring during the coronavirus pandemic.   Review clips: Reuters, PBS News 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/mexicospopulistpresident/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:18:40</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/mexicospopulistpresident/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mexico's populist president</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/mexicospopulistpresident/media.mp3</link>
			<description>When Andrés Manuel López Obrador, also known as Amlo, took office in late 2018 he promised a fourth political transformation of the country. Gideon Rachman talks to Jude Webber, the FT’s Mexico and Central America correspondent, about how Amlo’s plans to end 'neoliberalism' and fight corruption are faring during the coronavirus pandemic.   Review clips: Reuters, PBS News Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/mexicospopulistpresident/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 04:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:01</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/mexicospopulistpresident/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>German diplomacy tested by multiple crises</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germandiplomacytestedbymultiplecrises/media.mp3</link>
			<description>From the poisoning of Russian opposition politician Alexei Navalny and pressure to cancel the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia, to the refugee catastrophe in Greece and headaches over Brexit, Germany has no shortage of foreign policy crises to deal with. Gideon Rachman discusses how best to handle them with Norbert Röttgen, chairman of the Bundestag’s foreign affairs committee and a long-shot contender to replace Angela Merkel as leader of the ruling Christian Democrats.  Clips: Reuters 
 See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germandiplomacytestedbymultiplecrises/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 16:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:24:48</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germandiplomacytestedbymultiplecrises/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>German diplomacy tested by multiple crises</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germandiplomacytestedbymultiplecrises/media.mp3</link>
			<description>From the poisoning of Russian opposition politician Alexei Navalny and pressure to cancel the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia, to the refugee catastrophe in Greece and headaches over Brexit, Germany has no shortage of foreign policy crises to deal with. Gideon Rachman discusses how best to handle them with Norbert Röttgen, chairman of the Bundestag’s foreign affairs committee and a long-shot contender to replace Angela Merkel as leader of the ruling Christian Democrats.  Clips: Reuters Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germandiplomacytestedbymultiplecrises/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 10:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:27</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/therachmanreview/germandiplomacytestedbymultiplecrises/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why we need the UN</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65c37061afd19a00160e466f/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Mark Malloch-Brown, former deputy secretary-general of the UN and president of the Open Society Foundation, about the role of the United Nations. While it sometimes struggles to make an impact on matters of global security, it plays a unique and often unrecognised role in shaping policy on migration, refugees and climate. Clip: The GuardianICJ’s Israel judgment seeks to restore rule of law to a brutal conflictHead of UN agency for Palestinians defies Israeli calls to quitA ‘multipolar’ world defies the ‘rules-based’ orderSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65c37061afd19a00160e466f/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:26:47</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65c37061afd19a00160e466f/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Is China’s power on the wane?</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65ccf74b49352e0016a72fcd/media.mp3</link>
			<description>China’s property crisis and slowing growth rate have raised questions about its future as an economic and military power. Gideon discusses whether it’s time to call ‘peak China’ with Richard McGregor, senior fellow at the Lowy Institute in Sydney. Clip: BloombergFree links to read more on this topic:China’s consumers tighten belts even as prices fallChina’s growth enigmaThe looming trade tensions over China’s subsidiesWe shouldn’t call ‘peak China’ just yetSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner. Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65ccf74b49352e0016a72fcd/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:29:53</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65ccf74b49352e0016a72fcd/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Russia’s threat to Europe </title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65d61fce3b050400172a3519/media.mp3</link>
			<description>How much of a threat would Russia pose to Europe if its invasion of Ukraine was successful? Given recent remarks by the US Republican presidential contender Donald Trump, does Europe have the firepower to defend itself without the aid of the US? Gideon discusses these questions with the writer and historian Anne Applebaum, just back from the 2024 Munich Security Conference. Clip: Deutsche WelleFree links to read more on this topic:Ursula von der Leyen calls on EU to subsidise defence productionRussian victories shake global leaders’ faith in Ukraine war prospectsAlexei Navalny, Russian opposition activist, 1976-2024Joe Biden blasts Donald Trump for ‘un-American’ comments about Nato alliesSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner.Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65d61fce3b050400172a3519/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:19:16</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65d61fce3b050400172a3519/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Global threats: the view from Sydney</title>
			<link>https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65df79ce5568ae00163e3d4d/media.mp3</link>
			<description>Gideon talks to Michael Fullilove, executive director of the Lowy institute in Sydney, about Australia’s relations with India and China, and how Australians view the threat to world order posed by the war in Ukraine and the possibility of a second Trump presidency. Clip: midday indiaFree links to read more on this topic:The squawkus about Aukus is getting louderLeaked Russian military files reveal criteria for nuclear strikeWhite House decision to not replace Asia tsar stokes concern among US allies Asia space race heats up as China, Japan and India reach for the starsSubscribe to The Rachman Review wherever you get your podcasts - please listen, rate and subscribe.Presented by Gideon Rachman. Produced by Fiona Symon. Sound design is by Breen Turner. Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65df79ce5568ae00163e3d4d/media.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 05:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>00:20:38</itunes:duration>
			<enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/therachmanreview/e/65df79ce5568ae00163e3d4d/media.mp3" length="31457280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
